<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arti on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/arti/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arti on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/arti/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Zor</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/24/zor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/24/zor/</guid>
      <description>Zor is a great YBBB we produced with our Kammerflage male from Gold Rush named Zozoro. We paired him to our gorgeous female from Arti x Alla, Artalla. He brings some great baby blue bars and a lime green to yellow body. We only paired him a few times before letting him go to his forever home.&#xA;Zor&#xA;Zor1&#xA;Zor2&#xA;Zor3&#xA;Zor4&#xA;Zor5&#xA;Zor6&#xA;Zor7&#xA;Zor8&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Zozoro Dam Artalla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/23/avana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/23/avana/</guid>
      <description>Avana has some great Kammerflage Kreations lineage from her sire, Zozoro, and her dam, Artalla. All of her brothers had yellow bodies and a few had deep blue bars. It will be a lot of fun to prove her out with Zandrin - hoping for those blue bars!&#xA;Avana&#xA;Avana1&#xA;Avana2&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Zozoro Dam Artalla 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Avana (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Avana (F4-CG14).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zozoro x Artalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/23/zozoro-artalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/23/zozoro-artalla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our only female from Arti x Alla, and our male from Kammerflage Kreations, Zozoro. Zozoro brings some nice yellow and blue. His yellow settled into a lime green at rest and his bars were more baby blue than royal blue. Whereas Arti had some great deep blue bars and bit less yellow in the body. This has a lot of Kammerflage on each side of the lineage and it is unrelated to our main line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony x Paige</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/10/tony-paige/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/10/tony-paige/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our our 4th gen HB from Nugget x Amara, Tony, and our female from Tiffany Mallay, Paige. Paige has great potential from Ambilobe lines from Tropical Chameleons and Modern Day Dragons, and Tony is the spitting image of his dam sire, Artemis, with a little extra yellow from Nugget. These guys hatched out strong and we&amp;rsquo;re hoping to do an encore pairing with Zandrin next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Manjalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/19/arti-manjalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/19/arti-manjalla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between one of our F1 females from Colorado Chameleon, Manjalla, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. They both come from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations. The clutch was small and Manjalla was very weak, so we were only able to keep one baby alive from this group.&#xA;Hatch dates 8/19/2022 - 8/20/2022 Hatch rate 2/17 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artilly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/03/artilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/03/artilly/</guid>
      <description>Artilly is a great YBBB from our Arti x Lilly pairing. Arti is one of our favorite ybbb breeders who we mixed in at the 3rd gen and Lilly is a female from our Jude x Kako group. We did not get too many examples from the small clutch that produced her, so it will be a lot of fun to prove her out!&#xA;Artilly&#xA;Artilly1&#xA;Artilly2&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Arti Dam Lilly 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Daisy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/17/arti-daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/17/arti-daisy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Daisy, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Daisy is a great female from our Jude x Kako clutch. Some of my favorite yellows came from this pairing and Daisy didn&amp;rsquo;t disappoint ;)&#xA;Arti x Daisy Hatch dates 10/17/2021 - 10/26/2021 Hatch rate 4/26 1st&#xA;Img 0370</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/17/ghost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/17/ghost/</guid>
      <description>Ghost is a 4th gen ybbb Ambilobe breeder here at iPardalis. He is from our Arti and Daisy pairing. His yellows are so light when he fires up that we decided to name him Ghost. They are just so clean and bright! There is also an H bar on his right side. We are very excited to have him carry the torch on this part of our tree.&#xA;Ghost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dehibe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/16/dehibe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/16/dehibe/</guid>
      <description>Dehibe is a great YBBB Ambilobe we produced with Arti and Alla. He brings some great blue bars and a yellow body, very similar to his sire. He and his sister, Artalla, were the only two babies to survive Alla&amp;rsquo;s last clutch, and they are very special to us. This is a great cb combination without any of our main line in it.&#xA;Dehibe&#xA;Dehibe1&#xA;Dehibe2&#xA;Dehibe3&#xA;Dehibe4&#xA;Dehibe5</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/15/artalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/15/artalla/</guid>
      <description>Artalla is a very special HB female from Arti, a great ybbb breeder for us produced by Brian Stewart, and Alla, one of our first females and most prolific breeder who gave us 17 clutches over her long life! Artalla has some big shoes to fill, and we are extremely excited to work with her :)&#xA;Artalla&#xA;Artalla1&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Arti Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Artalla (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Alla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/15/arti-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/15/arti-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our most prolific female from Panther Creek Chameleons, Alla, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Alla is a wonderful female from JJ who was produced by Kammerflage Kreations. We only had a single clutch from these two because it was towards the end of Alla&amp;rsquo;s breeding career.&#xA;Arti x Alla Hatch dates 10/15/2021 - 10/19/2021 Hatch rate 3/20 Dehibe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x CH Bohana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/09/15/arti-bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/09/15/arti-bohana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our first captive hatched (CH) female, Bohana, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Bohana is a female Ambilobe hatched out by Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics from a wild caught imported female. Bohana&amp;rsquo;s wild genes didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to add much to our project when combined with Arti, so we did not keep any of these animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Tigravavy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/28/arti-tigravavy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/28/arti-tigravavy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Tigravavy, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Tigravavy is a stunning female from our Jude x Alla clutch. We were very happy with these guys!&#xA;Arti x Tigravavy Hatch dates 6/28/2021 - 7/29/2021 Hatch rate 25/26 F1&#xA;F2&#xA;M1&#xA;M10&#xA;M2&#xA;M3&#xA;M4&#xA;M5&#xA;M6</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</guid>
      <description>Arti is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. He brings some great deep blue bars and a yellow body. We are very excited to see what he produces in concert with our existing lines!&#xA;Arti&#xA;Arti1&#xA;Arti2&#xA;Arti3&#xA;Arti4&#xA;Arti5&#xA;Arti6&#xA;Arti7&#xA;Arti8&#xA;Filial F3-CG12 Sire Artemis Dam Felipe Sanchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Arti Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Colorado Chameleon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/coloradochams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/coloradochams/</guid>
      <description> Colorado Chameleon Arlo (WC) Arlo&#xA;Arlo1&#xA;Arlo2&#xA;Artemis Artemis&#xA;Artemis1&#xA;Artemis2&#xA;Artemis3&#xA;Artemis4&#xA;Artemis5&#xA;Sire Fantara Dam Felipe Sannchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter Perregrin/Pryo&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Sire Perregrin/Pyro Dam Miss Piggy </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Brian Stewart</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/19/brianstewart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/19/brianstewart/</guid>
      <description> Phone (414-243-9995) McNulty Mcnulty&#xA;Mcnulty1&#xA;Mcnulty2&#xA;Sire Stryfe Dam Sire Unknown Kammers Sire Artemis&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Sire Artemis Dam Felipe Sanchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
