<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>imelda on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/imelda/</link>
    <description>Recent content in imelda on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/imelda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jimanga</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/12/03/jimanga/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/12/03/jimanga/</guid>
      <description>Jimanga is one of our 5th gen Ambilobe breeders. He comes from our Manga x Imelda pairing, a great collab with Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics. I can trace his personality all the way back to Kako. They teach you that chameleons are a look-but-don&amp;rsquo;t-touch pet, the hard way haha&amp;hellip; but what comes with that is an absolutely amazing defense display. Definitely something I really enjoy about these guys!
Jimanga
Jimanga1
Jimanga2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manga x Imelda</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/12/03/manga-imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/12/03/manga-imelda/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Manga, and our female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Imelda. Imelda is a great mix of WC Gambit lines and Kammerflage Kreations yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe while Manga is the male with the most striking yellows from our Bleu x Patch clutch. We kept Jimanga from this group and he has his father&amp;rsquo;s wonderful profile! Just a gorgeous group of Ambilobe.
Manga x Imelda Hatch dates 12/03/2021 - 2/19/2022 Hatch rate 15/19 M1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>imelda</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</guid>
      <description>Imelda brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She layed successfully, but we have been monitoring a minor gular edema on her. We adjusted her supplementation and feeding schedule. Hopefully, it clears up in no time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Ramblin&#39; Exotics</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/20/ramblin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/20/ramblin/</guid>
      <description> Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics Hendrix Hendrix
Hendrix1
Hendrix2
Sire Dante Dam Sunkist Foxey Foxey
Foxey1
Foxey2
Sire Landy (Silk) Dam Hamy (Sweetness) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Tropical Chameleons</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/20/tropical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/20/tropical/</guid>
      <description> Tropical Chameleons Dante Dante
Sire Gambit Dam Polaris Sunkist Sire Bolt Dam Test Sonny Sonny
Sonny1
Sire Giga-vony (Old Yeller) Dam Fanala-Andriana (Frost Queen) Sonny&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Sire Sonny Dam Unknown </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Mythical Exotics</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/19/mythicalexotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/19/mythicalexotics/</guid>
      <description>Mythical Exotics Zephyros Zephyros</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
