<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lokana on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/lokana/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lokana on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/lokana/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vaosary</title>
      <link>/blog/2022/01/12/vaosary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022/01/12/vaosary/</guid>
      <description>Vaosary is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has a rusty coloration with even more orange than her sister Bumble Bee. Her first pairing is with our new WC Ambilobe, so we expect her to produce some absolutely amazing F1 YBBB Ambilobe for us!
Vaosary
Vaosary1
Vaosary2
Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Vaosary (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bumble Bee</title>
      <link>/blog/2022/01/11/bumble-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022/01/11/bumble-bee/</guid>
      <description>Bumble Bee is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has a great personality and a rusty coloration with lots of orange and light purple dots. We expect her to produce some absolutely amazing Ambilobe for us!
Bumblebee
Bumblebee1
Bumblebee2
Bumblebee3
Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Bumble Bee (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Bumble Bee (F4-CG14). Bumble Bee was born on 2022-01-11 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papafee x Lokana</title>
      <link>/blog/2022/01/11/papafee-lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022/01/11/papafee-lokana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Papafee, and our Ambilobe female from Chromatic Chameleons, Lokana. Lokana is from a great pairing between Kromatisk and Shirley. Kromatisk is one of my favorite Ambilobe breeders in the USA and Shirley is from one of my favorite ybbb combinations from Kammerflage Kreations. Papafee is the HB male from our Zanaka x Sunny clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the fourth generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lokana</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</guid>
      <description>Lokana is the half-sister of Loko. They each have a 50% chance of bringing Kromatisk&amp;rsquo;s amazing ybbb into our project, but Lokana also has Landy x Hamy from her dam, Shirley&amp;rsquo;s side. Really can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with the two possibilities here. We are very excited to see how she proves out over the years :).
Lokana
mtDNA Haplogroup* 3 (Ambilobe East) Filial F9-CG12 Sire Kromatisk Dam Shirley *preliminary results</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Chromatic Chameleons</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/chromatic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/chromatic/</guid>
      <description> Chromatic Chameleons Felipe Sanchez Felipe
Felipe1
Felipe2
Felipe3
Sire Bolt Dam Cowboy&amp;rsquo;s daughter Kromatisk Kromatisk
Kromatisk1
Kromatisk2
Kromatisk3
Sire JJ Dam Jackie Jackie Sire Wet Dream Dam Marley&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Shirley Sire Landy (Silk) Dam Hamy (Sweetness) </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
