<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>parasites on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>https://ipardalis.com/tags/parasites/</link>
    <description>Recent content in parasites on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ipardalis.com/tags/parasites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Parasites and Ethics: Origin Story</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/07/18/parasites_origin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/07/18/parasites_origin/</guid>
      <description>Rye, for good luck.
We received 5 females from reputable CB sources that had issues during/after quarantine since 2017. The first 2 were in 2017. They never had great appetites and seemed to have respiratory issues. We brought them to the vet and kept them isolated for 60 days; however, the vet did not see anything wrong with them, and after they seemed to be healthy enough, we tried to breed them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parasites and Ethics: Intro</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/07/12/parasites_and_ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/07/12/parasites_and_ethics/</guid>
      <description>tldr;   Every animal you acquire, whether it be captive bred (CB) or wild caught (WC), should receive multiple fecal exams. A positive fecal should be managed in consultation with a qualified vet who has experience working with chameleons. Many different species of parasites do not shed at a constant rate, so a negative fecal is not a gaurantee that the animal is clean.    We found Coccidia in 2 out of 25 exams that we performed in June-July 2021, and plan to run fecals on every animal in our possession and share the results/methods here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
