<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blossom on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>https://ipardalis.com/tags/blossom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blossom on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ipardalis.com/tags/blossom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blossom</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</guid>
      <description>We got lucky holding back Blossom from Jude x Alla. He looks like a mini-JJ, Alla&amp;rsquo;s sire, and is a key member of our 3rd generation breeding group. His personality is very similar to Alla&amp;rsquo;s in that he is very bold and rarely defensive. His yellows are bright and his colors are very vibrant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alla</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</guid>
      <description>Alla is our most successful female breeder to date. She has a gregarious personality and brings some of the nicest YBBB Kammerflage Kreations lineage into our project via her sire, JJ. We were very lucky to pick her up from Panther Creek Chameleons back in 2017 before JJ was sold to Chromatic Chameleons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kammerflage Kreations</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</guid>
      <description>Kammerflage Kreations  Manome-toky (Promise Keeper)  Sire Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) Dam Vony-reny    Promise keeper
      Promise keeper1
      Promise keeper2
      Promise keeper3
      Promise keeper4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Creek Chameleons</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</guid>
      <description>Panther Creek  JJ   Jj
      Jj1
      Jj2
      Jj3
      Jj4
      Jj5
      Jj6
      Sire Mavo-ra (Yellow Blood) Dam Sire Kely-tongotra (Little Foot)   Wet Dream   Wetdream</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</guid>
      <description>Judy was our first generation breeder from Candy Cane (F1) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. She laid one good clutch for us but died during laying complications after 2 more infertile clutches.
  Judy (1)
      Judy (2)
      Judy (3)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</guid>
      <description>Flash was our first generation breeder from Cowboy (CH) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. He had a very gentle personality and only gave us one healthy clutch with Judy, from which we kept Jude. We were still learning when we got Flash and he passed after consuming a large number of wild bugs when pesticides had been applied to the lawn behind ours.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
