<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blossom on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/blossom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blossom on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/blossom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blossom x Mavokely</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/20/blossom-mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/20/blossom-mavokely/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Blossom, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Mavokely. Mavokely is from one of our favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe, Amarillo, and Blossom is the HB male from our Jude x Alla clutch. Great combination of colorful ybbb and clean yellows!
Blossom x Mavokely Hatch dates 6/20/2021 - 6/24/2021 Hatch rate 22/22 F1
F2
M2
M3
M4
Hatch dates 8/08/2021 - 8/22/2021 Hatch rate 23/26 F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kiborin</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/20/kiborin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/20/kiborin/</guid>
      <description>Kiborin is our 4th gen HB from Blossom x Maitso. He is Blaitso&amp;rsquo;s brother. These two are just amazing animals and we are excited to see Kiborin&amp;rsquo;s clean yellow with blue. He has less red highlighting that his father and a really clean look!
Kiborin
Kiborin1
Kiborin2
Kiborin3
Kiborin4
Filial F4-CG13 Sire Blossom Dam Maitso 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Kiborin (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1. Kiborin (F4-CG13). Kiborin was born on 2021-06-19 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blaitso</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/19/blaitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/19/blaitso/</guid>
      <description>Blaitso is a drop dead gorgeous 4th gen female from our Blossom x Maitso. She has vibrant oranges, a great bar/body contrast and teal cheeks. Her lineage is also amazing so she will be fun to watch! We are lucky to have her in our breeding group.
Blaitso
Blaitso1
Blaitso2
Blaitso3
Blaitso4
Blaitso5
Filial F4-CG13 Sire Blossom Dam Maitso 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Blaitso (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blossom x Maitso</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/01/27/blossom-maitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/01/27/blossom-maitso/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Blossom, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Maitso. Maitso is from one of our favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe, Amarillo, and Blossom is the HB male from our Jude x Alla clutch. Great combination of colorful ybbb and clean yellows! Kiborin is our keeper from this group.
Blossom x Maitso Hatch dates 1/27/2021 - 3/07/2021 Hatch rate 25/27 1st
10th</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blossom</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</guid>
      <description>We got lucky holding back Blossom from Jude x Alla. He looks like a mini-JJ, Alla&amp;rsquo;s sire, and is a key member of our 3rd generation breeding group. His personality is very similar to Alla&amp;rsquo;s in that he is very bold and rarely defensive. His yellows are bright and his colors are very vibrant. I could not be happier with how he has turned out!
Blossom
Blossom1
Blossom2
Blossom3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alla</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</guid>
      <description>Alla is our most successful female breeder to date. She has a gregarious personality and brings some of the nicest YBBB Kammerflage Kreations lineage into our project via her sire, JJ. We were very lucky to pick her up from Panther Creek Chameleons back in 2017 before JJ was sold to Chromatic Chameleons.
Alla
Alla1
Alla2
Filial Unknown Sire JJ Dam Blue Bird&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 3 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Alla Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.
Body shot
Dsc00380
Dsc00383
Jude
Jude2
Filial Group F2 Sire Flash Dam Judy 4 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Jude (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kammerflage Kreations</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</guid>
      <description>Kammerflage Kreations Manome-toky (Promise Keeper) Sire Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) Dam Vony-reny Promise keeper
Promise keeper1
Promise keeper2
Promise keeper3
Promise keeper4
Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) 67102557 214752709408715 5451583889820614656 n
67119195 2313830222028769 4345136138969677824 n
Ankoso-bolamena (Goldie) Sire Ihany-drako (My Friend) Dam Hay-vao (Novel) Ihany-drako (My Friend) Sire Ampiosonga-fantatra (Also Known As) Dam Unknown My friend
Myfriend
Myfriend1
Hay-vao (Novel) Sire WC Bakaina (Divergent) Dam Goavy (Guava) Ampiosonga-fantatra (Also Known As) Sire Unknown Dam Unknown Alsoknownas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Creek Chameleons</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</guid>
      <description>Panther Creek JJ Jj
Jj1
Jj2
Jj3
Jj4
Jj5
Jj6
Sire Mavo-ra (Yellow Blood) Dam Sire Kely-tongotra (Little Foot) Wet Dream Wetdream
Wetdream1
Wetdream2
Sire Macho Dam Sire 24k&amp;rsquo;s daughter Test Sire Bolt Dam Sire Marley </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy</title>
      <link>/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</guid>
      <description>Judy was our first generation breeder from Candy Cane (F1) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. She laid one good clutch for us but died during laying complications after 2 more infertile clutches.
Judy (1)
Judy (2)
Judy (3)
Judy (4)
Judy (6)
Judy 1 year
Filial Group F2 Sire Candy Cane Dam Jake&amp;rsquo;s daughter 3 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Judy (F2) Generation 1 1. Judy (F2). Judy was born on 2015-02-11 at Chameleon&#39;s Paradise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash</title>
      <link>/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</guid>
      <description>Flash was our first generation breeder from Cowboy (CH) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. He had a very gentle personality and only gave us one healthy clutch with Judy, from which we kept Jude. We were still learning when we got Flash and he passed after consuming a large number of wild bugs when pesticides had been applied to the lawn behind ours. The vet said that he had kidney failure like he&amp;rsquo;d been poisoned, but we have been continuing to improve our husbandry year-after-year in his honor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
