<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pyro on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/pyro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pyro on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/pyro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mena</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/27/mena/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/27/mena/</guid>
      <description>Mena is our HB from Zava and F1 Manjaya. Zava had a significant amount of red and a few of Mena&amp;rsquo;s brothers got it, too. Manjaya seems to have taken after her WC sire, Arlo. A few of Mena&amp;rsquo;s brothers looked like mini Arlo&amp;rsquo;s. So less of the Perregrin/Pyro side of the lineage, more of the WC Arlo combined with Zava is what she brings to the table.&#xA;Mena</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jiolahy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/14/jiolahy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/14/jiolahy/</guid>
      <description>Jiolahy is a big F1 female from Chameleons 101&amp;rsquo;s The Don (WC). She brings fresh ybbb genetics combined with a great CB ybbb line created by Modern Day Dragons. We are very lucky to have her in our breeding group.&#xA;Jiolahy&#xA;Filial F1-CG5 Sire The Don (WC) Dam Perregrin/Pyro&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Jiolahy (F1-CG5) Generation 1 1. Jiolahy (F1-CG5). Jiolahy was born on 2021-07-14 at Eric Thompson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>paige</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/17/paige/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/17/paige/</guid>
      <description>Paige is a solid Modern Day Dragons x Tropical Chameleons YBBB female. She has great purples and pinks and a wonderful personality. We are very lucky to have her in our project and comes to us from Tiffany Mallay. Her first pairing will be with our 4th gen sire, Tony.&#xA;Paige&#xA;Paige1&#xA;Paige2&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire PJ Dam Sonny&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Paige (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>manjaya</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/06/manjaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/06/manjaya/</guid>
      <description>Manjaya s Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s sister and she brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with his daughters!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>manjalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/05/manjalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/05/manjalla/</guid>
      <description>Manjalla is Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s sister and she brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with his daughter!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaia/</guid>
      <description>Manjaia is Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s 3rd sister we own, and she also brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with his daughter!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</guid>
      <description>Manjaka brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with him!&#xA;Manjaka&#xA;Manjaka1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Modern Day Dragons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/moderndaydragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/moderndaydragons/</guid>
      <description> Modern Day Dragons Miss Piggy Sire Higgins Dam Sire Candy Cane PJ Pj&#xA;Pj1&#xA;Pj2&#xA;Sire Perregrin/Pyro Dam Miss Piggy </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
