<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alfred on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/alfred/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alfred on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/alfred/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ralph x Mainty</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/15/ralph-mainty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/15/ralph-mainty/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our forth generation hold back, Ralph, and our female from Nature&amp;rsquo;s Van Gogh, Mainty. Mainty has a few rainbow brothers and a few RBBB brothers, so it will be fun to see which side she brings here. We paired Mainty with Kosmo after she had an infertile clutch after Ralph. We will probably not keep any of these wonderful animals because of our long-term plans for Mainty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ralph</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/05/ralph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/05/ralph/</guid>
      <description>Ralph is a great 4th generation continuation of the Alfred line with vibrant blues and reds! Alfred was an odd ball from our Jude x Alla pairing, so these red-heavy Ambilobe are not closely related to many of the other red Ambilobe out there. We plan to keep him paired to one or two females and only do a few clutches with this fun side project.&#xA;Ralph&#xA;Ralph1&#xA;Ralph2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alfred x Kanto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/13/alfred-kanto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/13/alfred-kanto/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Alfred, and our female from Frank Payne, Kanto, from Living Art by Frank Payne. Kanto comes from some great OBBB/RBBB lines from Canvas Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Alfred is the male with the most red from our Jude x Alla clutch. We kept Ralph from this group and he is a wonderful RBBB!&#xA;Alfred x Kanto Hatch dates 4/13/2021 - 5/04/2021 Hatch rate 22/24 No pictures available</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alfred</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</guid>
      <description>Alfred is an extreme outlier from the Jude x Alla pairing. We were lucky to keep him because he carries some vibrant, almost dark neon colors. His resting colors are some of the nicest I have ever seen in person and I am very excited to work with him moving forward!&#xA;Alfred&#xA;Alfred1&#xA;Alfred2&#xA;Alfred3&#xA;Alfred4&#xA;Alfred5&#xA;Alfred6&#xA;Alfred7&#xA;Alfred8&#xA;Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</guid>
      <description>Alla is our most successful female breeder to date. She has a gregarious personality and brings some of the nicest YBBB Kammerflage Kreations lineage into our project via her sire, JJ. We were very lucky to pick her up from Panther Creek Chameleons back in 2017 before JJ was sold to Chromatic Chameleons.&#xA;Alla&#xA;Alla1&#xA;Alla2&#xA;Filial F8-CG11 Sire JJ Dam Blue Bird&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Alla Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.&#xA;Body shot&#xA;Dsc00380&#xA;Dsc00383&#xA;Jude&#xA;Jude2&#xA;Filial Group F2 Sire Flash Dam Judy 4 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Jude (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kammerflage Kreations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</guid>
      <description>Kammerflage Kreations Manome-toky (Promise Keeper) Sire Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) Dam Vony-reny Promise keeper&#xA;Promise keeper1&#xA;Promise keeper2&#xA;Promise keeper3&#xA;Promise keeper4&#xA;Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) 67102557 214752709408715 5451583889820614656 n&#xA;67119195 2313830222028769 4345136138969677824 n&#xA;Ankoso-bolamena (Goldie) Sire Ihany-drako (My Friend) Dam Hay-vao (Novel) Ihany-drako (My Friend) Sire Ampiosonga-fantatra (Also Known As) Dam Unknown My friend&#xA;Myfriend&#xA;Myfriend1&#xA;Hay-vao (Novel) Sire WC Bakaina (Divergent) Dam Goavy (Guava) Ampiosonga-fantatra (Also Known As) Sire Unknown Dam Unknown Alsoknownas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Creek Chameleons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</guid>
      <description>Panther Creek JJ Jj&#xA;Jj1&#xA;Jj2&#xA;Jj3&#xA;Jj4&#xA;Jj5&#xA;Jj6&#xA;Sire Mavo-ra (Yellow Blood) Dam Sire Kely-tongotra (Little Foot) Wet Dream Wetdream&#xA;Wetdream1&#xA;Wetdream2&#xA;Sire Macho Dam Sire 24k&amp;rsquo;s daughter Test Sire Marley Dam Sire Unknown </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</guid>
      <description>Judy was our first generation breeder from Candy Cane (F1) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. She laid one good clutch for us but died during laying complications after 2 more infertile clutches.&#xA;Judy (1)&#xA;Judy (2)&#xA;Judy (3)&#xA;Judy (4)&#xA;Judy (6)&#xA;Judy 1 year&#xA;Filial Group F2 Sire Candy Cane Dam Jake&amp;rsquo;s daughter 3 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Judy (F2) Generation 1 1. Judy (F2). Judy was born on 2015-02-11 at Chameleon&#39;s Paradise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</guid>
      <description>Flash was our first generation breeder from Cowboy (CH) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. He had a very gentle personality and only gave us one healthy clutch with Judy, from which we kept Jude. We were still learning when we got Flash and he passed after consuming a large number of wild bugs when pesticides had been applied to the lawn behind ours. The vet said that he had kidney failure like he&amp;rsquo;d been poisoned, but we have been continuing to improve our husbandry year-after-year in his honor.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
