<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Past Clutches @ iPardalis on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/past-clutches/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Past Clutches @ iPardalis on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/past-clutches/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WC Bibi x Mamony</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/07/06/bibi-mamony/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/07/06/bibi-mamony/</guid>
      <description>This pairing is a great F1 group with WC Bibi paired to our 4th gen female named Mamony from Blossom x Maitso. Our hope is that the strong blues on the female side of this lineage will help clean up the mixed bar look of WC Bibi and he&amp;rsquo;ll bring some size and fresh genetics into the mix. WC Bibi&amp;rsquo;s yellows are very interesting and slightly different from Blossom&amp;rsquo;s, so it will also be interesting to watch these animals as they mature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WC Dia x Vaosary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/29/dia-vaosary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/29/dia-vaosary/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was the only successful clutch with WC Dia. We paired him to our 5th gen female named Vaosary from Papafee x Lokana. Vaosary was a stand out female with a lot of orange from one of my favorite 5th gen groups. Because of how rare this line will be, they are a great option for breeders looking for high-quality foundation animals at the F1 generation. Really love that we got some WC Dia and Papafee clones in the mix here - very cool stuff!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimanga x Bumblebee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/28/jimanga-bumblebee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/28/jimanga-bumblebee/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our 5th gen male named Jimanga from Manga x Imelda, and a 5th gen female named Bumble Bee from Papafee x Lokana. This is the combination of two of our favorite lines and the culmination of years of selective breeding for yellow body blue bar traits. If they don&amp;rsquo;t prove out, we have no one to blame but ourselves! ;)&#xA;Hatch dates 6/28/23 - 7/10/23 Hatch rate 23/26 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiborin x Maize</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/03/10/kiborin-maize/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/03/10/kiborin-maize/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our male named Kiborin from Blossom x Maitso, and a female we picked up from Brian Stewart, Maize. Maize seems to be throwing everything from a beautiful orange body blue bar to a yellow body blue bar while Kiborin was one of our favorite yellow body blue bars from Blossom. This group has been very vibrant and a few males have had the ability to fire up to to point where their blue bars almost go white!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zozoro x Artalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/23/zozoro-artalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/23/zozoro-artalla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our only female from Arti x Alla, and our male from Kammerflage Kreations, Zozoro. Zozoro brings some nice yellow and blue. His yellow settled into a lime green at rest and his bars were more baby blue than royal blue. Whereas Arti had some great deep blue bars and bit less yellow in the body. This has a lot of Kammerflage on each side of the lineage and it is unrelated to our main line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ralph x Mainty</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/15/ralph-mainty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/15/ralph-mainty/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our forth generation hold back, Ralph, and our female from Nature&amp;rsquo;s Van Gogh, Mainty. Mainty has a few rainbow brothers and a few RBBB brothers, so it will be fun to see which side she brings here. We paired Mainty with Kosmo after she had an infertile clutch after Ralph. We will probably not keep any of these wonderful animals because of our long-term plans for Mainty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zandrin x Mara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/12/21/zandrin-mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/12/21/zandrin-mara/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female Mara from Chi-town Chameleons, and our 4th gen male, Zandrin. Zandrin was our favorite YBBB from Nugget and Mara brings the WC Legion line into our project via Nova. If we can get a HB that looks remotely similar to Zandrin x Nova, we will be super excited about this line :)&#xA;Hatch dates 12/04/22 - 12/21/2022 Hatch rate 32/40 F1&#xA;F10&#xA;F11</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Noko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/29/manjaka-noko/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/29/manjaka-noko/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female from Nugget x Loko, and our male from Colorado Chameleons, F1 Manjaka. Manjaka was pretty unassuming as a juvenile, but he became one of our favorite YBBB Ambilobe breeders as an adult. He had an extra blue bar, and yellows were classic Ambilobe. Loko came to us from Chromatic Chameleons and Nugget is our favorite 3rd gen YBBB breeder.&#xA;Hatch dates 11/19/22 - 11/29/22 Hatch rate 24/24 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Tigerlilly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/07/manjaka-tigerlilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/07/manjaka-tigerlilly/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female from Nugget x Amara, and our male from Colorado Chameleons, F1 Manjaka. Manjaka was pretty unassuming as a juvenile, but he became one of our favorite YBBB Ambilobe breeders as an adult. He had an extra blue bar, and yellows were classic Ambilobe. Amara came to us from Brian Stewart and her lineage is more rainbow Ambilobe.&#xA;Hatch dates 11/03/22 - 11/07/2022 Hatch rate 23/23 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony x Paige</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/10/tony-paige/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/10/tony-paige/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our our 4th gen HB from Nugget x Amara, Tony, and our female from Tiffany Mallay, Paige. Paige has great potential from Ambilobe lines from Tropical Chameleons and Modern Day Dragons, and Tony is the spitting image of his dam sire, Artemis, with a little extra yellow from Nugget. These guys hatched out strong and we&amp;rsquo;re hoping to do an encore pairing with Zandrin next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zava x Nuhana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/25/zava-nuhana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/25/zava-nuhana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our F1 female from Nugget x CH Bohana, and our male from Kammerflage Kreations, Zava. Zava was a vibrant rainbow Ambilobe. His yellow sat on top of a bright red dermal layer, and his bars were deep royal blue. F1 Nuhana brings fresh genetics and a chance at Nugget&amp;rsquo;s neon yellow body with blue bars.&#xA;Hatch dates 7/18/22 - 8/25/2022 Hatch rate 17/25 F1&#xA;M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zava x Manjaya</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/21/zava-manjaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/21/zava-manjaya/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our F1 female from WC Arlo x Perregrin/Pyro&amp;rsquo;s daughter, and our male from Kammerflage Kreations, Zava. Zava was a vibrant rainbow Ambilobe. His yellow sat on top of a bright red dermal layer, and his bars were deep royal blue. F1 Manjaya brings fresh genetics and a chance at that Perregrin/Sparkles yellow.&#xA;Hatch dates 7/27/22 - 8/21/2022 Hatch rate 8/14 F1&#xA;F2&#xA;F3&#xA;M1&#xA;M2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Manjalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/19/arti-manjalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/19/arti-manjalla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between one of our F1 females from Colorado Chameleon, Manjalla, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. They both come from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations. The clutch was small and Manjalla was very weak, so we were only able to keep one baby alive from this group.&#xA;Hatch dates 8/19/2022 - 8/20/2022 Hatch rate 2/17 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackson x Imelda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/16/jackson-imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/16/jackson-imelda/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Jackson, and our female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Imelda. Imelda is a great mix of WC Gambit lines and Kammerflage Kreations yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe while Jackson is the most vibrant male from our Jack x Mavokely clutch. We will definitely keep this line in our project in the years to come!&#xA;Hatch dates 7/14/2022 - 8/16/2022 Hatch rate 29/38 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Parasy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/26/manjaka-parasy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/26/manjaka-parasy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female from Jack x Mavokely, and our male from Colorado Chameleons, F1 Manjaka. Manjaka was pretty unassuming as a juvenile, but he became one of our favorite YBBB Ambilobe breeders as an adult. He had an extra blue bar, and yellows were classic Ambilobe. Mavokely came to us from Bobby Ruddock and she brings some of my favorite YBBB Ambilobe genetics - Amarillo.&#xA;Hatch dates 7/26/22 - 8/20/2022 Hatch rate 8/18 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Lokana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/05/manjaka-lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/05/manjaka-lokana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our F1 sire from Colorado Chameleons, Manjaka, and our female from Chromatic Chameleons, Lokana. Lokana is a mix of Chromatic and Kammerflage Kreations yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe while Manjaka is a wonderful YBBB from a recent import, WC Arlo. The outcomes have been extremely consiste YBBB thus far which are not directly related to our main line of Ambilobe. They are a great option for people looking for high quality pairings with our multi-generational lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papafee x Lokana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/11/papafee-lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/11/papafee-lokana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Papafee, and our Ambilobe female from Chromatic Chameleons, Lokana. Lokana is from a great pairing between Kromatisk and Shirley. Kromatisk is one of my favorite Ambilobe breeders in the USA and Shirley is from one of my favorite ybbb combinations from Kammerflage Kreations. Papafee is the HB male from our Zanaka x Sunny clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the fourth generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papafee x Coco</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/04/papafee-coco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/04/papafee-coco/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Papafee, and our little Ambilobe female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Coco. Coco is from a great pairing between Hendrix and Foxey. Hendrix brings a new WC Ambilobe line into the project and Foxey is from one of my favorite ybbb combinations from Kammerflage Kreations. Papafee is the HB male from our Zanaka x Sunny clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the fourth generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manga x Imelda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/manga-imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/manga-imelda/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Manga, and our female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Imelda. Imelda is a great mix of WC Gambit lines and Kammerflage Kreations yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe while Manga is the male with the most striking yellows from our Bleu x Patch clutch. We kept Jimanga from this group and he has his father&amp;rsquo;s wonderful profile! Just a gorgeous group of Ambilobe.&#xA;Hatch dates 12/03/2021 - 2/19/2022 Hatch rate 15/19 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Daisy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/17/arti-daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/17/arti-daisy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Daisy, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Daisy is a great female from our Jude x Kako clutch. Some of my favorite yellows came from this pairing and Daisy didn&amp;rsquo;t disappoint ;)&#xA;Arti x Daisy Hatch dates 10/17/2021 - 10/26/2021 Hatch rate 4/26 1st&#xA;Img 0370</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Alla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/15/arti-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/15/arti-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our most prolific female from Panther Creek Chameleons, Alla, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Alla is a wonderful female from JJ who was produced by Kammerflage Kreations. We only had a single clutch from these two because it was towards the end of Alla&amp;rsquo;s breeding career.&#xA;Arti x Alla Hatch dates 10/15/2021 - 10/19/2021 Hatch rate 3/20 Dehibe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x CH Bohana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/09/15/arti-bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/09/15/arti-bohana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our first captive hatched (CH) female, Bohana, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Bohana is a female Ambilobe hatched out by Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics from a wild caught imported female. Bohana&amp;rsquo;s wild genes didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to add much to our project when combined with Arti, so we did not keep any of these animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Tigravavy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/28/arti-tigravavy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/28/arti-tigravavy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Tigravavy, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Tigravavy is a stunning female from our Jude x Alla clutch. We were very happy with these guys!&#xA;Arti x Tigravavy Hatch dates 6/28/2021 - 7/29/2021 Hatch rate 25/26 F1&#xA;F2&#xA;M1&#xA;M10&#xA;M2&#xA;M3&#xA;M4&#xA;M5&#xA;M6</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blossom x Mavokely</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/20/blossom-mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/20/blossom-mavokely/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Blossom, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Mavokely. Mavokely is from one of our favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe, Amarillo, and Blossom is the HB male from our Jude x Alla clutch. Great combination of colorful ybbb and clean yellows!&#xA;Blossom x Mavokely Hatch dates 6/20/2021 - 6/24/2021 Hatch rate 22/22 F1&#xA;F2&#xA;M2&#xA;M3&#xA;M4&#xA;Hatch dates 8/08/2021 - 8/22/2021 Hatch rate 23/26 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Loko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/03/nugget-loko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/03/nugget-loko/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our gorgeous Ambilobe female from Chromatic Chameleons, Loko. Loko is from a great pairing between Kromatisk and Wet Dream - a ybbb x ybbb Ambilobe combination. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination with our favorite third gen yellow male with an extremely high quality yellow female!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Amara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/nugget-amara/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/nugget-amara/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our female from Brian Stewart, Amara. Amara proved out to carry a lot of her sire&amp;rsquo;s, Artemis&amp;rsquo;, traits like his dark blue bars and red highlighting. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination of colorful ybbb with both blue bars and clean yellows!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alfred x Kanto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/13/alfred-kanto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/13/alfred-kanto/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Alfred, and our female from Frank Payne, Kanto, from Living Art by Frank Payne. Kanto comes from some great OBBB/RBBB lines from Canvas Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Alfred is the male with the most red from our Jude x Alla clutch. We kept Ralph from this group and he is a wonderful RBBB!&#xA;Alfred x Kanto Hatch dates 4/13/2021 - 5/04/2021 Hatch rate 22/24 No pictures available</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x CH Bohana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/11/nugget-bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/11/nugget-bohana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our captive-hatched Ambilobe female from Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics, Bohana. Bohana was hatched from a wild caught female&amp;rsquo;s clutch of eggs and she seems to have a complex set of colors without a dominant phenotype. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination of wild Ambilobe genetics and clean yellows!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Daisy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/03/08/zanaka-daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/03/08/zanaka-daisy/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project.&#xA;Zanaka x Daisy F3-CG5&#xA;Hatch dates 3/8/2021 - 3/20/2021 Hatch rate 21/26 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blossom x Maitso</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/27/blossom-maitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/27/blossom-maitso/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Blossom, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Maitso. Maitso is from one of our favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe, Amarillo, and Blossom is the HB male from our Jude x Alla clutch. Great combination of colorful ybbb and clean yellows! Kiborin is our keeper from this group.&#xA;Blossom x Maitso Hatch dates 1/27/2021 - 3/07/2021 Hatch rate 25/27 1st&#xA;10th</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack x Mavokely</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Jack, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Mavokely. Jack had some of the nicest yellows from Jude x Alla and Bobby&amp;rsquo;s boy Amarillo is one of my favorite ybbb of all time. These guys should be very special.&#xA;Jack x Mavokely Hatch dates 1/20/2021 - 3/17/2021 Hatch rate 3/21 M1&#xA;Hb&#xA;Hb1&#xA;Jackson1&#xA;Jackson4</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Bubbles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/10/15/zanaka-bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/10/15/zanaka-bubbles/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project.&#xA;1st Clutch F3-CG13&#xA;Hatch dates 10/15/2020 - 10/17/2020 Hatch rate 37/39 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bleu x Patch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/09/12/bleu-patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/09/12/bleu-patch/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Patch, and our male from Jeremy Booker, Bleu, from Brightside Chameleons. Bleu is the only male with Stryfe in him and we are excited to see what that brings to the project. Manga was our keeper from this group.&#xA;Bleu x Patch Hatch dates 9/12/2020 - 9/27/2020 Hatch rate 29/32 F1&#xA;F2&#xA;F3&#xA;F4&#xA;Img 3183&#xA;M1&#xA;M2&#xA;Manga7&#xA;Hatch dates 10/28/2020 - 11/17/2020 Hatch rate 33/41 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Sunny</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project. Papafee is our keeper from this group.&#xA;Zanaka x Sunny F3&#xA;Hatch dates 7/17/2020 - 7/28/2020 Hatch rate 28/29 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Alla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing is between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our most successful female, Alla, from RB Barto @Panther Creek Chameleons. Nugget is one of my favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe paired with an all-time great in JJ who comes from some of the most popular Ambilobe lines at Kammerflage Kreations.&#xA;Nugget x Alla F4&#xA;Hatch dates 7/10/2020 - 7/31/2020 Hatch rate 15/20 Aw&#xA;Hb&#xA;Hb1&#xA;Jh&#xA;M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Alla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</guid>
      <description>This has been our most successful pairing to-date. Alla is an amazing female Ambilobe that we purchased from RB Barto in 2017. She has been producing clutches between 25-34 eggs every 60 to 90 days ever since!&#xA;We decided to keep Blossom, Jack, and Afred from this pairing as well as numerous females.&#xA;Jude x Alla Filial F3 Hatch dates 7/9/2019 - 7/20/2019 Hatch rate 30/31 Dsc02741&#xA;Img 2442</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Kako</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/05/jude-kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/05/jude-kako/</guid>
      <description>This pairing gave us Nugget, Patch, Sunny, Lilly, and Daisy.&#xA;Jude x Kako F2&#xA;Hatch dates 6/5/2019 - 6/19/2019 Hatch rate 34/34 Daisy&#xA;Img 1&#xA;Img 11&#xA;Img 2&#xA;Img 2535&#xA;Img 2584&#xA;Img 2587&#xA;Img 2612&#xA;Img 2619&#xA;Img 2631&#xA;Img 2678&#xA;Img 2718&#xA;Img 2780&#xA;Img 2813&#xA;Img 2828&#xA;Img 2857&#xA;Img 2917&#xA;Img 2919&#xA;Img 2954&#xA;Img 2977&#xA;Img 3224&#xA;Img 3632&#xA;Img 3642&#xA;Img 3873</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash x Judy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/10/17/flash-judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/10/17/flash-judy/</guid>
      <description>This was our first clutch. Both parents, Flash and Judy, were sourced from Bruce Galbraith at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. Our hatch rate was ~50% and 4 of the babies did not make it to the 3 month mark. That was the baseline that we have tried to improve upon. For this clutch, we had used a standard calcium w/ multivitamin twice a month for most of Judy&amp;rsquo;s life, and we raised the babies in what I would call &amp;ldquo;standard&amp;rdquo; baby bins (not fully-planted, bioactive bins like we use today).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judy&#39;s First Clutch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/03/21/first-clutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/03/21/first-clutch/</guid>
      <description>Female Fucifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons) will rock back and forth with their mouth agape in a defensive posture when they are not ready to mate.&#xA;It is always good to introduce the female into the male&amp;rsquo;s enclosure to avoid injury to either animal because their body language is not for show. Males are often too persistent for their own good. In the beginning of March, Judy climbed willingly into Flash&amp;rsquo;s cage, but we had to try multiple times before she was confortable.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
