<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>past clutches on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>https://ipardalis.com/categories/past-clutches/</link>
    <description>Recent content in past clutches on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ipardalis.com/categories/past-clutches/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jack x Mavokely</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Jack, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Mavokely. Jack had some of the nicest yellows from Jude x Alla and Bobby&amp;rsquo;s boy Amarillo is one of my favorite ybbb of all time. These guys should be very special.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleu x Patch</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/09/12/bleu-patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/09/12/bleu-patch/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Patch, and our male from Jeremy Booker, Bleu, from Brightside Chameleons. Bleu is the only male with Stryfe in him and we are excited to see what that brings to the project.
 Bleu x Patch  Hatch dates 9/12/2020 - 9/27/2020 Hatch rate 29/32    F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Sunny</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Alla</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing is between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our most successful female, Alla, from RB Barto @Panther Creek Chameleons. Nugget is one of my favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe paired with an all-time great in JJ who comes from some of the most popular Ambilobe lines at Kammerflage Kreations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Alla</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</guid>
      <description>This has been our most successful pairing to-date. Alla is an amazing female Ambilobe that we purchased from RB Barto in 2017. She has been producing clutches between 25-34 eggs every 60 to 90 days ever since!
We decided to keep Blossom, Jack, and Afred from this pairing as well as numerous females.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Kako</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/05/jude-kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/05/jude-kako/</guid>
      <description>This pairing gave us Nugget, Patch, Sunny, Lilly, and Daisy.
Jude x Kako F2
 Hatch dates 6/5/2019 - 6/19/2019 Hatch rate 34/34    Daisy
      Img 1
      Img 11
      Img 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash x Judy</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/10/17/flash-judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/10/17/flash-judy/</guid>
      <description>This was our first clutch. Both parents, Flash and Judy, were sourced from Bruce Galbraith at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. Our hatch rate was ~50% and 4 of the babies did not make it to the 3 month mark. That was the baseline that we have tried to improve upon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
