<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>past clutches on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/categories/past-clutches/</link>
    <description>Recent content in past clutches on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/past-clutches/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Papafee x Lokana</title>
      <link>/blog/2022/01/11/papafee-lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022/01/11/papafee-lokana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Papafee, and our Ambilobe female from Chromatic Chameleons, Lokana. Lokana is from a great pairing between Kromatisk and Shirley. Kromatisk is one of my favorite Ambilobe breeders in the USA and Shirley is from one of my favorite ybbb combinations from Kammerflage Kreations. Papafee is the HB male from our Zanaka x Sunny clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the fourth generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papafee x Coco</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/12/04/papafee-coco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/12/04/papafee-coco/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Papafee, and our little Ambilobe female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Coco. Coco is from a great pairing between Hendrix and Foxey. Hendrix brings a new WC Ambilobe line into the project and Foxey is from one of my favorite ybbb combinations from Kammerflage Kreations. Papafee is the HB male from our Zanaka x Sunny clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the fourth generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manga x Imelda</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/12/03/manga-imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/12/03/manga-imelda/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Manga, and our female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Imelda. Imelda is a great mix of WC Gambit lines and Kammerflage Kreations yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe while Manga is the male with the most striking yellows from our Bleu x Patch clutch. We kept Jimanga from this group and he has his father&amp;rsquo;s wonderful profile! Just a gorgeous group of Ambilobe.
Manga x Imelda Hatch dates 12/03/2021 - 2/19/2022 Hatch rate 15/19 M1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Daisy</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/17/arti-daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/17/arti-daisy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Daisy, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Daisy is a great female from our Jude x Kako clutch. Some of my favorite yellows came from this pairing and Daisy didn&amp;rsquo;t disappoint ;)
Arti x Daisy Hatch dates 10/17/2021 - 10/26/2021 Hatch rate 4/26 1st
Img 0370</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Alla</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/15/arti-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/15/arti-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our most prolific female from Panther Creek Chameleons, Alla, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Alla is a wonderful female from JJ who was produced by Kammerflage Kreations. We only had a single clutch from these two because it was towards the end of Alla&amp;rsquo;s breeding career.
Arti x Alla Hatch dates 10/15/2021 - 10/19/2021 Hatch rate 3/20 Dehibe</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arti x CH Bohana</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/09/15/arti-bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/09/15/arti-bohana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our first captive hatched (CH) female, Bohana, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Bohana is a female Ambilobe hatched out by Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics from a wild caught imported female. Bohana&amp;rsquo;s wild genes didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to add much to our project when combined with Arti, so we did not keep any of these animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Tigravavy</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/28/arti-tigravavy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/28/arti-tigravavy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Tigravavy, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Tigravavy is a stunning female from our Jude x Alla clutch. We were very happy with these guys!
Arti x Tigravavy Hatch dates 6/28/2021 - 7/29/2021 Hatch rate 25/26 F1
F2
M1
M10
M2
M3
M4
M5
M6</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blossom x Mavokely</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/20/blossom-mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/20/blossom-mavokely/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Blossom, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Mavokely. Mavokely is from one of our favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe, Amarillo, and Blossom is the HB male from our Jude x Alla clutch. Great combination of colorful ybbb and clean yellows!
Blossom x Mavokely Hatch dates 6/20/2021 - 6/24/2021 Hatch rate 22/22 F1
F2
M2
M3
M4
Hatch dates 8/08/2021 - 8/22/2021 Hatch rate 23/26 F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Loko</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/03/nugget-loko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/03/nugget-loko/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our gorgeous Ambilobe female from Chromatic Chameleons, Loko. Loko is from a great pairing between Kromatisk and Wet Dream - a ybbb x ybbb Ambilobe combination. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination with our favorite third gen yellow male with an extremely high quality yellow female!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Amara</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/01/nugget-amara/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/01/nugget-amara/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our female from Brian Stewart, Amara. Amara proved out to carry a lot of her sire&amp;rsquo;s, Artemis&amp;rsquo;, traits like his dark blue bars and red highlighting. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination of colorful ybbb with both blue bars and clean yellows!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfred x Kanto</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/04/13/alfred-kanto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/04/13/alfred-kanto/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Alfred, and our female from Frank Payne, Kanto, from Living Art by Frank Payne. Kanto comes from some great OBBB/RBBB lines from Canvas Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Alfred is the male with the most red from our Jude x Alla clutch. We kept Ralph from this group and he is a wonderful RBBB!
Alfred x Kanto Hatch dates 4/13/2021 - 5/04/2021 Hatch rate 22/24 No pictures available</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x CH Bohana</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/04/11/nugget-bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/04/11/nugget-bohana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our captive-hatched Ambilobe female from Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics, Bohana. Bohana was hatched from a wild caught female&amp;rsquo;s clutch of eggs and she seems to have a complex set of colors without a dominant phenotype. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination of wild Ambilobe genetics and clean yellows!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Daisy</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/03/08/zanaka-daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/03/08/zanaka-daisy/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project.
Zanaka x Daisy F3-CG5
Hatch dates 3/8/2021 - 3/20/2021 Hatch rate 21/26 F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blossom x Maitso</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/01/27/blossom-maitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/01/27/blossom-maitso/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Blossom, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Maitso. Maitso is from one of our favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe, Amarillo, and Blossom is the HB male from our Jude x Alla clutch. Great combination of colorful ybbb and clean yellows! Kiborin is our keeper from this group.
Blossom x Maitso Hatch dates 1/27/2021 - 3/07/2021 Hatch rate 25/27 1st
10th</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack x Mavokely</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Jack, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Mavokely. Jack had some of the nicest yellows from Jude x Alla and Bobby&amp;rsquo;s boy Amarillo is one of my favorite ybbb of all time. These guys should be very special.
Jack x Mavokely Hatch dates 1/20/2021 - 3/17/2021 Hatch rate 3/21 M1
Hb
Hb1
Jackson1
Jackson4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Bubbles</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/10/15/zanaka-bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/10/15/zanaka-bubbles/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project.
Zanaka x Bubbles F3-CG13
Hatch dates 10/15/2020 - 10/17/2020 Hatch rate 37/39 F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleu x Patch</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/09/12/bleu-patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/09/12/bleu-patch/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Patch, and our male from Jeremy Booker, Bleu, from Brightside Chameleons. Bleu is the only male with Stryfe in him and we are excited to see what that brings to the project. Manga was our keeper from this group.
Bleu x Patch Hatch dates 9/12/2020 - 9/27/2020 Hatch rate 29/32 F1
F2
F3
F4
M1
M2
Manga7
Hatch dates 10/28/2020 - 11/17/2020 Hatch rate 33/41 F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Sunny</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project. Papafee is our keeper from this group.
Zanaka x Sunny F3
Hatch dates 7/17/2020 - 7/28/2020 Hatch rate 28/29 F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Alla</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing is between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our most successful female, Alla, from RB Barto @Panther Creek Chameleons. Nugget is one of my favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe paired with an all-time great in JJ who comes from some of the most popular Ambilobe lines at Kammerflage Kreations.
Nugget x Alla F4
Hatch dates 7/10/2020 - 7/31/2020 Hatch rate 15/20 Aw
Hb
Hb1
Jh
M1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Alla</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</guid>
      <description>This has been our most successful pairing to-date. Alla is an amazing female Ambilobe that we purchased from RB Barto in 2017. She has been producing clutches between 25-34 eggs every 60 to 90 days ever since!
We decided to keep Blossom, Jack, and Afred from this pairing as well as numerous females.
Jude x Alla Filial F3 Hatch dates 7/9/2019 - 7/20/2019 Hatch rate 30/31 Dsc02741
Img 2442</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Kako</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/06/05/jude-kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/06/05/jude-kako/</guid>
      <description>This pairing gave us Nugget, Patch, Sunny, Lilly, and Daisy.
Jude x Kako F2
Hatch dates 6/5/2019 - 6/19/2019 Hatch rate 34/34 Daisy
Img 1
Img 11
Img 2
Img 2535
Img 2584
Img 2587
Img 2612
Img 2619
Img 2631
Img 2678
Img 2718
Img 2780
Img 2813
Img 2828
Img 2857
Img 2917
Img 2919
Img 2954
Img 2977
Img 3224
Img 3632
Img 3642
Img 3873</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash x Judy</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/10/17/flash-judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/10/17/flash-judy/</guid>
      <description>This was our first clutch. Both parents, Flash and Judy, were sourced from Bruce Galbraith at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. Our hatch rate was ~50% and 4 of the babies did not make it to the 3 month mark. That was the baseline that we have tried to improve upon. For this clutch, we had used a standard calcium w/ multivitamin twice a month for most of Judy&amp;rsquo;s life, and we raised the babies in what I would call &amp;ldquo;standard&amp;rdquo; baby bins (not fully-planted, bioactive bins like we use today).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
