<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>daisy on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/daisy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in daisy on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/daisy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Daisy</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/17/arti-daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/17/arti-daisy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Daisy, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Daisy is a great female from our Jude x Kako clutch. Some of my favorite yellows came from this pairing and Daisy didn&amp;rsquo;t disappoint ;)
Arti x Daisy Hatch dates 10/17/2021 - 10/26/2021 Hatch rate 4/26 1st
Img 0370</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/17/ghost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/17/ghost/</guid>
      <description>Ghost is a 4th gen ybbb Ambilobe breeder here at iPardalis. He is from our Arti and Daisy pairing. His yellows are so light when he fires up that we decided to name him Ghost. They are just so clean and bright! There is also an H bar on his right side. We are very excited to have him carry the torch on this part of our tree.
Ghost</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Daisy</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/03/08/zanaka-daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/03/08/zanaka-daisy/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project.
Zanaka x Daisy F3-CG5
Hatch dates 3/8/2021 - 3/20/2021 Hatch rate 21/26 F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daisy</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/06/07/daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/06/07/daisy/</guid>
      <description>Daisy also has some really nice purples, hatched 6/5/19 from Jude x Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her 19 male siblings were bright yellow bodied blue bar Ambilobe, with the exception of one male who fired red bar. I hope she can function like a female version of her brother, Nugget, in our pairings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kako</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</guid>
      <description>Kako was one of the two females we paired with our second generation breeder - Jude. We purchased her from RB Barto, but she was produced by Bobby Ruddock. Her line is one of our favorite yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe lines in the USA. Vibrant yellows and clean blue bars.
Kako
Kako1
Filial Group F2 Sire Sparkles Dam Leo&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 4 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Kako (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.
Body shot
Dsc00380
Dsc00383
Jude
Jude2
Filial Group F2 Sire Flash Dam Judy 4 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Jude (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Bobby Ruddock</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/bobbyruddock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/bobbyruddock/</guid>
      <description> Sparkles F1
Sparkles1
Sparkles2
Sire Son of Loza and Flamming River&amp;rsquo;s daughter Dam Unknown WC Amarillo F2
Amarillo
Amarillo1
Sire Sparkles Dam Leo Sasha Sire Sinister </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Company</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/pantherco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/pantherco/</guid>
      <description>Panther Company Leo Leo
Leo1
Leo1
Leo2
Leo3
Leo4
Leo5
Leo6
Leo7</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy</title>
      <link>/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</guid>
      <description>Judy was our first generation breeder from Candy Cane (F1) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. She laid one good clutch for us but died during laying complications after 2 more infertile clutches.
Judy (1)
Judy (2)
Judy (3)
Judy (4)
Judy (6)
Judy 1 year
Filial Group F2 Sire Candy Cane Dam Jake&amp;rsquo;s daughter 3 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Judy (F2) Generation 1 1. Judy (F2). Judy was born on 2015-02-11 at Chameleon&#39;s Paradise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash</title>
      <link>/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</guid>
      <description>Flash was our first generation breeder from Cowboy (CH) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. He had a very gentle personality and only gave us one healthy clutch with Judy, from which we kept Jude. We were still learning when we got Flash and he passed after consuming a large number of wild bugs when pesticides had been applied to the lawn behind ours. The vet said that he had kidney failure like he&amp;rsquo;d been poisoned, but we have been continuing to improve our husbandry year-after-year in his honor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
