<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zava on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/zava/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zava on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/zava/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Zava x Nuhana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/25/zava-nuhana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/25/zava-nuhana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our F1 female from Nugget x CH Bohana, and our male from Kammerflage Kreations, Zava. Zava was a vibrant rainbow Ambilobe. His yellow sat on top of a bright red dermal layer, and his bars were deep royal blue. F1 Nuhana brings fresh genetics and a chance at Nugget&amp;rsquo;s neon yellow body with blue bars.&#xA;Hatch dates 7/18/22 - 8/25/2022 Hatch rate 17/25 F1&#xA;M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zava x Manjaya</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/21/zava-manjaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/21/zava-manjaya/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our F1 female from WC Arlo x Perregrin/Pyro&amp;rsquo;s daughter, and our male from Kammerflage Kreations, Zava. Zava was a vibrant rainbow Ambilobe. His yellow sat on top of a bright red dermal layer, and his bars were deep royal blue. F1 Manjaya brings fresh genetics and a chance at that Perregrin/Sparkles yellow.&#xA;Hatch dates 7/27/22 - 8/21/2022 Hatch rate 8/14 F1&#xA;F2&#xA;F3&#xA;M1&#xA;M2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mena</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/27/mena/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/27/mena/</guid>
      <description>Mena is our HB from Zava and F1 Manjaya. Zava had a significant amount of red and a few of Mena&amp;rsquo;s brothers got it, too. Manjaya seems to have taken after her WC sire, Arlo. A few of Mena&amp;rsquo;s brothers looked like mini Arlo&amp;rsquo;s. So less of the Perregrin/Pyro side of the lineage, more of the WC Arlo combined with Zava is what she brings to the table.&#xA;Mena</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>zava</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/03/21/zava/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/03/21/zava/</guid>
      <description>Zava is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage Kreations Green Giant x Promise Keeper pairing, produced by Ed Kammer. He brings some great deep blue bars and a yellow body with a significant amount of red highlighting. We were really hoping he&amp;rsquo;d have less red and more yellow, so we only did a few clutches with him.&#xA;Zava&#xA;Zava1&#xA;Zava2&#xA;Zava3&#xA;Zava4&#xA;Zava5&#xA;Zava6&#xA;Filial F3-CG13 Sire Itso-triombe (Green Giant) Dam Jiona (June) 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
