<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>updates on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/categories/updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in updates on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New iPardalis Genes</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/04/05/newline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/04/05/newline/</guid>
      <description>Zanaka (F2) Zanaka is F2 because his mother&amp;rsquo;s father was a wild-caught Ambilobe named Herb (Fanitso), owned by Kammerflage Kreations.
Bohana (CH) Bohana was hatched by Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics from eggs laid by an Ambilobe female imported in 2019.
Bohana&amp;rsquo;s brothers proved out and are some very nice yellow body blue bar Ambilobe, like this guy owned by Daniel Gordinho named Goldust:
I was thinking of pairing these two together, but Nugget has really impressed us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy&#39;s First Clutch</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/03/21/first-clutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/03/21/first-clutch/</guid>
      <description>Female Fucifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons) will rock back and forth with their mouth agape in a defensive posture when they are not ready to mate.
It is always good to introduce the female into the male&amp;rsquo;s enclosure to avoid injury to either animal because their body language is not for show. Males are often too persistent for their own good. In the beginning of March, Judy climbed willingly into Flash&amp;rsquo;s cage, but we had to try multiple times before she was confortable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
