<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>flamethrower on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/flamethrower/</link>
    <description>Recent content in flamethrower on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/flamethrower/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mainty</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/09/05/mainty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/09/05/mainty/</guid>
      <description>Mainty is one of the nicest RBBB females I could find for Ralph. Her sire, Bangheera, is a classic red body blue bar Ambilobe produced by Highlighter Chameleons and owned by Nature&amp;rsquo;s Van Gogh. After talking to Logan about Mainty&amp;rsquo;s brothers, it looks like many of them proved out to be similar to Grape Inferno or Bangheera, so although Moonclaw&amp;rsquo;s sire is Flamethrower, it seems she took after her dam sire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Charles Yamaguchi</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/yamaguchi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/yamaguchi/</guid>
      <description>Charles Yamaguchi Charles Yamaguchi isn&amp;rsquo;t a real person. Elizabeth Lawrence scammed people under this persona selling a bunch of Ambilobe x Nosy Be crosses to people. Her other aliases include: Cami Garden Hat, April Wilcox, Trevor Neufeld, and April Michelle. I would never add a female from this lineage, but I found a great looking male that&amp;rsquo;s a few gens removed from her scam. So the male has proven out, but I will definitely want to run a locale genetic test to confirm the locale of these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Highlighter Chameleons</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/highlighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/highlighter/</guid>
      <description> Highlighter Chameleons Mango Saphire Mangosaphire
Sire Karamba-ady (Cage Combat) Dam Telo heny&amp;rsquo;s daughter Flamethrower Flamethrower
Flamethrower1
Flamethrower2
Sire Tropicali Dam Sire [Arira/Thunder&amp;rsquo;s daughter] Copperhead&amp;rsquo;s daughter Sire Copperhead Dam Unknown Grape Inferno Grapeinferno
Grapeinferno1
Sire Manga-hay (Blue Heat) Dam Bolitika-zandry (Little Sister) Tropicali Tropicali
Tropicali1
Tropicali2
Sire Unknown Dam Unknown </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
