<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manjaka on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/manjaka/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manjaka on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/manjaka/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Noko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/29/manjaka-noko/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/29/manjaka-noko/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female from Nugget x Loko, and our male from Colorado Chameleons, F1 Manjaka. Manjaka was pretty unassuming as a juvenile, but he became one of our favorite YBBB Ambilobe breeders as an adult. He had an extra blue bar, and yellows were classic Ambilobe. Loko came to us from Chromatic Chameleons and Nugget is our favorite 3rd gen YBBB breeder.&#xA;Hatch dates 11/19/22 - 11/29/22 Hatch rate 24/24 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Tigerlilly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/07/manjaka-tigerlilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/07/manjaka-tigerlilly/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female from Nugget x Amara, and our male from Colorado Chameleons, F1 Manjaka. Manjaka was pretty unassuming as a juvenile, but he became one of our favorite YBBB Ambilobe breeders as an adult. He had an extra blue bar, and yellows were classic Ambilobe. Amara came to us from Brian Stewart and her lineage is more rainbow Ambilobe.&#xA;Hatch dates 11/03/22 - 11/07/2022 Hatch rate 23/23 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parasi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/20/parasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/20/parasi/</guid>
      <description>Parasi is a great Ambilobe female from our F1 sire from Colorado Chameleon named Manjaka and our female from Jack and Mavokely. Many of her brothers had great yellow bodies and blue bars - a few had mixed red/blue bars. We are very excited to see what she does with WC Tratra!&#xA;Parasi&#xA;Parasi1&#xA;Filial F2-CG14 Sire Manjaka Dam Parasy 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Parasi (F2-CG14) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Parasy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/26/manjaka-parasy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/26/manjaka-parasy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female from Jack x Mavokely, and our male from Colorado Chameleons, F1 Manjaka. Manjaka was pretty unassuming as a juvenile, but he became one of our favorite YBBB Ambilobe breeders as an adult. He had an extra blue bar, and yellows were classic Ambilobe. Mavokely came to us from Bobby Ruddock and she brings some of my favorite YBBB Ambilobe genetics - Amarillo.&#xA;Hatch dates 7/26/22 - 8/20/2022 Hatch rate 8/18 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Lokana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/05/manjaka-lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/05/manjaka-lokana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our F1 sire from Colorado Chameleons, Manjaka, and our female from Chromatic Chameleons, Lokana. Lokana is a mix of Chromatic and Kammerflage Kreations yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe while Manjaka is a wonderful YBBB from a recent import, WC Arlo. The outcomes have been extremely consiste YBBB thus far which are not directly related to our main line of Ambilobe. They are a great option for people looking for high quality pairings with our multi-generational lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranoka</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/05/ranoka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/05/ranoka/</guid>
      <description>Ranoka is a really interesting mix of F1 Manjaka and Kromatisk, Lokana&amp;rsquo;s sire. He has the radiant yellow that Manjaka has, but he also has the red embers at the edge of the yellow like Kromatisk - this almost looks orange at times and gives it an almost 3D look against a blue background. Really unique animal!&#xA;Ranoka&#xA;Ranoka1&#xA;Ranoka2&#xA;Ranoka3&#xA;Ranoka4&#xA;Ranoka5&#xA;Ranoka6&#xA;Ranoka7&#xA;Ranoka8&#xA;Filial F2-CG14 Sire Manjaka Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tsara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/01/tsara/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/01/tsara/</guid>
      <description>Tsara Tarehy means attractive in Malagasy. We named the two sisters from Manjaka x Lokana Tsara and Tarehy :). Check out that clutch to see how consistent their YBBB phenotypes were. It is a very good proxy for what these two sisters bring to the table: great yellows and bars that shift from Landy to Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s blues. Very good complement to our existing lines!&#xA;Tsara&#xA;Tsara1&#xA;Tsara2&#xA;Filial F2-CG14 Sire Manjaka Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarehy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/31/tarehy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/31/tarehy/</guid>
      <description>Tsara Tarehy means attractive in Malagasy. We named the two sisters from Manjaka x Lokana Tsara and Tarehy :). Check out that clutch to see how consistent their YBBB phenotypes were. It is a very good proxy for what these two sisters bring to the table: great yellows and bars that shift from Landy to Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s blues. Very good complement to our existing lines!&#xA;Tarehy&#xA;Tarehy1&#xA;Tarehy2&#xA;Filial F2-CG14 Sire Manjaka Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</guid>
      <description>Manjaka brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with him!&#xA;Manjaka&#xA;Manjaka1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Brian Collins</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/19/briancollins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/19/briancollins/</guid>
      <description> Higgins Higgins&#xA;Higgins1&#xA;Higgins2&#xA;Sire Pelellu Dam Sire Anguar </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
