<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nugget on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>https://ipardalis.com/tags/nugget/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nugget on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ipardalis.com/tags/nugget/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Alla</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing is between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our most successful female, Alla, from RB Barto @Panther Creek Chameleons. Nugget is one of my favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe paired with an all-time great in JJ who comes from some of the most popular Ambilobe lines at Kammerflage Kreations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</guid>
      <description>Nugget was an alpha male from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. He has many of the traits I love about Jude/Flash. He is a bold YBBB with great lineage. His yellows are more vibrant and his blue bars do not have any red pock marks like Jude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kako</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</guid>
      <description>Kako was one of the two females we paired with our second generation breeder - Jude. We purchased her from RB Barto, but she was produced by Bobby Ruddock. Her line is one of our favorite yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe lines in the USA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Bobby Ruddock</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/bobbyruddock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/bobbyruddock/</guid>
      <description>                          Sparkles F1
  Sparkles1
      Sparkles2
      Sire Son of Loza and Flamming River&amp;rsquo;s daughter Dam Unknown WC   Amarillo F2
  Amarillo
      Amarillo1
      Sire Sparkles Dam Leo   Sasha  Sire Sinister  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Company</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/pantherco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/pantherco/</guid>
      <description>Panther Company Leo   Leo
      Leo1
      Leo1
      Leo2
      Leo3
      Leo4
      Leo5</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</guid>
      <description>Judy was our first generation breeder from Candy Cane (F1) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. She laid one good clutch for us but died during laying complications after 2 more infertile clutches.
  Judy (1)
      Judy (2)
      Judy (3)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</guid>
      <description>Flash was our first generation breeder from Cowboy (CH) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. He had a very gentle personality and only gave us one healthy clutch with Judy, from which we kept Jude. We were still learning when we got Flash and he passed after consuming a large number of wild bugs when pesticides had been applied to the lawn behind ours.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
