<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nugget on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/nugget/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nugget on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/nugget/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Zandrin x Mara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/12/21/zandrin-mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/12/21/zandrin-mara/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female Mara from Chi-town Chameleons, and our 4th gen male, Zandrin. Zandrin was our favorite YBBB from Nugget and Mara brings the WC Legion line into our project via Nova. If we can get a HB that looks remotely similar to Zandrin x Nova, we will be super excited about this line :)&#xA;Hatch dates 12/04/22 - 12/21/2022 Hatch rate 32/40 F1&#xA;F10&#xA;F11</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Noko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/29/manjaka-noko/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/29/manjaka-noko/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female from Nugget x Loko, and our male from Colorado Chameleons, F1 Manjaka. Manjaka was pretty unassuming as a juvenile, but he became one of our favorite YBBB Ambilobe breeders as an adult. He had an extra blue bar, and yellows were classic Ambilobe. Loko came to us from Chromatic Chameleons and Nugget is our favorite 3rd gen YBBB breeder.&#xA;Hatch dates 11/19/22 - 11/29/22 Hatch rate 24/24 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Tigerlilly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/07/manjaka-tigerlilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/07/manjaka-tigerlilly/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female from Nugget x Amara, and our male from Colorado Chameleons, F1 Manjaka. Manjaka was pretty unassuming as a juvenile, but he became one of our favorite YBBB Ambilobe breeders as an adult. He had an extra blue bar, and yellows were classic Ambilobe. Amara came to us from Brian Stewart and her lineage is more rainbow Ambilobe.&#xA;Hatch dates 11/03/22 - 11/07/2022 Hatch rate 23/23 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zava x Nuhana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/25/zava-nuhana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/25/zava-nuhana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our F1 female from Nugget x CH Bohana, and our male from Kammerflage Kreations, Zava. Zava was a vibrant rainbow Ambilobe. His yellow sat on top of a bright red dermal layer, and his bars were deep royal blue. F1 Nuhana brings fresh genetics and a chance at Nugget&amp;rsquo;s neon yellow body with blue bars.&#xA;Hatch dates 7/18/22 - 8/25/2022 Hatch rate 17/25 F1&#xA;M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zandrin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/04/zandrin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/04/zandrin/</guid>
      <description>Zandrin is our 4th gen HB from Nugget x Loko. He has amazing yellows with blue bars and some vibrant red highlights on his turrets and spine. He is a phenomenal Ambilobe Panther Chameleon.&#xA;Zandrin&#xA;Zandrin1&#xA;Zandrin2&#xA;Zandrin3&#xA;Zandrin4&#xA;Zandrin5&#xA;Zandrin6&#xA;Zandrin7&#xA;Zandrin8&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Nugget Dam Loko 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Zandrin (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Zandrin (F4-CG14). Zandrin was born on 2021-06-04 at iPardalis. He is the son of Nugget (F3-CG4) and Loko (F5-CG13).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/03/noko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/03/noko/</guid>
      <description>Noko is our HB female from Nugget and Loko. Her brother is Zandrin. She should throw some intense yellow and blue with some interesting red highlighting. Her personality is very calm and photogenic. It was incredibly easy to get some nice profile pictures of her!&#xA;Noko&#xA;Noko1&#xA;Noko2&#xA;Noko3&#xA;Noko4&#xA;Noko5&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Nugget Dam Loko 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Noko (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Noko (F4-CG14).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Loko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/03/nugget-loko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/03/nugget-loko/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our gorgeous Ambilobe female from Chromatic Chameleons, Loko. Loko is from a great pairing between Kromatisk and Wet Dream - a ybbb x ybbb Ambilobe combination. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination with our favorite third gen yellow male with an extremely high quality yellow female!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Amara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/nugget-amara/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/nugget-amara/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our female from Brian Stewart, Amara. Amara proved out to carry a lot of her sire&amp;rsquo;s, Artemis&amp;rsquo;, traits like his dark blue bars and red highlighting. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination of colorful ybbb with both blue bars and clean yellows!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tigerlilly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/tigerlilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/tigerlilly/</guid>
      <description>Tiger Lilly is one of the most stunning females I have seen in person. She has an amazing bar/body contrast, organge highlights in her face and turrets and an orang glow on her arms and tail. We are very lucky to get to work with her. Hopefully, those traits are a sign that she is as cool as her sire, Nugget.&#xA;Tigerlilly&#xA;Tigerlilly1&#xA;Tigerlilly2&#xA;Tigerlilly3&#xA;Tigerlilly4&#xA;Tigerlilly5&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Nugget Dam Amara 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tony</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/tony/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/tony/</guid>
      <description>Tony one of our 4th generation YBBB Ambilobe. He has some great traits from his dam, Amara, like his deep blue bars and red highlights, but he also has some vibrant yellows from his sire, Nugget. His profile is one of my favorites with striking turret and gular lines. We are very lucky to have him in our breeding group!&#xA;Tony&#xA;Tony1&#xA;Tony2&#xA;Tony3&#xA;Tony4&#xA;Tony5&#xA;Tony6&#xA;Tony7&#xA;Tony8</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x CH Bohana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/11/nugget-bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/11/nugget-bohana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our captive-hatched Ambilobe female from Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics, Bohana. Bohana was hatched from a wild caught female&amp;rsquo;s clutch of eggs and she seems to have a complex set of colors without a dominant phenotype. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination of wild Ambilobe genetics and clean yellows!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nuhana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/14/nuhana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/14/nuhana/</guid>
      <description>Nuhana is an F1 female we produced with our 3rd gen ybbb, Nugget and our captive-hatched (CH) female, Bohana. Her brothers have been pretty diverse in their color scheme. Fingers crossed she takes after her father!&#xA;Nuhana&#xA;Nuhana1&#xA;Nuhana2&#xA;Filial F1-CG5 Sire Nugget Dam Bohana 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Nuhana (F1-CG5) Generation 1 1. Nuhana (F1-CG5). Nuhana was born on 2021-01-14 at iPardalis. She is the daughter of Nugget (F3-CG4) and Bohana (CH).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Alla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing is between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our most successful female, Alla, from RB Barto @Panther Creek Chameleons. Nugget is one of my favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe paired with an all-time great in JJ who comes from some of the most popular Ambilobe lines at Kammerflage Kreations.&#xA;Nugget x Alla F4&#xA;Hatch dates 7/10/2020 - 7/31/2020 Hatch rate 15/20 Aw&#xA;Hb&#xA;Hb1&#xA;Jh&#xA;M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</guid>
      <description>Nugget was an alpha male from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. He has many of the traits I love about Jude/Flash. He is a bold YBBB with great lineage. His yellows are more vibrant and his blue bars do not have any red pock marks like Jude. He is an amazingly clean yellow body blue bar Ambilobe.&#xA;Nugget&#xA;Nugget1&#xA;Nugget2&#xA;Nugget3&#xA;Nugget4&#xA;Nugget5&#xA;Filial F3-CG4 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kako</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</guid>
      <description>Kako was one of the two females we paired with our second generation breeder - Jude. We purchased her from RB Barto, but she was produced by Bobby Ruddock. Her line is one of our favorite yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe lines in the USA. Vibrant yellows and clean blue bars.&#xA;Kako&#xA;Kako1&#xA;Filial Group F2 Sire Sparkles Dam Leo&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 4 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Kako (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.&#xA;Body shot&#xA;Dsc00380&#xA;Dsc00383&#xA;Jude&#xA;Jude2&#xA;Filial Group F2 Sire Flash Dam Judy 4 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Jude (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Bobby Ruddock</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/bobbyruddock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/bobbyruddock/</guid>
      <description> Sparkles F1&#xA;Sparkles1&#xA;Sparkles2&#xA;Sire Son of Loza and Flamming River&amp;rsquo;s daughter Dam Unknown WC Amarillo F2&#xA;Amarillo&#xA;Amarillo1&#xA;Sire Sparkles Dam Leo Sasha Sire Sinister </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Company</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/pantherco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/pantherco/</guid>
      <description>Panther Company Leo Leo&#xA;Leo1&#xA;Leo1&#xA;Leo2&#xA;Leo3&#xA;Leo4&#xA;Leo5&#xA;Leo6&#xA;Leo7</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</guid>
      <description>Judy was our first generation breeder from Candy Cane (F1) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. She laid one good clutch for us but died during laying complications after 2 more infertile clutches.&#xA;Judy (1)&#xA;Judy (2)&#xA;Judy (3)&#xA;Judy (4)&#xA;Judy (6)&#xA;Judy 1 year&#xA;Filial Group F2 Sire Candy Cane Dam Jake&amp;rsquo;s daughter 3 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Judy (F2) Generation 1 1. Judy (F2). Judy was born on 2015-02-11 at Chameleon&#39;s Paradise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</guid>
      <description>Flash was our first generation breeder from Cowboy (CH) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. He had a very gentle personality and only gave us one healthy clutch with Judy, from which we kept Jude. We were still learning when we got Flash and he passed after consuming a large number of wild bugs when pesticides had been applied to the lawn behind ours. The vet said that he had kidney failure like he&amp;rsquo;d been poisoned, but we have been continuing to improve our husbandry year-after-year in his honor.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
