<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>iPardalis</title>
    <link>http://ipardalis.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on iPardalis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Jonathan Mark Hill; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://ipardalis.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy&#39;s First Clutch</title>
      <link>http://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/03/21/first-clutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/03/21/first-clutch/</guid>
      <description>Female Fucifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons) will rock back and forth with their mouth agape in a defensive posture when they are not ready to mate.
             
It is always good to introduce the female into the male&amp;rsquo;s enclosure to avoid injury to either animal because their body language is not for show and males are often too persistent for their own good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://ipardalis.com/babies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ipardalis.com/babies/</guid>
      <description>HI!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Active Breeders</title>
      <link>http://ipardalis.com/breeders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ipardalis.com/breeders/</guid>
      <description>Flash    1 year stick shot
      1 year
      2 years green
      2 years yellow
      4 months
      Eating</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>http://ipardalis.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ipardalis.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>We raise Fucifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons) individually, under highly controlled conditions to ensure their health and longevity. They are one of the most sought after species of chameleons because of their amazing colors, size and relatively low maintenance requirements. Different regions of Madagascar have distinct color morphs, the most popular of which are Ambilobe (blue/red bar), Nosy Be, Nosy Faly, Sambava and Ambanja. Our breeding pair is from the Ambilobe region of Madagascar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orders</title>
      <link>http://ipardalis.com/orders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ipardalis.com/orders/</guid>
      <description>We have done our research. Please let us know if you have any questions about raising healthy Chameleons and setting up their homes. If you have a question, we are happy to share our knowledge of Chameleon health, husbandry and nutrition.
We require pictures of your enclosure pre-shipment, and there is a $50 discount for on-site pickups.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>