<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>https://ipardalis.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ipardalis.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UVI Impact on Growth of Furcifer pardalis Neonates</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/08/04/2021-08-04-uvi-impact-on-growth-of-furcifer-pardalis-neonates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/08/04/2021-08-04-uvi-impact-on-growth-of-furcifer-pardalis-neonates/</guid>
      <description>We raised two clutches of Furcifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons) under controlled conditions to answer a simple question:
 How does the growth rate of babies raised under UVI 3 and UVI 6 compare?
 Michael Nash performed a similar experiment which he details in this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parasites and Ethics: Origin Story</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/07/18/parasites_origin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/07/18/parasites_origin/</guid>
      <description>Rye, for good luck.
We received 5 females from reputable CB sources that had issues during/after quarantine since 2017. The first 2 were in 2017. They never had great appetites and seemed to have respiratory issues. We brought them to the vet and kept them isolated for 60 days; however, the vet did not see anything wrong with them, and after they seemed to be healthy enough, we tried to breed them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parasites and Ethics: Intro</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/07/12/parasites_and_ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/07/12/parasites_and_ethics/</guid>
      <description>tldr;   Every animal you acquire, whether it be captive bred (CB) or wild caught (WC), should receive multiple fecal exams. A positive fecal should be managed in consultation with a qualified vet who has experience working with chameleons. Many different species of parasites do not shed at a constant rate, so a negative fecal is not a gaurantee that the animal is clean.    We found Coccidia in 2 out of 25 exams that we performed in June-July 2021, and plan to run fecals on every animal in our possession and share the results/methods here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack x Mavokely</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Jack, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Mavokely. Jack had some of the nicest yellows from Jude x Alla and Bobby&amp;rsquo;s boy Amarillo is one of my favorite ybbb of all time. These guys should be very special.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coco</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/04/coco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/04/coco/</guid>
      <description>Coco brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&#39; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She has phenomenal coloring for a female and has been able to lay and bounce back easily thus far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>imelda</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</guid>
      <description>Imelda brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&#39; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She layed successfully, but we have been monitoring a minor gular edema on her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lokana</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</guid>
      <description>Lokana is the half-sister of Loko. They each have a 50% chance of bringing Kromatisk&amp;rsquo;s amazing ybbb into our project, but Lokana also has Landy x Hamy from her dam, Shirley&amp;rsquo;s side. Really can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with the two possibilities here. We are very excited to see how she proves out over the years :).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</guid>
      <description>Manjaka brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manga</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</guid>
      <description>Manga had some of the nicest yellows from all of Bleu and Patch&amp;rsquo;s sons. He has a striking facial pattern and is a classic Ambilobe panther chameleon. We&amp;rsquo;re very lucky to have him in our 4th generation breeding program.
  Manga
      Manga1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleu x Patch</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/09/12/bleu-patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/09/12/bleu-patch/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Patch, and our male from Jeremy Booker, Bleu, from Brightside Chameleons. Bleu is the only male with Stryfe in him and we are excited to see what that brings to the project.
 Bleu x Patch  Hatch dates 9/12/2020 - 9/27/2020 Hatch rate 29/32    F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papafee</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</guid>
      <description>Papafee is a monster yellow-bodied Ambilobe. He was our sole holdback from Zanaka and Sunny to carry on in our 4th generation of Ambilobe panther chameleons. His yellows are extremely vibrant and were evident at a young age (2 months). He almost has a neon quality to him and he is about 24&amp;quot; head to tail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Sunny</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Alla</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing is between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our most successful female, Alla, from RB Barto @Panther Creek Chameleons. Nugget is one of my favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe paired with an all-time great in JJ who comes from some of the most popular Ambilobe lines at Kammerflage Kreations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Husbandry: Furcifer pardalis (Panther Chameleon)</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/05/husbandry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/05/husbandry/</guid>
      <description>Enclosure I tend to use indoor 24&amp;quot;x24&amp;quot;x48&amp;quot; screen enclosures for males, and 18&amp;quot;x18&amp;quot;x36&amp;quot; screen enclosures for females. I add horizontal and vertical boards to the frame which can support 3 levels of horizontal perching branches as well as hold up plants. In the base of the enclosure, I put 12&amp;quot; of bioactive space with drainage, soil barrier, abg mix, spag moss and leaf litter. For microfauna, I use springtails and isopods some red wrigglers and lesser mealworms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Housing: Furcifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons)</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/05/housing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/05/housing/</guid>
      <description>We get a lot of questions about our housing strategy, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d provide an organized response. Here is our strategy for hatchling, baby, juvenile, adult male and adult female Furcifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons).
   Term Age (months)     Hatchling 0 - 1   Baby 1 - 4   Juvenile 4 - 8   Adult 8+    Hatchlings We find that it is advantageous to house hatchlings in bio-active tubs because their food items are so small - and would escape screen enclosures - and some hatchlings like to tuck under the leaves near the soil (ABG mix) while digesting their remaining yolk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loko</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/18/loko/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/18/loko/</guid>
      <description>Loko is a premium CB Ambilobe from some of the best lines in the USA. Her sire, Kromatisk from Chromatic Chameleons, is one of my favorite active breeders of the locale. My hope is that we can get some little guys that glow yellow from her and Nugget!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bing (冰)</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/14/bing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/14/bing/</guid>
      <description>Great little girl we got from Frank Payne. I am a huge fan of her shoulder patches and her night sky pattern on the dark body sections. Her older sister, Violet, was our first female; however, we have not gotten any clutches from her yet. Bing is a sweetheart, and we hope to hatch our first clutches from her in 2021!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feng (风)</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/07/feng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/07/feng/</guid>
      <description>Another little girl we got from Frank Payne. She&amp;rsquo;s very healthy and vibrant with an nice dark background on her body.
  Feng
      Feng1
      Feng10
      Feng11</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arti</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</guid>
      <description>Arti is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. He brings some great deep blue bars and a yellow body. We are very excited to see what he produces in concert with our existing lines!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New iPardalis Genes</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/05/newline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/05/newline/</guid>
      <description>Zanaka (F2) Zanaka is F2 because his mother&amp;rsquo;s father was a wild-caught Ambilobe named Herb (Fanitso), owned by Kammerflage Kreations.
Bohana (CH)  Bohana was hatched by Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics from eggs laid by an Ambilobe female imported in 2019.
Bohana&amp;rsquo;s brothers proved out and are some very nice yellow body blue bar Ambilobe, like this guy owned by Daniel Gordinho named Goldust:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amara</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/04/amara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/04/amara/</guid>
      <description>Amara is Arti&amp;rsquo;s sister from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. It will be interesting to compare her offspring with Arti&amp;rsquo;s to figure out which traits she is carrying from their shared lineage. I have always been curious about the females role in breeding and I think it is the key to producing some extraordinary animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bohana (CH)</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/03/29/bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/03/29/bohana/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful captive hatched (CH) female we picked up from Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics. Her brothers have ranged from true solid red body blue bar (RBBB) to yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe, so it will be extremely interesting to see where she lands. Fingers crossed she is carrying the YBBB genes we specialize in! If not, we will pair her to Alfred next to create some fresh combinations of vibrant, multi-colored Ambilobe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanto</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/02/15/kanto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/02/15/kanto/</guid>
      <description>Kanto is a beautiful female we picked up from Living Art by Frank Payne this year because her sire, Brightflame, is a great match for Alfred. All we know is that Brightflame came from a Canvas pairing and that some of the last pairings done were Bolt x Marley and Marley x Outline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huo (火)</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/01/01/huo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/01/01/huo/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful female that we picked up from Kevin Stanford. She has a really nice pitch-black body with a fire tip on the top of her yellow streaks. Stunning specimen of this species! We were able to get a few healthy clutches from her and hope to produce our first clutch from them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maitso</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/11/13/maitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/11/13/maitso/</guid>
      <description>Maitso&amp;rsquo;s sire, Amarillo, is the top yellow boby blue bar Ambilobe in the USA. He is a vibrant yellow from snout to vent without any red to mess with what he has going on. The only way I could concieve of a way to improve upon him is to get some thicker blue bars on him and get rid of the red on his turrets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mavokely</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/11/12/mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/11/12/mavokely/</guid>
      <description>Mavokely&amp;rsquo;s sire, Amarillo, is the top yellow boby blue bar Ambilobe in the USA. He is a vibrant yellow from snout to vent without any red to mess with what he has going on. The only way I could concieve of a way to improve upon him is to get some thicker blue bars on him and get rid of the red on his turrets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfred</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</guid>
      <description>Alfred is an extreme outlier from the Jude x Alla pairing. We were lucky to keep him because he carries some vibrant, almost dark neon colors. His resting colors are some of the nicest I have ever seen in person and I am very excited to work with him moving forward!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</guid>
      <description>Jack is a beautiful Ambilobe from our Jude x Alla pairing. When he was young, his yellows were dominant and covered his entire body. However, as he aged, oranges started to creep into his body from his gular and his tail turned a vibrant red. He is a beautiful animal, but that is not the look we are breeding for long-term, aside from his clean blue bars and yellow body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/08/21/zanaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/08/21/zanaka/</guid>
      <description>Zanaka is a giant F2 Ambilobe from Kammerflage Kreations. His personality was gentle to the extreme and he was hard to get fired up. It was almost as if other males didn&amp;rsquo;t exist, but when he saw a female, he would light up and start bobbing like a mad man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubbles</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</guid>
      <description>Bubbles is a massive female. At the one year mark, she already weighs 90 grams when receptive. She came from our Jude x Alla pairing and is one of the few females we decided to keep. She&amp;rsquo;s like a giant version of Alla. Healthy, hungry and bold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleu</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/15/bleu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/15/bleu/</guid>
      <description>Bleu is a male we picked up from the Stryfe line. He was raised by Jeremy Booker at Brightside Chameleons, and he was a bit of a challenge to work with. We released him in early 2020 and only produced a few clutches with him. We hope to select some nice males from his offspring to bring that line into our project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Button</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/14/button/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/14/button/</guid>
      <description>Button was a female with nice high contrast barring from Jude x Alla. We bred her a few times before letting her go to make space for fresh genetics, but she was a phenomenal breeder for us! It will be interesting to see how much the high contrast carries into her offspring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blossom</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</guid>
      <description>We got lucky holding back Blossom from Jude x Alla. He looks like a mini-JJ, Alla&amp;rsquo;s sire, and is a key member of our 3rd generation breeding group. His personality is very similar to Alla&amp;rsquo;s in that he is very bold and rarely defensive. His yellows are bright and his colors are very vibrant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Alla</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</guid>
      <description>This has been our most successful pairing to-date. Alla is an amazing female Ambilobe that we purchased from RB Barto in 2017. She has been producing clutches between 25-34 eggs every 60 to 90 days ever since!
We decided to keep Blossom, Jack, and Afred from this pairing as well as numerous females.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio Bin Experiment</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/30/bio-bin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/30/bio-bin/</guid>
      <description>Given that wild baby Panther Chameleons are often found in low brush or tall grass, we would like to simulate that as much as possible. So in 2019, we are experimenting with raising our babies in bio bins for the first month. We have multiple soil layers (drainage, abg &amp;amp; leaf) and 3 - 4 species of insects in every bin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunny</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/10/sunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/10/sunny/</guid>
      <description>Sunny was my second favorite female from the Jude x Kako clutch, hatched 6/5/19. She reminds me a lot of her mother, Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. With any luck we will be able to grap a killer yellow body blue bar male from her and Zanaka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</guid>
      <description>Nugget was an alpha male from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. He has many of the traits I love about Jude/Flash. He is a bold YBBB with great lineage. His yellows are more vibrant and his blue bars do not have any red pock marks like Jude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/08/patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/08/patch/</guid>
      <description>Patch was my favorite female from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her line is an extremely strong yellow body blue bar Ambilobe group, so I have high hopes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daisy</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/07/daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/07/daisy/</guid>
      <description>Daisy also has some really nice purples, hatched 6/5/19 from Jude x Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her 19 male siblings were bright yellow bodied blue bar Ambilobe, with the exception of one male who fired red bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lilly</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/06/lilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/06/lilly/</guid>
      <description>Lilly has some really nice purples, hatched 6/5/19 from Jude x Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her daughters will hopefully be equally beautiful, but we have a theory that her coloration indicates her sons will be killer yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Kako</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/05/jude-kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/05/jude-kako/</guid>
      <description>This pairing gave us Nugget, Patch, Sunny, Lilly, and Daisy.
Jude x Kako F2
 Hatch dates 6/5/2019 - 6/19/2019 Hatch rate 34/34    Daisy
      Img 1
      Img 11
      Img 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Di (地)</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2018/11/04/di/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2018/11/04/di/</guid>
      <description>                         Our first adult male from Frank Payne
  Di
      Sire M3 Dam F5   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alla</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</guid>
      <description>Alla is our most successful female breeder to date. She has a gregarious personality and brings some of the nicest YBBB Kammerflage Kreations lineage into our project via her sire, JJ. We were very lucky to pick her up from Panther Creek Chameleons back in 2017 before JJ was sold to Chromatic Chameleons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kako</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</guid>
      <description>Kako was one of the two females we paired with our second generation breeder - Jude. We purchased her from RB Barto, but she was produced by Bobby Ruddock. Her line is one of our favorite yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe lines in the USA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash x Judy</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/10/17/flash-judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/10/17/flash-judy/</guid>
      <description>This was our first clutch. Both parents, Flash and Judy, were sourced from Bruce Galbraith at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. Our hatch rate was ~50% and 4 of the babies did not make it to the 3 month mark. That was the baseline that we have tried to improve upon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy&#39;s First Clutch</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/03/21/first-clutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/03/21/first-clutch/</guid>
      <description>Female Fucifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons) will rock back and forth with their mouth agape in a defensive posture when they are not ready to mate.
             It is always good to introduce the female into the male&amp;rsquo;s enclosure to avoid injury to either animal because their body language is not for show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Colorado Chameleon</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/22/coloradochams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/22/coloradochams/</guid>
      <description>Colorado Chameleon  Arlo (WC)   Arlo
      Arlo1
      Arlo2
      Artemis   Artemis
      Artemis1
      Artemis2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kevin Stanford Reptiles</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/22/kevinstanford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/22/kevinstanford/</guid>
      <description>Kevin Stanford Reptiles Kevin has some really interesting oranges on a lot of his female Furcifer minor. The lineage on
Huo&amp;rsquo;s Sire   Img 5681
      Img 5683
      Huo&amp;rsquo;s Dam   Img 5679</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Living Art by Frank Payne</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/22/livingart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/22/livingart/</guid>
      <description>                         Living Art by Frank Payne  Brightflame Unknown
  Brightflame
      Brightflame1
      Sire Canvas Sire (possibly Bolt/Marley) Dam Canvas Dam (possibly Marley or Outline&amp;rsquo;s daughter)   Minors  Sires M1, M3, M6, M20 Dams F3, F5, F8, F20  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Modern Day Dragons</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/22/moderndaydragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/22/moderndaydragons/</guid>
      <description>                         Modern Day Dragons  Miss Piggy  Sire Higgins Dam Sire Candy Cane  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Bobby Ruddock</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/bobbyruddock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/bobbyruddock/</guid>
      <description>                          Sparkles F1
  Sparkles1
      Sparkles2
      Sire Son of Loza and Flamming River&amp;rsquo;s daughter Dam Unknown WC   Amarillo F2
  Amarillo
      Amarillo1
      Sire Sparkles Dam Leo   Sasha  Sire Sinister  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Brightside Chameleons</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/brightside/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/brightside/</guid>
      <description>Brightside Chameleons  Stryfe   Stryfe
      Stryfe1
      Stryfe2
      Sire Dio Dam Stryfe&amp;rsquo;s Dam   Emma Frost  Sire Felipe Sanchez Dam Sire Macho   Perregrin/Pyro   Pyro</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Canvas Chameleons</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/canvas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/canvas/</guid>
      <description>Canvas Chameleons  Marley   Marley
      Marley1
      Marley2
      Bolt WC
  Bolt
      Outline   Outline
      Outline1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Chameleon&#39;s Paradise</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/chameleonparadise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/chameleonparadise/</guid>
      <description>Chameleon Paradise  Cowboy WC
  Cowboy
      Cowboy2
      Cowboy3
      Candy Cane F1
  Candy cane
      Candy cane1
      Candy cane2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Chromatic Chameleons</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/chromatic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/chromatic/</guid>
      <description>Chromatic Chameleons  Felipe Sanchez   Felipe
      Felipe1
      Felipe2
      Felipe3
      Sire Bolt Dam Cowboy&amp;rsquo;s daughter   Kromatisk   Kromatisk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Joshua Illencik</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/joshuaillencik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/joshuaillencik/</guid>
      <description>Joshua Illencik  Dio  Sire Little Foot    Dio
      Dio1
      Stryfe&amp;rsquo;s Dam  Sire Zeratul    Zeratul
      Zeratul1
      Zeratul2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kammerflage Kreations</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</guid>
      <description>Kammerflage Kreations  Manome-toky (Promise Keeper)  Sire Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) Dam Vony-reny    Promise keeper
      Promise keeper1
      Promise keeper2
      Promise keeper3
      Promise keeper4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Company</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/pantherco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/pantherco/</guid>
      <description>Panther Company Leo   Leo
      Leo1
      Leo1
      Leo2
      Leo3
      Leo4
      Leo5</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Creek Chameleons</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</guid>
      <description>Panther Creek  JJ   Jj
      Jj1
      Jj2
      Jj3
      Jj4
      Jj5
      Jj6
      Sire Mavo-ra (Yellow Blood) Dam Sire Kely-tongotra (Little Foot)   Wet Dream   Wetdream</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Shane Conlin</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/shaneconlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/shaneconlin/</guid>
      <description>                         Shane Conlin Macho   Macho
      Macho1
      Macho2
      Sire Candy Cane Dam Sire Cowboy   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Ramblin&#39; Exotics</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/20/ramblin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/20/ramblin/</guid>
      <description>Ramblin&#39; Exotics  Hendrix   Hendrix
      Hendrix1
      Hendrix2
      Sire Dante Dam Sunkist   Foxey   Foxey
      Foxey1
      Foxey2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Tropical Chameleons</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/20/tropical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/20/tropical/</guid>
      <description>                         Tropical Chameleons  Dante   Dante
      Sire Gambit Dam Polaris   Sunkist  Sire Bolt Dam Test  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Brian Collins</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/19/briancollins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/19/briancollins/</guid>
      <description>                          Higgins   Higgins
      Higgins1
      Higgins2
      Sire Pelellu Dam Sire Anguar  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Mythical Exotics</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/19/mythicalexotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/19/mythicalexotics/</guid>
      <description>                         Mythical Exotics  Zephyros   Zephyros
     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</guid>
      <description>Judy was our first generation breeder from Candy Cane (F1) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. She laid one good clutch for us but died during laying complications after 2 more infertile clutches.
  Judy (1)
      Judy (2)
      Judy (3)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</guid>
      <description>Flash was our first generation breeder from Cowboy (CH) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. He had a very gentle personality and only gave us one healthy clutch with Judy, from which we kept Jude. We were still learning when we got Flash and he passed after consuming a large number of wild bugs when pesticides had been applied to the lawn behind ours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Clutches</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/babies/available/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/babies/available/</guid>
      <description>All of our juveniles will be a minimum of 3 months of age when they ship. However, you can place a $75 hold on any individual before that date. Holds are 100% refundable for any reason and will be applied to your balance when you&amp;rsquo;re ready to ship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>We raise Fucifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons) individually, under highly controlled conditions to ensure their health and longevity. They are one of the most sought after species of chameleons because of their amazing colors, size and relatively low maintenance requirements. Different regions of Madagascar have distinct color morphs, the most popular of which are Ambilobe (blue/red bar), Nosy Be, Nosy Faly, Sambava and Ambanja. Our breeding group is from the Ambilobe region of Madagascar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage of iPardalis</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/ambilobe/lineage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/ambilobe/lineage/</guid>
      <description>Panther Creek  JJ  Sire Mavo-ra (Yellow Blood) Dam Sire Little Foot    Jj
      Jj1
      Jj2
      Jj3
      Jj4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/tos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/tos/</guid>
      <description>By purchasing from iPardalis, you are agreeing to our terms of service.
Shipping Info We require pictures of your enclosure pre-shipment
We ship Monday, Tuesday or Wednesday via FedEx Priority Overnight for next day arrival. iPardalis has live arrival gaurantees on all shipments.
FedEx requires a phone # for shipping live animals in case they need to reach out to the recipient directly. We will also need to look up the closest shipping center to your zip code and confirm prior to shipping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Clutches</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/babies/upcoming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/babies/upcoming/</guid>
      <description>Reserve first, pick first We run a $75 reservation program for all of our upcoming clutches. Reservations are 100% refundable for any reason and will be applied to your balance when you&amp;rsquo;re ready to ship. When the first group of babies reaches the 3 month mark, we run down the reservation list before offering any to the public.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
