<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>husbandry on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>https://ipardalis.com/categories/husbandry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in husbandry on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ipardalis.com/categories/husbandry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UVI Impact on Growth of Furcifer pardalis Neonates</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/08/04/2021-08-04-uvi-impact-on-growth-of-furcifer-pardalis-neonates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/08/04/2021-08-04-uvi-impact-on-growth-of-furcifer-pardalis-neonates/</guid>
      <description>We raised two clutches of Furcifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons) under controlled conditions to answer a simple question:
 How does the growth rate of babies raised under UVI 3 and UVI 6 compare?
 Michael Nash performed a similar experiment which he details in this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parasites and Ethics: Origin Story</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/07/18/parasites_origin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/07/18/parasites_origin/</guid>
      <description>Rye, for good luck.
We received 5 females from reputable CB sources that had issues during/after quarantine since 2017. The first 2 were in 2017. They never had great appetites and seemed to have respiratory issues. We brought them to the vet and kept them isolated for 60 days; however, the vet did not see anything wrong with them, and after they seemed to be healthy enough, we tried to breed them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parasites and Ethics: Intro</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/07/12/parasites_and_ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/07/12/parasites_and_ethics/</guid>
      <description>tldr;   Every animal you acquire, whether it be captive bred (CB) or wild caught (WC), should receive multiple fecal exams. A positive fecal should be managed in consultation with a qualified vet who has experience working with chameleons. Many different species of parasites do not shed at a constant rate, so a negative fecal is not a gaurantee that the animal is clean.    We found Coccidia in 2 out of 25 exams that we performed in June-July 2021, and plan to run fecals on every animal in our possession and share the results/methods here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Husbandry: Furcifer pardalis (Panther Chameleon)</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/05/husbandry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/05/husbandry/</guid>
      <description>Enclosure I tend to use indoor 24&amp;quot;x24&amp;quot;x48&amp;quot; screen enclosures for males, and 18&amp;quot;x18&amp;quot;x36&amp;quot; screen enclosures for females. I add horizontal and vertical boards to the frame which can support 3 levels of horizontal perching branches as well as hold up plants. In the base of the enclosure, I put 12&amp;quot; of bioactive space with drainage, soil barrier, abg mix, spag moss and leaf litter. For microfauna, I use springtails and isopods some red wrigglers and lesser mealworms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Housing: Furcifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons)</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/05/housing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/05/housing/</guid>
      <description>We get a lot of questions about our housing strategy, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d provide an organized response. Here is our strategy for hatchling, baby, juvenile, adult male and adult female Furcifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons).
   Term Age (months)     Hatchling 0 - 1   Baby 1 - 4   Juvenile 4 - 8   Adult 8+    Hatchlings We find that it is advantageous to house hatchlings in bio-active tubs because their food items are so small - and would escape screen enclosures - and some hatchlings like to tuck under the leaves near the soil (ABG mix) while digesting their remaining yolk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bio Bin Experiment</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/30/bio-bin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/30/bio-bin/</guid>
      <description>Given that wild baby Panther Chameleons are often found in low brush or tall grass, we would like to simulate that as much as possible. So in 2019, we are experimenting with raising our babies in bio bins for the first month. We have multiple soil layers (drainage, abg &amp;amp; leaf) and 3 - 4 species of insects in every bin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
