<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Judy on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/judy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Judy on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/judy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bubbles</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</guid>
      <description>Bubbles is a massive female. At the one year mark, she already weighs 90 grams when receptive. She came from our Jude x Alla pairing and is one of the few females we decided to keep. She&amp;rsquo;s like a giant version of Alla. Healthy, hungry and bold. Very happy we decided to hold on to this girl!
Bubbles
Bubbles1
Bubbles3
Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Button</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/07/14/button/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/07/14/button/</guid>
      <description>Button was a female with nice high contrast barring from Jude x Alla. We bred her a few times before letting her go to make space for fresh genetics, but she was a phenomenal breeder for us! It will be interesting to see how much the high contrast carries into her offspring.
Button
Button1
Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Button (F3) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash x Judy</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/10/17/flash-judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/10/17/flash-judy/</guid>
      <description>This was our first clutch. Both parents, Flash and Judy, were sourced from Bruce Galbraith at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. Our hatch rate was ~50% and 4 of the babies did not make it to the 3 month mark. That was the baseline that we have tried to improve upon. For this clutch, we had used a standard calcium w/ multivitamin twice a month for most of Judy&amp;rsquo;s life, and we raised the babies in what I would call &amp;ldquo;standard&amp;rdquo; baby bins (not fully-planted, bioactive bins like we use today).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.
Body shot
Dsc00380
Dsc00383
Jude
Jude2
Filial Group F2 Sire Flash Dam Judy 4 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Jude (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy&#39;s First Clutch</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/03/21/first-clutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/03/21/first-clutch/</guid>
      <description>Female Fucifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons) will rock back and forth with their mouth agape in a defensive posture when they are not ready to mate.
It is always good to introduce the female into the male&amp;rsquo;s enclosure to avoid injury to either animal because their body language is not for show. Males are often too persistent for their own good. In the beginning of March, Judy climbed willingly into Flash&amp;rsquo;s cage, but we had to try multiple times before she was confortable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Chameleon&#39;s Paradise</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/chameleonparadise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/chameleonparadise/</guid>
      <description>Chameleon Paradise Cowboy WC
Cowboy
Cowboy2
Cowboy3
Candy Cane F1
Candy cane
Candy cane1
Candy cane2
Candy cane3
Jake F1 Jake
Jake1
Jake2
King King
King1
24k 24k
24k1
24k3
600 24k1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy</title>
      <link>/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</guid>
      <description>Judy was our first generation breeder from Candy Cane (F1) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. She laid one good clutch for us but died during laying complications after 2 more infertile clutches.
Judy (1)
Judy (2)
Judy (3)
Judy (4)
Judy (6)
Judy 1 year
Filial Group F2 Sire Candy Cane Dam Jake&amp;rsquo;s daughter 3 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Judy (F2) Generation 1 1. Judy (F2). Judy was born on 2015-02-11 at Chameleon&#39;s Paradise.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
