<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>artemis on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/artemis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in artemis on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/artemis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Daisy</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/17/arti-daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/17/arti-daisy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Daisy, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Daisy is a great female from our Jude x Kako clutch. Some of my favorite yellows came from this pairing and Daisy didn&amp;rsquo;t disappoint ;)
Arti x Daisy Hatch dates 10/17/2021 - 10/26/2021 Hatch rate 4/26 1st
Img 0370</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/17/ghost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/17/ghost/</guid>
      <description>Ghost is a 4th gen ybbb Ambilobe breeder here at iPardalis. He is from our Arti and Daisy pairing. His yellows are so light when he fires up that we decided to name him Ghost. They are just so clean and bright! There is also an H bar on his right side. We are very excited to have him carry the torch on this part of our tree.
Ghost</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dehibe</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/16/dehibe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/16/dehibe/</guid>
      <description>Dehibe is a great YBBB Ambilobe we produced with Arti and Alla. He brings some great blue bars and a yellow body, very similar to his sire. He and his sister, Artalla, were the only two babies to survive Alla&amp;rsquo;s last clutch, and they are very special to us. This is a great cb combination without any of our main line in it.
Dehibe
Dehibe1
Dehibe2
Dehibe3
Dehibe4
Filial F4-CG13 Sire Arti Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artalla</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/15/artalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/15/artalla/</guid>
      <description>Artalla is a very special HB female from Arti, a great ybbb breeder for us produced by Brian Stewart, and Alla, one of our first females and most prolific breeder who gave us 17 clutches over her long life! Artalla has some big shoes to fill, and we are extremely excited to work with her :)
Artalla
Artalla1
Filial F4-CG13 Sire Arti Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Artalla (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Alla</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/15/arti-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/15/arti-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our most prolific female from Panther Creek Chameleons, Alla, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Alla is a wonderful female from JJ who was produced by Kammerflage Kreations. We only had a single clutch from these two because it was towards the end of Alla&amp;rsquo;s breeding career.
Arti x Alla Hatch dates 10/15/2021 - 10/19/2021 Hatch rate 3/20 Dehibe</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arti x CH Bohana</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/09/15/arti-bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/09/15/arti-bohana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our first captive hatched (CH) female, Bohana, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Bohana is a female Ambilobe hatched out by Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics from a wild caught imported female. Bohana&amp;rsquo;s wild genes didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to add much to our project when combined with Arti, so we did not keep any of these animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Tigravavy</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/28/arti-tigravavy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/28/arti-tigravavy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Tigravavy, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Tigravavy is a stunning female from our Jude x Alla clutch. We were very happy with these guys!
Arti x Tigravavy Hatch dates 6/28/2021 - 7/29/2021 Hatch rate 25/26 F1
F2
M1
M10
M2
M3
M4
M5
M6</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Amara</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/01/nugget-amara/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/01/nugget-amara/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our female from Brian Stewart, Amara. Amara proved out to carry a lot of her sire&amp;rsquo;s, Artemis&amp;rsquo;, traits like his dark blue bars and red highlighting. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination of colorful ybbb with both blue bars and clean yellows!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tigerlilly</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/01/tigerlilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/01/tigerlilly/</guid>
      <description>Tiger Lilly is one of the most stunning females I have seen in person. She has an amazing bar/body contrast, organge highlights in her face and turrets and an orang glow on her arms and tail. We are very lucky to get to work with her. Hopefully, those traits are a sign that she is as cool as her sire, Nugget.
Tigerlilly
Tigerlilly1
Tigerlilly2
Tigerlilly3
Tigerlilly4
Tigerlilly5
Filial F4-CG13 Sire Nugget Dam Amara 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tony</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/01/tony/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/01/tony/</guid>
      <description>Tony one of our 4th generation YBBB Ambilobe. He has some great traits from his dam, Amara, like his deep blue bars and red highlights, but he also has some vibrant yellows from his sire, Nugget. His profile is one of my favorites with striking turret and gular lines. We are very lucky to have him in our breeding group!
Tony
Tony1
Tony2
Tony3
Tony4
Tony5
Tony6
Tony7
Tony8</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arti</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</guid>
      <description>Arti is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. He brings some great deep blue bars and a yellow body. We are very excited to see what he produces in concert with our existing lines!
Arti
Arti1
Arti2
Arti3
Arti4
Arti5
Arti6
Arti7
Arti8
Filial F3 Sire Artemis Dam Felipe Sanchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Arti Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amara</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/04/04/amara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/04/04/amara/</guid>
      <description>Amara is Arti&amp;rsquo;s sister from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. It will be interesting to compare her offspring with Arti&amp;rsquo;s to figure out which traits she is carrying from their shared lineage. I have always been curious about the females role in breeding and I think it is the key to producing some extraordinary animals.
Amara
Amara1
Amara2
Filial F3 Sire Artemis Dam Felipe Sanchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Colorado Chameleon</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/22/coloradochams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/22/coloradochams/</guid>
      <description> Colorado Chameleon Arlo (WC) Arlo
Arlo1
Arlo2
Artemis Artemis
Artemis1
Artemis2
Artemis3
Artemis4
Artemis5
Sire Fantara Dam Felipe Sannchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter Perregrin/Pryo&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Sire Perregrin/Pyro Dam Miss Piggy </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
