<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sparkles on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/sparkles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sparkles on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/sparkles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blossom x Mavokely</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/20/blossom-mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/20/blossom-mavokely/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Blossom, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Mavokely. Mavokely is from one of our favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe, Amarillo, and Blossom is the HB male from our Jude x Alla clutch. Great combination of colorful ybbb and clean yellows!
Blossom x Mavokely Hatch dates 6/20/2021 - 6/24/2021 Hatch rate 22/22 F1
F2
M2
M3
M4
Hatch dates 8/08/2021 - 8/22/2021 Hatch rate 23/26 F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blossom x Maitso</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/01/27/blossom-maitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/01/27/blossom-maitso/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Blossom, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Maitso. Maitso is from one of our favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe, Amarillo, and Blossom is the HB male from our Jude x Alla clutch. Great combination of colorful ybbb and clean yellows! Kiborin is our keeper from this group.
Blossom x Maitso Hatch dates 1/27/2021 - 3/07/2021 Hatch rate 25/27 1st
10th</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack x Mavokely</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Jack, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Mavokely. Jack had some of the nicest yellows from Jude x Alla and Bobby&amp;rsquo;s boy Amarillo is one of my favorite ybbb of all time. These guys should be very special.
Jack x Mavokely Hatch dates 1/20/2021 - 3/17/2021 Hatch rate 3/21 M1
Hb
Hb1
Jackson1
Jackson4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>manjaya</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/12/06/manjaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/12/06/manjaya/</guid>
      <description>Manjaya s Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s sister and she brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with his daughters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>manjalla</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/12/05/manjalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/12/05/manjalla/</guid>
      <description>Manjalla is Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s sister and she brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with his daughter!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</guid>
      <description>Manjaka brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with him!
Manjaka
Manjaka1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manga</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</guid>
      <description>Manga had some of the nicest yellows from all of Bleu and Patch&amp;rsquo;s sons. He has a striking facial pattern and is a classic Ambilobe panther chameleon. We&amp;rsquo;re very lucky to have him in our 4th generation breeding program.
Manga
Manga1
Manga2
Manga3
Manga4
Manga5
Manga6
Manga7
Manga8
Filial F4-CG4 Sire Bleu Dam Patch 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Manga Generation 1 1. Manga. Manga was born on 2020-10-28 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunny</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/06/10/sunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/06/10/sunny/</guid>
      <description>Sunny was my second favorite female from the Jude x Kako clutch, hatched 6/5/19. She reminds me a lot of her mother, Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. With any luck we will be able to grap a killer yellow body blue bar male from her and Zanaka.
Sunny
Sunny1
Sunny2
Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</guid>
      <description>Nugget was an alpha male from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. He has many of the traits I love about Jude/Flash. He is a bold YBBB with great lineage. His yellows are more vibrant and his blue bars do not have any red pock marks like Jude. He is an amazingly clean yellow body blue bar Ambilobe.
Nugget
Nugget1
Nugget2
Nugget3
Nugget4
Nugget5
Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/06/08/patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/06/08/patch/</guid>
      <description>Patch was my favorite female from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her line is an extremely strong yellow body blue bar Ambilobe group, so I have high hopes!
Patch
Patch1
Patch2
Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Patch (F3) Generation 1 1. Patch (F3).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daisy</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/06/07/daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/06/07/daisy/</guid>
      <description>Daisy also has some really nice purples, hatched 6/5/19 from Jude x Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her 19 male siblings were bright yellow bodied blue bar Ambilobe, with the exception of one male who fired red bar. I hope she can function like a female version of her brother, Nugget, in our pairings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lilly</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/06/06/lilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/06/06/lilly/</guid>
      <description>Lilly has some really nice purples, hatched 6/5/19 from Jude x Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her daughters will hopefully be equally beautiful, but we have a theory that her coloration indicates her sons will be killer yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe! Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Lilly (F3) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Kako</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/06/05/jude-kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/06/05/jude-kako/</guid>
      <description>This pairing gave us Nugget, Patch, Sunny, Lilly, and Daisy.
Jude x Kako F2
Hatch dates 6/5/2019 - 6/19/2019 Hatch rate 34/34 Daisy
Img 1
Img 11
Img 2
Img 2535
Img 2584
Img 2587
Img 2612
Img 2619
Img 2631
Img 2678
Img 2718
Img 2780
Img 2813
Img 2828
Img 2857
Img 2917
Img 2919
Img 2954
Img 2977
Img 3224
Img 3632
Img 3642
Img 3873</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kako</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</guid>
      <description>Kako was one of the two females we paired with our second generation breeder - Jude. We purchased her from RB Barto, but she was produced by Bobby Ruddock. Her line is one of our favorite yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe lines in the USA. Vibrant yellows and clean blue bars.
Kako
Kako1
Filial Group F2 Sire Sparkles Dam Leo&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 4 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Kako (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Bobby Ruddock</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/bobbyruddock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/bobbyruddock/</guid>
      <description> Sparkles F1
Sparkles1
Sparkles2
Sire Son of Loza and Flamming River&amp;rsquo;s daughter Dam Unknown WC Amarillo F2
Amarillo
Amarillo1
Sire Sparkles Dam Leo Sasha Sire Sinister </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Company</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/pantherco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/pantherco/</guid>
      <description>Panther Company Leo Leo
Leo1
Leo1
Leo2
Leo3
Leo4
Leo5
Leo6
Leo7</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
