<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jack on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/jack/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jack on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/jack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>parasy</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/01/21/parasy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/01/21/parasy/</guid>
      <description>Parasy is Jackson&amp;rsquo;s sister. She has great YBBB potential from our 4th generation of Ambilobe. We will have to prove her out to see which side of the tree she takes after, but her lineage is phenomenal on both sides. Her dam sire is one of our favorites from Bobby Rodduck, and Jack was one of the best YBBB from our Jude x Alla pairing.
Parasy
Parasy1
Parasy2
Parasy3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack x Mavokely</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Jack, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Mavokely. Jack had some of the nicest yellows from Jude x Alla and Bobby&amp;rsquo;s boy Amarillo is one of my favorite ybbb of all time. These guys should be very special.
Jack x Mavokely Hatch dates 1/20/2021 - 3/17/2021 Hatch rate 3/21 M1
Hb
Hb1
Jackson1
Jackson4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jackson</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/01/20/jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/01/20/jackson/</guid>
      <description>Jackson is a great YBBB from our 4th generation of Ambilobe. Son of Jack, he brings some great blue bars and a yellow body w/ a little less red/orange highlighting than his father. His dam sire is one of our favorites from Bobby Rodduck, so he&amp;rsquo;s a very valuable addition to our project!
Jackson
Jackson1
Jackson2
Jackson3
Jackson4
Jackson5
mtDNA Haplogroup* 3 (Ambilobe East) Filial F4-CG13 Sire Jack Dam Mavokely *preliminary results</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</guid>
      <description>Jack is a beautiful Ambilobe from our Jude x Alla pairing. When he was young, his yellows were dominant and covered his entire body. However, as he aged, oranges started to creep into his body from his gular and his tail turned a vibrant red. He is a beautiful animal, but that is not the look we are breeding for long-term, aside from his clean blue bars and yellow body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alla</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</guid>
      <description>Alla is our most successful female breeder to date. She has a gregarious personality and brings some of the nicest YBBB Kammerflage Kreations lineage into our project via her sire, JJ. We were very lucky to pick her up from Panther Creek Chameleons back in 2017 before JJ was sold to Chromatic Chameleons.
Alla
Alla1
Alla2
Filial Unknown Sire JJ Dam Blue Bird&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 3 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Alla Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.
Body shot
Dsc00380
Dsc00383
Jude
Jude2
Filial Group F2 Sire Flash Dam Judy 4 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Jude (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kammerflage Kreations</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</guid>
      <description>Kammerflage Kreations Manome-toky (Promise Keeper) Sire Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) Dam Vony-reny Promise keeper
Promise keeper1
Promise keeper2
Promise keeper3
Promise keeper4
Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) 67102557 214752709408715 5451583889820614656 n
67119195 2313830222028769 4345136138969677824 n
Ankoso-bolamena (Goldie) Sire Ihany-drako (My Friend) Dam Hay-vao (Novel) Ihany-drako (My Friend) Sire Ampiosonga-fantatra (Also Known As) Dam Unknown My friend
Myfriend
Myfriend1
Hay-vao (Novel) Sire WC Bakaina (Divergent) Dam Goavy (Guava) Ampiosonga-fantatra (Also Known As) Sire Unknown Dam Unknown Alsoknownas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Creek Chameleons</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</guid>
      <description>Panther Creek JJ Jj
Jj1
Jj2
Jj3
Jj4
Jj5
Jj6
Sire Mavo-ra (Yellow Blood) Dam Sire Kely-tongotra (Little Foot) Wet Dream Wetdream
Wetdream1
Wetdream2
Sire Macho Dam Sire 24k&amp;rsquo;s daughter Test Sire Bolt Dam Sire Marley </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy</title>
      <link>/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</guid>
      <description>Judy was our first generation breeder from Candy Cane (F1) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. She laid one good clutch for us but died during laying complications after 2 more infertile clutches.
Judy (1)
Judy (2)
Judy (3)
Judy (4)
Judy (6)
Judy 1 year
Filial Group F2 Sire Candy Cane Dam Jake&amp;rsquo;s daughter 3 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Judy (F2) Generation 1 1. Judy (F2). Judy was born on 2015-02-11 at Chameleon&#39;s Paradise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash</title>
      <link>/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</guid>
      <description>Flash was our first generation breeder from Cowboy (CH) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. He had a very gentle personality and only gave us one healthy clutch with Judy, from which we kept Jude. We were still learning when we got Flash and he passed after consuming a large number of wild bugs when pesticides had been applied to the lawn behind ours. The vet said that he had kidney failure like he&amp;rsquo;d been poisoned, but we have been continuing to improve our husbandry year-after-year in his honor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
