<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Papafee on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/papafee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Papafee on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/papafee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WC Dia x Vaosary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/29/dia-vaosary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/29/dia-vaosary/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was the only successful clutch with WC Dia. We paired him to our 5th gen female named Vaosary from Papafee x Lokana. Vaosary was a stand out female with a lot of orange from one of my favorite 5th gen groups. Because of how rare this line will be, they are a great option for breeders looking for high-quality foundation animals at the F1 generation. Really love that we got some WC Dia and Papafee clones in the mix here - very cool stuff!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimanga x Bumblebee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/28/jimanga-bumblebee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/28/jimanga-bumblebee/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our 5th gen male named Jimanga from Manga x Imelda, and a 5th gen female named Bumble Bee from Papafee x Lokana. This is the combination of two of our favorite lines and the culmination of years of selective breeding for yellow body blue bar traits. If they don&amp;rsquo;t prove out, we have no one to blame but ourselves! ;)&#xA;Hatch dates 6/28/23 - 7/10/23 Hatch rate 23/26 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mami</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/11/mami/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/11/mami/</guid>
      <description>Mami is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has more purples and pinks like her mother, Lokana, whereas her two sisters Vaosary and Bumble Bee remind me of their aunts, Papafee&amp;rsquo;s sisters. Her first pairing is with our new WC Ambilobe, so we expect her to produce some absolutely amazing F1 YBBB Ambilobe for us!&#xA;Mami&#xA;Mami1&#xA;Mami2&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papamavo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/01/papamavo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/01/papamavo/</guid>
      <description>Papamavo is one of our 5th generation Ambilobe Panther Chameleon breeders from Papafee x Lokana. He has great vibrancy and a solid yellow body. His attitude is a bit more feisty than his father, but he&amp;rsquo;s calming down a bit now as he reaches adulthood. We are excited to see what he does for us!&#xA;Papamavo&#xA;Papamavo1&#xA;Papamavo2&#xA;Papamavo3&#xA;Papamavo4&#xA;Papamavo5&#xA;Papamavo6&#xA;Papamavo7&#xA;Papamavo8&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaosary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/12/vaosary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/12/vaosary/</guid>
      <description>Vaosary is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has a rusty coloration with even more orange than her sister Bumble Bee. Her first pairing is with our new WC Ambilobe, so we expect her to produce some absolutely amazing F1 YBBB Ambilobe for us!&#xA;Vaosary&#xA;Vaosary1&#xA;Vaosary2&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Vaosary (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bumble Bee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/11/bumblebee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/11/bumblebee/</guid>
      <description>Bumble Bee is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has a great personality and a rusty coloration with lots of orange and light purple dots. We expect her to produce some absolutely amazing Ambilobe for us!&#xA;Bumblebee&#xA;Bumblebee1&#xA;Bumblebee2&#xA;Bumblebee3&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Bumble Bee (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Bumble Bee (F4-CG14). Bumble Bee was born on 2022-01-11 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papafee x Lokana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/11/papafee-lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/11/papafee-lokana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Papafee, and our Ambilobe female from Chromatic Chameleons, Lokana. Lokana is from a great pairing between Kromatisk and Shirley. Kromatisk is one of my favorite Ambilobe breeders in the USA and Shirley is from one of my favorite ybbb combinations from Kammerflage Kreations. Papafee is the HB male from our Zanaka x Sunny clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the fourth generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pepita</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/07/pepita/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/07/pepita/</guid>
      <description>Pepita is a great 5th gen YBBB from our Papafee x Coco pairing. She only had 3 brothers, and at least one looked a lot like the Landy side of Coco&amp;rsquo;s lineage. Therefore, my expectation is that Pepita will throw Papafee or Landy looks. It will be a lot of fun to see what she does for us. She definitely resembles Coco more than Papafee&amp;rsquo;s dam, Sunny.&#xA;Pepita&#xA;Pepita1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papafee x Coco</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/04/papafee-coco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/04/papafee-coco/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Papafee, and our little Ambilobe female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Coco. Coco is from a great pairing between Hendrix and Foxey. Hendrix brings a new WC Ambilobe line into the project and Foxey is from one of my favorite ybbb combinations from Kammerflage Kreations. Papafee is the HB male from our Zanaka x Sunny clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the fourth generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papafee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</guid>
      <description>Papafee is a monster yellow-bodied Ambilobe. He was our sole holdback from Zanaka and Sunny to carry on in our 4th generation of Ambilobe panther chameleons. His yellows are extremely vibrant and were evident at a young age (2 months). He almost has a neon quality to him and he is about 24&amp;quot; head to tail. A very impressive animal.&#xA;Papafee&#xA;Papafee1&#xA;Papafee2&#xA;Papafee3&#xA;Papafee4&#xA;Papafee5&#xA;Filial F3-CG12 Sire Zanaka Dam Sunny 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
