<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>papafee on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/papafee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in papafee on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/papafee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vaosary</title>
      <link>/blog/2022/01/12/vaosary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022/01/12/vaosary/</guid>
      <description>Vaosary is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has a rusty coloration with even more orange than her sister Bumble Bee. Her first pairing is with our new WC Ambilobe, so we expect her to produce some absolutely amazing F1 YBBB Ambilobe for us!
Vaosary
Vaosary1
Vaosary2
Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Vaosary (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bumble Bee</title>
      <link>/blog/2022/01/11/bumble-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022/01/11/bumble-bee/</guid>
      <description>Bumble Bee is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has a great personality and a rusty coloration with lots of orange and light purple dots. We expect her to produce some absolutely amazing Ambilobe for us!
Bumblebee
Bumblebee1
Bumblebee2
Bumblebee3
Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Bumble Bee (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Bumble Bee (F4-CG14). Bumble Bee was born on 2022-01-11 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papafee x Lokana</title>
      <link>/blog/2022/01/11/papafee-lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022/01/11/papafee-lokana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Papafee, and our Ambilobe female from Chromatic Chameleons, Lokana. Lokana is from a great pairing between Kromatisk and Shirley. Kromatisk is one of my favorite Ambilobe breeders in the USA and Shirley is from one of my favorite ybbb combinations from Kammerflage Kreations. Papafee is the HB male from our Zanaka x Sunny clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the fourth generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papafee x Coco</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/12/04/papafee-coco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/12/04/papafee-coco/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Papafee, and our little Ambilobe female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Coco. Coco is from a great pairing between Hendrix and Foxey. Hendrix brings a new WC Ambilobe line into the project and Foxey is from one of my favorite ybbb combinations from Kammerflage Kreations. Papafee is the HB male from our Zanaka x Sunny clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the fourth generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papafee</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</guid>
      <description>Papafee is a monster yellow-bodied Ambilobe. He was our sole holdback from Zanaka and Sunny to carry on in our 4th generation of Ambilobe panther chameleons. His yellows are extremely vibrant and were evident at a young age (2 months). He almost has a neon quality to him and he is about 24&amp;quot; head to tail. A very impressive animal.
Papafee
Papafee1
Papafee2
Papafee3
Papafee4
Papafee5
Filial F3 Sire Zanaka Dam Sunny 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
