<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manga on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/manga/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manga on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/manga/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jimanga x Bumblebee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/28/jimanga-bumblebee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/28/jimanga-bumblebee/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our 5th gen male named Jimanga from Manga x Imelda, and a 5th gen female named Bumble Bee from Papafee x Lokana. This is the combination of two of our favorite lines and the culmination of years of selective breeding for yellow body blue bar traits. If they don&amp;rsquo;t prove out, we have no one to blame but ourselves! ;)&#xA;Hatch dates 6/28/23 - 7/10/23 Hatch rate 23/26 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimanga</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/jimanga/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/jimanga/</guid>
      <description>Jimanga is one of our 5th gen Ambilobe breeders. He comes from our Manga x Imelda pairing, a great collab with Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics. I can trace his personality all the way back to Kako. They teach you that chameleons are a look-but-don&amp;rsquo;t-touch pet, the hard way haha&amp;hellip; but what comes with that is an absolutely amazing defense display. Definitely something I really enjoy about these guys!&#xA;Jimanga&#xA;Jimanga1&#xA;Jimanga2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimelda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/jimelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/jimelda/</guid>
      <description>Jimelda is Jimanga&amp;rsquo;s sister from our Manga x Imelda pairing. She has some wonderful purples and a fiesty attitude! Manga was one of our best ybbb of all time, so we are really hoping Jimelda carries some of those traits into an F1 gen with WC Bibi. Those could very well be some of the best in the country if they prove out.&#xA;Jimelda&#xA;Jimelda1&#xA;Jimelda2&#xA;Jimelda3&#xA;Jimelda4&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Manga Dam Imelda 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manga x Imelda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/manga-imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/manga-imelda/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Manga, and our female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Imelda. Imelda is a great mix of WC Gambit lines and Kammerflage Kreations yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe while Manga is the male with the most striking yellows from our Bleu x Patch clutch. We kept Jimanga from this group and he has his father&amp;rsquo;s wonderful profile! Just a gorgeous group of Ambilobe.&#xA;Hatch dates 12/03/2021 - 2/19/2022 Hatch rate 15/19 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manga</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</guid>
      <description>Manga had some of the nicest yellows from all of Bleu and Patch&amp;rsquo;s sons. He has a striking facial pattern and is a classic Ambilobe panther chameleon. We&amp;rsquo;re very lucky to have him in our 4th generation breeding program.&#xA;Manga&#xA;Manga1&#xA;Manga2&#xA;Manga3&#xA;Manga4&#xA;Manga5&#xA;Manga6&#xA;Manga7&#xA;Manga8&#xA;Filial F4-CG4 Sire Bleu Dam Patch 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Manga Generation 1 1. Manga. Manga was born on 2020-10-28 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
