<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>manga on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/manga/</link>
    <description>Recent content in manga on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/manga/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jimanga</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/12/03/jimanga/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/12/03/jimanga/</guid>
      <description>Jimanga is one of our 5th gen Ambilobe breeders. He comes from our Manga x Imelda pairing, a great collab with Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics. I can trace his personality all the way back to Kako. They teach you that chameleons are a look-but-don&amp;rsquo;t-touch pet, the hard way haha&amp;hellip; but what comes with that is an absolutely amazing defense display. Definitely something I really enjoy about these guys!
Jimanga
Jimanga1
Jimanga2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manga x Imelda</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/12/03/manga-imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/12/03/manga-imelda/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Manga, and our female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Imelda. Imelda is a great mix of WC Gambit lines and Kammerflage Kreations yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe while Manga is the male with the most striking yellows from our Bleu x Patch clutch. We kept Jimanga from this group and he has his father&amp;rsquo;s wonderful profile! Just a gorgeous group of Ambilobe.
Manga x Imelda Hatch dates 12/03/2021 - 2/19/2022 Hatch rate 15/19 M1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manga</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</guid>
      <description>Manga had some of the nicest yellows from all of Bleu and Patch&amp;rsquo;s sons. He has a striking facial pattern and is a classic Ambilobe panther chameleon. We&amp;rsquo;re very lucky to have him in our 4th generation breeding program.
Manga
Manga1
Manga2
Manga3
Manga4
Manga5
Manga6
Manga7
Manga8
Filial F4-CG4 Sire Bleu Dam Patch 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Manga Generation 1 1. Manga. Manga was born on 2020-10-28 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
