<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Retired Panther Chameleons on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/retired-pardalis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Retired Panther Chameleons on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/retired-pardalis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Zor</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/24/zor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/24/zor/</guid>
      <description>Zor is a great YBBB we produced with our Kammerflage male from Gold Rush named Zozoro. We paired him to our gorgeous female from Arti x Alla, Artalla. He brings some great baby blue bars and a lime green to yellow body. We only paired him a few times before letting him go to his forever home.&#xA;Zor&#xA;Zor1&#xA;Zor2&#xA;Zor3&#xA;Zor4&#xA;Zor5&#xA;Zor6&#xA;Zor7&#xA;Zor8&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Zozoro Dam Artalla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parasi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/20/parasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/20/parasi/</guid>
      <description>Parasi is a great Ambilobe female from our F1 sire from Colorado Chameleon named Manjaka and our female from Jack and Mavokely. Many of her brothers had great yellow bodies and blue bars - a few had mixed red/blue bars. We are very excited to see what she does with WC Tratra!&#xA;Parasi&#xA;Parasi1&#xA;Filial F2-CG14 Sire Manjaka Dam Parasy 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Parasi (F2-CG14) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miafina (WC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/29/miafina/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/29/miafina/</guid>
      <description>Imported by One World Exotica in June 2022.&#xA;Miafina is a wild caught (WC) Ambilobe Panther Chameleon. Miafina is derived from the Malagasy word for &amp;ldquo;mystery&amp;rdquo; because her phenotype is a complete mystery. We are very excited to prove her out with our WC Tratra who is an Ambilobe male without very much, if any, red highlighting. When we watch her sons develop, we&amp;rsquo;ll get an estimate for what she brings to the table besides fresh WC genetics!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tratra (WC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/29/tratra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/29/tratra/</guid>
      <description>Imported by One World Exotica&#xA;Tratra is a classic wild caught (WC) Ambilobe panther chameleon. Tratra translates to &amp;ldquo;caught&amp;rdquo; in Malagasy, which complements our other two WC Bibi and WC Dia because bibidia translates to &amp;ldquo;wild&amp;rdquo; in Malagasy. After we failed to fully acclimate Dia, we decided to try again with Tratra. He has beautiful baby blue bars like our first CB holdback, Jude, and a nice consistent green body color.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dia (WC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/28/dia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/28/dia/</guid>
      <description>Imported by One World Exotica in June 2022.&#xA;Dia was our favorite WC import, between him and Bibi. He had a clean yellow body and his bars showed more blue as he settled in; however, he did not fully acclimate and we only got a few clutches from him. We did find him some top notch females from our line, so hopefully those great traits get worked into the gene pool!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranoka</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/05/ranoka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/05/ranoka/</guid>
      <description>Ranoka is a really interesting mix of F1 Manjaka and Kromatisk, Lokana&amp;rsquo;s sire. He has the radiant yellow that Manjaka has, but he also has the red embers at the edge of the yellow like Kromatisk - this almost looks orange at times and gives it an almost 3D look against a blue background. Really unique animal!&#xA;Ranoka&#xA;Ranoka1&#xA;Ranoka2&#xA;Ranoka3&#xA;Ranoka4&#xA;Ranoka5&#xA;Ranoka6&#xA;Ranoka7&#xA;Ranoka8&#xA;Filial F2-CG14 Sire Manjaka Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mami</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/11/mami/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/11/mami/</guid>
      <description>Mami is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has more purples and pinks like her mother, Lokana, whereas her two sisters Vaosary and Bumble Bee remind me of their aunts, Papafee&amp;rsquo;s sisters. Her first pairing is with our new WC Ambilobe, so we expect her to produce some absolutely amazing F1 YBBB Ambilobe for us!&#xA;Mami&#xA;Mami1&#xA;Mami2&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robina</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/07/robina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/07/robina/</guid>
      <description>Robina is a female we acquired from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics Clapton x Layla pairing. Her sire, Clapton, and dam sire, DynamiteTNT, both have phenomenal blue bars which I believe will complement Ralph&amp;rsquo;s really well. With any luck, a few Ralph clones could pop out because Robina is an RBBB x RBBB female. She has some interesting turquoise and subtle differences from most of my other females. She is awesome!&#xA;Robina</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maize</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/13/maize/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/13/maize/</guid>
      <description>Maize is a great YBBB Ambilobe female from our good friend Brian Stewart. McNulty is a male from one of Brian&amp;rsquo;s old projects from the Stryfe line and he paired him up with a female from one of his recent pairings with Artemis from Colorado Chameleons. These should be a lot of fun to prove out because they have three ybbb sires in the closest lineage. Top notch stuff as always!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beans</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/12/beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/12/beans/</guid>
      <description>Beans is a great YBBB Ambilobe female from our good friend Brian Stewart. McNulty is a male from one of Brian&amp;rsquo;s old projects from the Stryfe line and he paired him up with a female from one of his recent pairings with Artemis from Colorado Chameleons. These should be a lot of fun to prove out because they have three ybbb sires in the closest lineage. Top notch stuff as always!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaosary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/12/vaosary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/12/vaosary/</guid>
      <description>Vaosary is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has a rusty coloration with even more orange than her sister Bumble Bee. Her first pairing is with our new WC Ambilobe, so we expect her to produce some absolutely amazing F1 YBBB Ambilobe for us!&#xA;Vaosary&#xA;Vaosary1&#xA;Vaosary2&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Vaosary (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bumble Bee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/11/bumblebee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/11/bumblebee/</guid>
      <description>Bumble Bee is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has a great personality and a rusty coloration with lots of orange and light purple dots. We expect her to produce some absolutely amazing Ambilobe for us!&#xA;Bumblebee&#xA;Bumblebee1&#xA;Bumblebee2&#xA;Bumblebee3&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Bumble Bee (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Bumble Bee (F4-CG14). Bumble Bee was born on 2022-01-11 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/15/artalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/15/artalla/</guid>
      <description>Artalla is a very special HB female from Arti, a great ybbb breeder for us produced by Brian Stewart, and Alla, one of our first females and most prolific breeder who gave us 17 clutches over her long life! Artalla has some big shoes to fill, and we are extremely excited to work with her :)&#xA;Artalla&#xA;Artalla1&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Arti Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Artalla (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zozoro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/06/zozoro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/06/zozoro/</guid>
      <description>Zozoro is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage sire Gold Rush. His father is my favorite YBBB produced over the past few years and his mother is the combination of a vibrant YBBB named My Friend and a true F1 from two different WC that the Kammer&amp;rsquo;s acclimated recently. Very excited to work this guy into our 4th/5th generation of Ambilobe!&#xA;Zozoro&#xA;Zozoro1&#xA;Zozoro2&#xA;Zozoro3&#xA;Zozoro4&#xA;Zozoro5&#xA;Filial F3-CG13 Sire Au-Mirongatra (Gold Rush) Dam Ankoso-Bolamena (Goldie) 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mainty</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/09/05/mainty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/09/05/mainty/</guid>
      <description>Mainty is one of the nicest RBBB females I could find for Ralph. Her sire, Bangheera, is a classic red body blue bar Ambilobe produced by Highlighter Chameleons and owned by Nature&amp;rsquo;s Van Gogh. After talking to Logan about Mainty&amp;rsquo;s brothers, it looks like many of them proved out to be similar to Grape Inferno or Bangheera, so although Moonclaw&amp;rsquo;s sire is Flamethrower, it seems she took after her dam sire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jiolahy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/14/jiolahy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/14/jiolahy/</guid>
      <description>Jiolahy is a big F1 female from Chameleons 101&amp;rsquo;s The Don (WC). She brings fresh ybbb genetics combined with a great CB ybbb line created by Modern Day Dragons. We are very lucky to have her in our breeding group.&#xA;Jiolahy&#xA;Filial F1-CG5 Sire The Don (WC) Dam Perregrin/Pyro&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Jiolahy (F1-CG5) Generation 1 1. Jiolahy (F1-CG5). Jiolahy was born on 2021-07-14 at Eric Thompson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/13/mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/13/mara/</guid>
      <description>Mara is the beautiful sister of Maro. They are a pair of Ambilobe breeders we acquired from Chi-Town Chameleons from their Sammy x Nova (F1) pairing. It is looking like Maro is taking after Sammy, so it will be interesting to prove out Mara and see who her sons resemble.&#xA;Mara&#xA;Mara1&#xA;Mara2&#xA;Mara3&#xA;Mara4&#xA;Mara5&#xA;Filial F3 Sire Sammy Dam Storm 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Mara (F3) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>maro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/13/maro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/13/maro/</guid>
      <description>Maro (F3) is a great edition to our YBBB project. We have been tracking the WC Legion line ever since we saw Jeremy Booker acquire him years ago. This great Chi-town Chameleons Sammy x Storm pairing finally carries those genetics with nice yellow bodies on both sides!&#xA;Maro&#xA;Maro1&#xA;Maro2&#xA;Maro3&#xA;mtDNA Haplogroup* 3 (Ambilobe East) Filial F3 Sire Sammy Dam Storm *preliminary results&#xA;5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Maro (F3) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiborin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/20/kiborin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/20/kiborin/</guid>
      <description>Kiborin is our 4th gen HB from Blossom x Maitso. He is Blaitso&amp;rsquo;s brother. These two are just amazing animals and we are excited to see Kiborin&amp;rsquo;s clean yellow with blue. He has less red highlighting that his father and a really clean look!&#xA;Kiborin&#xA;Kiborin1&#xA;Kiborin2&#xA;Kiborin3&#xA;Kiborin4&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Blossom Dam Maitso 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Kiborin (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1. Kiborin (F4-CG13). Kiborin was born on 2021-06-19 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamony</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/20/mamony/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/20/mamony/</guid>
      <description>Mamony is a nice 4th gen female from our Blossom x Maitso. She resembles Blossom&amp;rsquo;s dam, Alla, more than she resembles her own dam, Maitso. I have a theory that those are hints about which side of the tree a female takes after, so check for Blossom-like offspring from Mamony!&#xA;Mamony&#xA;Mamony1&#xA;Mamony2&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Blossom Dam Maitso 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Mamony (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tigerlilly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/tigerlilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/tigerlilly/</guid>
      <description>Tiger Lilly is one of the most stunning females I have seen in person. She has an amazing bar/body contrast, organge highlights in her face and turrets and an orang glow on her arms and tail. We are very lucky to get to work with her. Hopefully, those traits are a sign that she is as cool as her sire, Nugget.&#xA;Tigerlilly&#xA;Tigerlilly1&#xA;Tigerlilly2&#xA;Tigerlilly3&#xA;Tigerlilly4&#xA;Tigerlilly5&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Nugget Dam Amara 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tony</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/tony/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/tony/</guid>
      <description>Tony one of our 4th generation YBBB Ambilobe. He has some great traits from his dam, Amara, like his deep blue bars and red highlights, but he also has some vibrant yellows from his sire, Nugget. His profile is one of my favorites with striking turret and gular lines. We are very lucky to have him in our breeding group!&#xA;Tony&#xA;Tony1&#xA;Tony2&#xA;Tony3&#xA;Tony4&#xA;Tony5&#xA;Tony6&#xA;Tony7&#xA;Tony8</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kosma</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/05/02/kosma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/05/02/kosma/</guid>
      <description>Kosma is Kosmo&amp;rsquo;s sister. Kosmo is one of my favorite RBBB Ambilobe produced over the past few years. He was sold as an egg by Eric Thompson, purchased as a juvenile by LA Chams and then we acquired him and his sister, Kosma, so we could have a solid RBBB Ambilobe project with two unrelated lines. However, because of their many homes, their lineage information was not very well maintained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>paige</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/17/paige/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/17/paige/</guid>
      <description>Paige is a solid Modern Day Dragons x Tropical Chameleons YBBB female. She has great purples and pinks and a wonderful personality. We are very lucky to have her in our project and comes to us from Tiffany Mallay. Her first pairing will be with our 4th gen sire, Tony.&#xA;Paige&#xA;Paige1&#xA;Paige2&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire PJ Dam Sonny&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Paige (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lelafo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/02/lelafo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/02/lelafo/</guid>
      <description>Lelafo is a very different Ambilobe variety that we acquire specifically to keep the fun rolling with the Alfred line! Her Sire, Vulcan, was produced by Chameleons by Design with two very orange WC males and acquired by New England Chameleons who paired him with an amazing female from their orange boy, Odin. She has a ton of orange and red on both sides. Can&amp;rsquo;t wait to prove her out!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>zava</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/03/21/zava/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/03/21/zava/</guid>
      <description>Zava is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage Kreations Green Giant x Promise Keeper pairing, produced by Ed Kammer. He brings some great deep blue bars and a yellow body with a significant amount of red highlighting. We were really hoping he&amp;rsquo;d have less red and more yellow, so we only did a few clutches with him.&#xA;Zava&#xA;Zava1&#xA;Zava2&#xA;Zava3&#xA;Zava4&#xA;Zava5&#xA;Zava6&#xA;Filial F3-CG13 Sire Itso-triombe (Green Giant) Dam Jiona (June) 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>parasy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/21/parasy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/21/parasy/</guid>
      <description>Parasy is Jackson&amp;rsquo;s sister. She has great YBBB potential from our 4th generation of Ambilobe. We will have to prove her out to see which side of the tree she takes after, but her lineage is phenomenal on both sides. Her dam sire is one of our favorites from Bobby Rodduck, and Jack was one of the best YBBB from our Jude x Alla pairing.&#xA;Parasy&#xA;Parasy1&#xA;Parasy2&#xA;Parasy3</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nuhana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/14/nuhana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/14/nuhana/</guid>
      <description>Nuhana is an F1 female we produced with our 3rd gen ybbb, Nugget and our captive-hatched (CH) female, Bohana. Her brothers have been pretty diverse in their color scheme. Fingers crossed she takes after her father!&#xA;Nuhana&#xA;Nuhana1&#xA;Nuhana2&#xA;Filial F1-CG5 Sire Nugget Dam Bohana 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Nuhana (F1-CG5) Generation 1 1. Nuhana (F1-CG5). Nuhana was born on 2021-01-14 at iPardalis. She is the daughter of Nugget (F3-CG4) and Bohana (CH).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>manjaya</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/06/manjaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/06/manjaya/</guid>
      <description>Manjaya s Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s sister and she brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with his daughters!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>manjalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/05/manjalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/05/manjalla/</guid>
      <description>Manjalla is Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s sister and she brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with his daughter!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>coco</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/04/coco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/04/coco/</guid>
      <description>Coco brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She has phenomenal coloring for a female and has been able to lay and bounce back easily thus far. Very healthy girl!&#xA;Coco&#xA;Coco1&#xA;Coco2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>imelda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</guid>
      <description>Imelda brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She layed successfully, but we have been monitoring a minor gular edema on her. We adjusted her supplementation and feeding schedule. Hopefully, it clears up in no time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>lokana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</guid>
      <description>Lokana is the half-sister of Loko. They each have a 50% chance of bringing Kromatisk&amp;rsquo;s amazing ybbb into our project, but Lokana also has Landy x Hamy from her dam, Shirley&amp;rsquo;s side. Really can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with the two possibilities here. We are very excited to see how she proves out over the years :).&#xA;Lokana&#xA;mtDNA Haplogroup* 3 (Ambilobe East) Filial F9-CG13 Sire Kromatisk Dam Shirley *preliminary results</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaia/</guid>
      <description>Manjaia is Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s 3rd sister we own, and she also brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with his daughter!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</guid>
      <description>Manjaka brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with him!&#xA;Manjaka&#xA;Manjaka1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manga</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</guid>
      <description>Manga had some of the nicest yellows from all of Bleu and Patch&amp;rsquo;s sons. He has a striking facial pattern and is a classic Ambilobe panther chameleon. We&amp;rsquo;re very lucky to have him in our 4th generation breeding program.&#xA;Manga&#xA;Manga1&#xA;Manga2&#xA;Manga3&#xA;Manga4&#xA;Manga5&#xA;Manga6&#xA;Manga7&#xA;Manga8&#xA;Filial F4-CG4 Sire Bleu Dam Patch 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Manga Generation 1 1. Manga. Manga was born on 2020-10-28 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papafee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</guid>
      <description>Papafee is a monster yellow-bodied Ambilobe. He was our sole holdback from Zanaka and Sunny to carry on in our 4th generation of Ambilobe panther chameleons. His yellows are extremely vibrant and were evident at a young age (2 months). He almost has a neon quality to him and he is about 24&amp;quot; head to tail. A very impressive animal.&#xA;Papafee&#xA;Papafee1&#xA;Papafee2&#xA;Papafee3&#xA;Papafee4&#xA;Papafee5&#xA;Filial F3-CG12 Sire Zanaka Dam Sunny 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/18/loko/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/18/loko/</guid>
      <description>Loko is a premium CB Ambilobe from some of the best lines in the USA. Her sire, Kromatisk from Chromatic Chameleons, is one of my favorite active breeders of the locale. My hope is that we can get some little guys that glow yellow from her and Nugget!&#xA;Loko&#xA;Loko1&#xA;Loko2&#xA;Filial Group F5-CG13 Sire Kromatisk Dam Jackie 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Loko Generation 1 1. Loko. Loko was born on 2020-04-18 at Chromatic Chameleons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</guid>
      <description>Arti is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. He brings some great deep blue bars and a yellow body. We are very excited to see what he produces in concert with our existing lines!&#xA;Arti&#xA;Arti1&#xA;Arti2&#xA;Arti3&#xA;Arti4&#xA;Arti5&#xA;Arti6&#xA;Arti7&#xA;Arti8&#xA;Filial F3-CG12 Sire Artemis Dam Felipe Sanchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Arti Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/04/amara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/04/amara/</guid>
      <description>Amara is Arti&amp;rsquo;s sister from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. It will be interesting to compare her offspring with Arti&amp;rsquo;s to figure out which traits she is carrying from their shared lineage. I have always been curious about the females role in breeding and I think it is the key to producing some extraordinary animals.&#xA;Amara&#xA;Amara1&#xA;Amara2&#xA;Filial F3-CG12 Sire Artemis Dam Felipe Sanchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bohana (CH)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/03/29/bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/03/29/bohana/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful captive hatched (CH) female we picked up from Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics. Her brothers have ranged from true solid red body blue bar (RBBB) to yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe, so it will be extremely interesting to see where she lands. Fingers crossed she is carrying the YBBB genes we specialize in! If not, we will pair her to Alfred next to create some fresh combinations of vibrant, multi-colored Ambilobe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/02/15/kanto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/02/15/kanto/</guid>
      <description>Kanto is a beautiful female we picked up from Living Art by Frank Payne this year because her sire, Brightflame, is a great match for Alfred. All we know is that Brightflame came from a Canvas pairing and that some of the last pairings done were Bolt x Marley and Marley x Outline.&#xA;Kanto&#xA;Kanto1&#xA;Filial Group Unknown Sire Brightflame Dam Triple&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 3 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Kanto Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tigravavy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/12/12/tigravavy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/12/12/tigravavy/</guid>
      <description>Tigravavy is a one of our favorite females from the Jude x Alla clutch. Her brothers have been everything from clean ybbb like Mondrian, Clyde, and Toby to more rainbow Ambilobe like Alfred, Blossom and Jack. Predominantly ybbb but a few beautiful odd balls mixed in. Tigravavy has deep browns and a golden body, great contrast. If her sons have even a fraction of her good looks, they will be wild!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maitso</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/11/13/maitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/11/13/maitso/</guid>
      <description>Maitso&amp;rsquo;s sire, Amarillo, is the top yellow boby blue bar Ambilobe in the USA. He is a vibrant yellow from snout to vent without any red to mess with what he has going on. The only way I could concieve of a way to improve upon him is to get some thicker blue bars on him and get rid of the red on his turrets. We&amp;rsquo;ll see what we can do!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mavokely</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/11/12/mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/11/12/mavokely/</guid>
      <description>Mavokely&amp;rsquo;s sire, Amarillo, is the top yellow boby blue bar Ambilobe in the USA. He is a vibrant yellow from snout to vent without any red to mess with what he has going on. The only way I could concieve of a way to improve upon him is to get some thicker blue bars on him and get rid of the red on his turrets. We&amp;rsquo;ll see what we can do!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alfred</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</guid>
      <description>Alfred is an extreme outlier from the Jude x Alla pairing. We were lucky to keep him because he carries some vibrant, almost dark neon colors. His resting colors are some of the nicest I have ever seen in person and I am very excited to work with him moving forward!&#xA;Alfred&#xA;Alfred1&#xA;Alfred2&#xA;Alfred3&#xA;Alfred4&#xA;Alfred5&#xA;Alfred6&#xA;Alfred7&#xA;Alfred8&#xA;Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</guid>
      <description>Jack is a beautiful Ambilobe from our Jude x Alla pairing. When he was young, his yellows were dominant and covered his entire body. However, as he aged, oranges started to creep into his body from his gular and his tail turned a vibrant red. He is a beautiful animal, but that is not the look we are breeding for long-term, aside from his clean blue bars and yellow body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/08/21/zanaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/08/21/zanaka/</guid>
      <description>Zanaka is a giant F2 Ambilobe from Kammerflage Kreations. His personality was gentle to the extreme and he was hard to get fired up. It was almost as if other males didn&amp;rsquo;t exist, but when he saw a female, he would light up and start bobbing like a mad man. He was a phenomenal animal to work with, but he had a lot more red in his bars than what our long-term project goals are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bubbles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</guid>
      <description>Bubbles is a massive female. At the one year mark, she already weighs 90 grams when receptive. She came from our Jude x Alla pairing and is one of the few females we decided to keep. She&amp;rsquo;s like a giant version of Alla. Healthy, hungry and bold. Very happy we decided to hold on to this girl!&#xA;Bubbles&#xA;Bubbles1&#xA;Bubbles3&#xA;Filial F3-CG12 Sire Jude Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bleu</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/15/bleu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/15/bleu/</guid>
      <description>Bleu is a male we picked up from the Stryfe line. He was raised by Jeremy Booker at Brightside Chameleons, and he was a bit of a challenge to work with. We released him in early 2020 and only produced a few clutches with him. We hope to select some nice males from his offspring to bring that line into our project.&#xA;Bleu&#xA;Bleu1&#xA;Bleu2&#xA;Filial F3-CG11 Sire Stryfe Dam Emma Frost 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Button</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/14/button/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/14/button/</guid>
      <description>Button was a female with nice high contrast barring from Jude x Alla. We bred her a few times before letting her go to make space for fresh genetics, but she was a phenomenal breeder for us! It will be interesting to see how much the high contrast carries into her offspring.&#xA;Button&#xA;Button1&#xA;Filial F3-CG12 Sire Jude Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Button (F3) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blossom</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</guid>
      <description>We got lucky holding back Blossom from Jude x Alla. He looks like a mini-JJ, Alla&amp;rsquo;s sire, and is a key member of our 3rd generation breeding group. His personality is very similar to Alla&amp;rsquo;s in that he is very bold and rarely defensive. His yellows are bright and his colors are very vibrant. I could not be happier with how he has turned out!&#xA;Blossom&#xA;Blossom1&#xA;Blossom2&#xA;Blossom3</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunny</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/10/sunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/10/sunny/</guid>
      <description>Sunny was my second favorite female from the Jude x Kako clutch, hatched 6/5/19. She reminds me a lot of her mother, Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. With any luck we will be able to grap a killer yellow body blue bar male from her and Zanaka.&#xA;Sunny&#xA;Sunny1&#xA;Sunny2&#xA;Filial F3-CG4 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</guid>
      <description>Nugget was an alpha male from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. He has many of the traits I love about Jude/Flash. He is a bold YBBB with great lineage. His yellows are more vibrant and his blue bars do not have any red pock marks like Jude. He is an amazingly clean yellow body blue bar Ambilobe.&#xA;Nugget&#xA;Nugget1&#xA;Nugget2&#xA;Nugget3&#xA;Nugget4&#xA;Nugget5&#xA;Filial F3-CG4 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/08/patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/08/patch/</guid>
      <description>Patch was my favorite female from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her line is an extremely strong yellow body blue bar Ambilobe group, so I have high hopes!&#xA;Patch&#xA;Patch1&#xA;Patch2&#xA;Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Patch (F3) Generation 1 1. Patch (F3).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daisy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/07/daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/07/daisy/</guid>
      <description>Daisy also has some really nice purples, hatched 6/5/19 from Jude x Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her 19 male siblings were bright yellow bodied blue bar Ambilobe, with the exception of one male who fired red bar. I hope she can function like a female version of her brother, Nugget, in our pairings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lilly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/06/lilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/06/lilly/</guid>
      <description>Lilly has some really nice purples, hatched 6/5/19 from Jude x Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her daughters will hopefully be equally beautiful, but we have a theory that her coloration indicates her sons will be killer yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe!&#xA;Lilly&#xA;Lilly1&#xA;Lilly2&#xA;Lilly3&#xA;Lilly4&#xA;Filial F3-CG4 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</guid>
      <description>Alla is our most successful female breeder to date. She has a gregarious personality and brings some of the nicest YBBB Kammerflage Kreations lineage into our project via her sire, JJ. We were very lucky to pick her up from Panther Creek Chameleons back in 2017 before JJ was sold to Chromatic Chameleons.&#xA;Alla&#xA;Alla1&#xA;Alla2&#xA;Filial F8-CG11 Sire JJ Dam Blue Bird&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Alla Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kako</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</guid>
      <description>Kako was one of the two females we paired with our second generation breeder - Jude. We purchased her from RB Barto, but she was produced by Bobby Ruddock. Her line is one of our favorite yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe lines in the USA. Vibrant yellows and clean blue bars.&#xA;Kako&#xA;Kako1&#xA;Filial Group F2 Sire Sparkles Dam Leo&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 4 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Kako (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.&#xA;Body shot&#xA;Dsc00380&#xA;Dsc00383&#xA;Jude&#xA;Jude2&#xA;Filial Group F2 Sire Flash Dam Judy 4 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Jude (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</guid>
      <description>Judy was our first generation breeder from Candy Cane (F1) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. She laid one good clutch for us but died during laying complications after 2 more infertile clutches.&#xA;Judy (1)&#xA;Judy (2)&#xA;Judy (3)&#xA;Judy (4)&#xA;Judy (6)&#xA;Judy 1 year&#xA;Filial Group F2 Sire Candy Cane Dam Jake&amp;rsquo;s daughter 3 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Judy (F2) Generation 1 1. Judy (F2). Judy was born on 2015-02-11 at Chameleon&#39;s Paradise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</guid>
      <description>Flash was our first generation breeder from Cowboy (CH) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. He had a very gentle personality and only gave us one healthy clutch with Judy, from which we kept Jude. We were still learning when we got Flash and he passed after consuming a large number of wild bugs when pesticides had been applied to the lawn behind ours. The vet said that he had kidney failure like he&amp;rsquo;d been poisoned, but we have been continuing to improve our husbandry year-after-year in his honor.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
