<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>retired-ambilobe on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>https://ipardalis.com/categories/retired-ambilobe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in retired-ambilobe on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ipardalis.com/categories/retired-ambilobe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>zava</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/03/21/zava/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/03/21/zava/</guid>
      <description>Zava is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage Kreations Green Giant x Promise Keeper pairing, produced by Ed Kammer. He brings some great deep blue bars and a yellow body with a significant amount of red highlighting. We were really hoping he&amp;rsquo;d have less red and more yellow, so we only did a few clutches with him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arti</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</guid>
      <description>Arti is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. He brings some great deep blue bars and a yellow body. We are very excited to see what he produces in concert with our existing lines!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanto</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/02/15/kanto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/02/15/kanto/</guid>
      <description>Kanto is a beautiful female we picked up from Living Art by Frank Payne this year because her sire, Brightflame, is a great match for Alfred. All we know is that Brightflame came from a Canvas pairing and that some of the last pairings done were Bolt x Marley and Marley x Outline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tigravavy</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/12/12/tigravavy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/12/12/tigravavy/</guid>
      <description>Tigravavy is a one of our favorite females from the Jude x Alla clutch. Her brothers have been everything from clean ybbb like Mondrian, Clyde, and Toby to more rainbow Ambilobe like Alfred, Blossom and Jack. Predominantly ybbb but a few beautiful odd balls mixed in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</guid>
      <description>Jack is a beautiful Ambilobe from our Jude x Alla pairing. When he was young, his yellows were dominant and covered his entire body. However, as he aged, oranges started to creep into his body from his gular and his tail turned a vibrant red. He is a beautiful animal, but that is not the look we are breeding for long-term, aside from his clean blue bars and yellow body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/08/21/zanaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/08/21/zanaka/</guid>
      <description>Zanaka is a giant F2 Ambilobe from Kammerflage Kreations. His personality was gentle to the extreme and he was hard to get fired up. It was almost as if other males didn&amp;rsquo;t exist, but when he saw a female, he would light up and start bobbing like a mad man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubbles</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</guid>
      <description>Bubbles is a massive female. At the one year mark, she already weighs 90 grams when receptive. She came from our Jude x Alla pairing and is one of the few females we decided to keep. She&amp;rsquo;s like a giant version of Alla. Healthy, hungry and bold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleu</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/15/bleu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/15/bleu/</guid>
      <description>Bleu is a male we picked up from the Stryfe line. He was raised by Jeremy Booker at Brightside Chameleons, and he was a bit of a challenge to work with. We released him in early 2020 and only produced a few clutches with him. We hope to select some nice males from his offspring to bring that line into our project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Button</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/14/button/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/14/button/</guid>
      <description>Button was a female with nice high contrast barring from Jude x Alla. We bred her a few times before letting her go to make space for fresh genetics, but she was a phenomenal breeder for us! It will be interesting to see how much the high contrast carries into her offspring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunny</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/10/sunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/10/sunny/</guid>
      <description>Sunny was my second favorite female from the Jude x Kako clutch, hatched 6/5/19. She reminds me a lot of her mother, Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. With any luck we will be able to grap a killer yellow body blue bar male from her and Zanaka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patch</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/08/patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/08/patch/</guid>
      <description>Patch was my favorite female from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her line is an extremely strong yellow body blue bar Ambilobe group, so I have high hopes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kako</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</guid>
      <description>Kako was one of the two females we paired with our second generation breeder - Jude. We purchased her from RB Barto, but she was produced by Bobby Ruddock. Her line is one of our favorite yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe lines in the USA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judy</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</guid>
      <description>Judy was our first generation breeder from Candy Cane (F1) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. She laid one good clutch for us but died during laying complications after 2 more infertile clutches.
  Judy (1)
      Judy (2)
      Judy (3)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</guid>
      <description>Flash was our first generation breeder from Cowboy (CH) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. He had a very gentle personality and only gave us one healthy clutch with Judy, from which we kept Jude. We were still learning when we got Flash and he passed after consuming a large number of wild bugs when pesticides had been applied to the lawn behind ours.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
