<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Taiyang (WC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/10/03/taiyang/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/10/03/taiyang/</guid>
      <description>Imported by One World Exotica in October 2023.&#xA;WC Taiyang and WC Haiyang are two of my favorite wild caught imports; Taiyang means sun in Chinese because he has a ton of yellow w/ a little mix of orange like the sun, and Haiyang means sea/ocean in Chinese. Haiyang&amp;rsquo;s blue bars are really something for a WC, so we have the sun (Taiyang) and the sea (Haiyang). They both came in great condition, and I hope to be working with them for years to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiyang (WC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/10/02/haiyang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/10/02/haiyang/</guid>
      <description>Imported by One World Exotica in October 2023.&#xA;WC Haiyang came in with some face injuries which make him less likely to get the glam shots on social media; however, we are incredibly happy with him from a genetics and breeding standpoint. His blue bars are the best of all of our WC imports from One World Exotica and his body is very nice as well - green/yellow and only some very sparce red/orange markings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reptile Show Reporter: Jon Hill from iPardalis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/09/23/rsr_jonhill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/09/23/rsr_jonhill/</guid>
      <description>A great discussion with Sean McNeeley where we cover:&#xA;my history in the hobby individually raising Panther Chameleons the impact of husbandry on polygenic traits show strategies to grow the industry and improve outcomes for customers </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WC Bibi x Mamony</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/07/06/bibi-mamony/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/07/06/bibi-mamony/</guid>
      <description>This pairing is a great F1 group with WC Bibi paired to our 4th gen female named Mamony from Blossom x Maitso. Our hope is that the strong blues on the female side of this lineage will help clean up the mixed bar look of WC Bibi and he&amp;rsquo;ll bring some size and fresh genetics into the mix. WC Bibi&amp;rsquo;s yellows are very interesting and slightly different from Blossom&amp;rsquo;s, so it will also be interesting to watch these animals as they mature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parasites and Ethics - Coccidia Found in Furcifer pardalis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/07/04/parasites_coccidia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/07/04/parasites_coccidia/</guid>
      <description>Executive Summary Coccidia Basics Structure Life Cycle Known Species Isospora brygooi Choleoeimeria glawi Eimeria vencesi Discussion Reference TL;DR&#xA;This article examines three of species of Coccidia which are known to infect Furcifer pardalis and poses a theory that Choleoeimeria glawi (Figure 3) are more likely to cause serious illness based on extant literature and our experience. More clinical research is warranted because we are not specialists in parasitology or veterinary microbiology, and we did not attempt to bifurcate our clinical results by Coccidia species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WC Dia x Vaosary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/29/dia-vaosary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/29/dia-vaosary/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was the only successful clutch with WC Dia. We paired him to our 5th gen female named Vaosary from Papafee x Lokana. Vaosary was a stand out female with a lot of orange from one of my favorite 5th gen groups. Because of how rare this line will be, they are a great option for breeders looking for high-quality foundation animals at the F1 generation. Really love that we got some WC Dia and Papafee clones in the mix here - very cool stuff!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimanga x Bumblebee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/28/jimanga-bumblebee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/28/jimanga-bumblebee/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our 5th gen male named Jimanga from Manga x Imelda, and a 5th gen female named Bumble Bee from Papafee x Lokana. This is the combination of two of our favorite lines and the culmination of years of selective breeding for yellow body blue bar traits. If they don&amp;rsquo;t prove out, we have no one to blame but ourselves! ;)&#xA;Hatch dates 6/28/23 - 7/10/23 Hatch rate 23/26 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Chronicles: Ethics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/23/cc_egg_sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/23/cc_egg_sales/</guid>
      <description>Great discussion with Amanda &amp;amp; Lee Ready of Ready&amp;rsquo;s Rainforest, The Reptile Gumbo Podcast, and Dr. Rob Coke DVM about egg sales and other random ideas that popped into our heads.&#xA;We planned on discussing&#xA;Ethics The impact of egg sales on the community Why we chose not to sell eggs This was a great show with 2 chameleon breeders and a top reptile veterinarian.&#xA;Podcast link: Chameleon Chronicles: Ethics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ethics of Egg Sales</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/07/egg_sales_101/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/07/egg_sales_101/</guid>
      <description>We have taken a strong public stance against the sale of panther chameleon eggs. This post will summarize our points and provide a single source of information on our work on this topic. If you have seen us on Facebook or another forum fighting the good fight, this is why.&#xA;Panther Chameleons are not easy reptiles to keep in captivity. They are an arboreal species with specific conditions which require constant maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Academy: Chameleon Breeder Husbandry vs Keeper Husbandry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/05/05/ca_keepervsbreeder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/05/05/ca_keepervsbreeder/</guid>
      <description>This is a discussion about whether breeders should get a pass for poor husbandry. We know that the practical constraints of breeding animals for a profit yields a compromising attitude towards husbandry. I believe it should be uncompromising, and I am happy to hold myself to the same standards as my customers. Bill is a leader in this movement and I hope we can encourage more breeders to commit to higher standards of care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mighty Morphing Reptiles: The Ethics of Selling Chameleon Eggs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/04/09/mm_shortcuttotrama/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/04/09/mm_shortcuttotrama/</guid>
      <description>Ryan and Mitch are two breeders who I have a long history with. We met on social media when I got started in the hobby in 2015-2016. We have had late-night discussions on all sorts of drama, challenges, and much needed breeder therapy sessions. Mitch was a major sponsor of the panther chameleon local form genetic test. He creates some crazy cool cross-locale and pure locale panther chameleons, and Ryan started a podcast recently but I knew him from his Cap Est project - which is to-date the best I have seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiborin x Maize</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/03/10/kiborin-maize/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/03/10/kiborin-maize/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our male named Kiborin from Blossom x Maitso, and a female we picked up from Brian Stewart, Maize. Maize seems to be throwing everything from a beautiful orange body blue bar to a yellow body blue bar while Kiborin was one of our favorite yellow body blue bars from Blossom. This group has been very vibrant and a few males have had the ability to fire up to to point where their blue bars almost go white!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animals at Home: Selling Chameleon Eggs &amp; Other Unethical Breeding Practices</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/02/12/animalsathome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/02/12/animalsathome/</guid>
      <description>This is a great discussion about our project from an ethical perspective. Dillon over at Animals at Home has created some of the best content on ethical keeping. We were honored to speak with him after he fired an ethical shot across the bow of herpetoculture.&#xA;Care of the animal comes first - business comes second Over production and a breeder&amp;rsquo;s responsibility to market their work Egg sales Group raising vs individual-raising Breeding vs flipping Genetics - polygenic traits and selective breeding Wild caught and importation Parasites and captive health management strategies </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zor</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/24/zor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/24/zor/</guid>
      <description>Zor is a great YBBB we produced with our Kammerflage male from Gold Rush named Zozoro. We paired him to our gorgeous female from Arti x Alla, Artalla. He brings some great baby blue bars and a lime green to yellow body. We only paired him a few times before letting him go to his forever home.&#xA;Zor&#xA;Zor1&#xA;Zor2&#xA;Zor3&#xA;Zor4&#xA;Zor5&#xA;Zor6&#xA;Zor7&#xA;Zor8&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Zozoro Dam Artalla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/23/avana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/23/avana/</guid>
      <description>Avana has some great Kammerflage Kreations lineage from her sire, Zozoro, and her dam, Artalla. All of her brothers had yellow bodies and a few had deep blue bars. It will be a lot of fun to prove her out with Zandrin - hoping for those blue bars!&#xA;Avana&#xA;Avana1&#xA;Avana2&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Zozoro Dam Artalla 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Avana (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Avana (F4-CG14).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zozoro x Artalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/23/zozoro-artalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/23/zozoro-artalla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our only female from Arti x Alla, and our male from Kammerflage Kreations, Zozoro. Zozoro brings some nice yellow and blue. His yellow settled into a lime green at rest and his bars were more baby blue than royal blue. Whereas Arti had some great deep blue bars and bit less yellow in the body. This has a lot of Kammerflage on each side of the lineage and it is unrelated to our main line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ralph x Mainty</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/15/ralph-mainty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/15/ralph-mainty/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our forth generation hold back, Ralph, and our female from Nature&amp;rsquo;s Van Gogh, Mainty. Mainty has a few rainbow brothers and a few RBBB brothers, so it will be fun to see which side she brings here. We paired Mainty with Kosmo after she had an infertile clutch after Ralph. We will probably not keep any of these wonderful animals because of our long-term plans for Mainty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zandrin x Mara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/12/21/zandrin-mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/12/21/zandrin-mara/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female Mara from Chi-town Chameleons, and our 4th gen male, Zandrin. Zandrin was our favorite YBBB from Nugget and Mara brings the WC Legion line into our project via Nova. If we can get a HB that looks remotely similar to Zandrin x Nova, we will be super excited about this line :)&#xA;Hatch dates 12/04/22 - 12/21/2022 Hatch rate 32/40 F1&#xA;F10&#xA;F11</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Noko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/29/manjaka-noko/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/29/manjaka-noko/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female from Nugget x Loko, and our male from Colorado Chameleons, F1 Manjaka. Manjaka was pretty unassuming as a juvenile, but he became one of our favorite YBBB Ambilobe breeders as an adult. He had an extra blue bar, and yellows were classic Ambilobe. Loko came to us from Chromatic Chameleons and Nugget is our favorite 3rd gen YBBB breeder.&#xA;Hatch dates 11/19/22 - 11/29/22 Hatch rate 24/24 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parasites and Ethics: Ethics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/19/parasites_ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/19/parasites_ethics/</guid>
      <description>We believe that sharing information about our experience with parasites will not only help our customers keep their animals healthy, but it could help build awareness and promote preventative actions throughout the industry. Our hope is that it will accomplish that goal and build stronger relationships with our customers. Eventually, it will result in long-term project sustainability and a stronger community of hobbyists.&#xA;Most people would not publish this story about parasites on their business page because most people are concerned about short-term revenue and less concerned about their integrity and animal welfare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Tigerlilly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/07/manjaka-tigerlilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/11/07/manjaka-tigerlilly/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female from Nugget x Amara, and our male from Colorado Chameleons, F1 Manjaka. Manjaka was pretty unassuming as a juvenile, but he became one of our favorite YBBB Ambilobe breeders as an adult. He had an extra blue bar, and yellows were classic Ambilobe. Amara came to us from Brian Stewart and her lineage is more rainbow Ambilobe.&#xA;Hatch dates 11/03/22 - 11/07/2022 Hatch rate 23/23 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selectively Breeding Furcifer Pardalis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/10/14/2022-10-14-selectively-breeding-furcifer-pardalis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/10/14/2022-10-14-selectively-breeding-furcifer-pardalis/</guid>
      <description>The best Panther Chameleon breeders have a deep understanding of their genetics, inheritance patterns and can help you get what you want. This knowledge plays into the ethics of selling Panther Chameleons because there is a lot of false advertising in the industry which is very surface-level without much understanding of the species. This is our answer to the filtered images and click-bait on Instagram and TikTok.&#xA;Introduction Given that Panther Chameleon (Furcifer pardalis) colors are polygenic traits, and Panther Chameleons are a sexually dimorphic species, selective breeding for a given color is challenging and many breeders fail to achieve a consistent result.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Academy: The Chameleon Hour, Oct 7, 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/10/07/chamhour20221007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/10/07/chamhour20221007/</guid>
      <description>This episode kicks off with a discussion about chameleon safe plants, Michael Nash on diapause, and finishes up with a discussion between Bill and I about creating a safe environment for chameleon hatchlings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teny</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/10/teny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/10/teny/</guid>
      <description>Teny is a beautiful female Ambilobe panther chameleon who we produced with Tony and Paige. Her sire had nice deep blue bars like his dam sire, Artemis with a clean yellow body like Nugget. Her dam brings a great Tropical Chameleons x Modern Day Dragons YBBB lineage from Tiffany Mallay.&#xA;Teny&#xA;Teny1&#xA;Teny2&#xA;Filial F5-CG14 Sire Tony Dam Paige 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Teny (F5-CG14) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony x Paige</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/10/tony-paige/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/10/tony-paige/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our our 4th gen HB from Nugget x Amara, Tony, and our female from Tiffany Mallay, Paige. Paige has great potential from Ambilobe lines from Tropical Chameleons and Modern Day Dragons, and Tony is the spitting image of his dam sire, Artemis, with a little extra yellow from Nugget. These guys hatched out strong and we&amp;rsquo;re hoping to do an encore pairing with Zandrin next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zava x Nuhana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/25/zava-nuhana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/25/zava-nuhana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our F1 female from Nugget x CH Bohana, and our male from Kammerflage Kreations, Zava. Zava was a vibrant rainbow Ambilobe. His yellow sat on top of a bright red dermal layer, and his bars were deep royal blue. F1 Nuhana brings fresh genetics and a chance at Nugget&amp;rsquo;s neon yellow body with blue bars.&#xA;Hatch dates 7/18/22 - 8/25/2022 Hatch rate 17/25 F1&#xA;M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zava x Manjaya</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/21/zava-manjaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/21/zava-manjaya/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our F1 female from WC Arlo x Perregrin/Pyro&amp;rsquo;s daughter, and our male from Kammerflage Kreations, Zava. Zava was a vibrant rainbow Ambilobe. His yellow sat on top of a bright red dermal layer, and his bars were deep royal blue. F1 Manjaya brings fresh genetics and a chance at that Perregrin/Sparkles yellow.&#xA;Hatch dates 7/27/22 - 8/21/2022 Hatch rate 8/14 F1&#xA;F2&#xA;F3&#xA;M1&#xA;M2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parasi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/20/parasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/20/parasi/</guid>
      <description>Parasi is a great Ambilobe female from our F1 sire from Colorado Chameleon named Manjaka and our female from Jack and Mavokely. Many of her brothers had great yellow bodies and blue bars - a few had mixed red/blue bars. We are very excited to see what she does with WC Tratra!&#xA;Parasi&#xA;Parasi1&#xA;Filial F2-CG14 Sire Manjaka Dam Parasy 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Parasi (F2-CG14) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Manjalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/19/arti-manjalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/19/arti-manjalla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between one of our F1 females from Colorado Chameleon, Manjalla, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. They both come from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations. The clutch was small and Manjalla was very weak, so we were only able to keep one baby alive from this group.&#xA;Hatch dates 8/19/2022 - 8/20/2022 Hatch rate 2/17 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackson x Imelda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/16/jackson-imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/08/16/jackson-imelda/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Jackson, and our female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Imelda. Imelda is a great mix of WC Gambit lines and Kammerflage Kreations yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe while Jackson is the most vibrant male from our Jack x Mavokely clutch. We will definitely keep this line in our project in the years to come!&#xA;Hatch dates 7/14/2022 - 8/16/2022 Hatch rate 29/38 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kintana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/31/kintana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/31/kintana/</guid>
      <description>Kintana is a line-bred YBBB from Chromatic Chameleons from Capella and Kromatisk. Capella is one of our favorite sires they have produced over the past few years, and Kromatisk is easily one of our favorites over the past decade. We have a decent amount of Felipe Sanchez and JJ/Kromatisk in our existing lines, so we will do our best to avoid those as long as we can. Otherwise, she should bring some more solid genetics from one of the best Ambilobe projects in the USA over at Chromatic Chameleons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mena</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/27/mena/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/27/mena/</guid>
      <description>Mena is our HB from Zava and F1 Manjaya. Zava had a significant amount of red and a few of Mena&amp;rsquo;s brothers got it, too. Manjaya seems to have taken after her WC sire, Arlo. A few of Mena&amp;rsquo;s brothers looked like mini Arlo&amp;rsquo;s. So less of the Perregrin/Pyro side of the lineage, more of the WC Arlo combined with Zava is what she brings to the table.&#xA;Mena</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Parasy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/26/manjaka-parasy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/26/manjaka-parasy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our female from Jack x Mavokely, and our male from Colorado Chameleons, F1 Manjaka. Manjaka was pretty unassuming as a juvenile, but he became one of our favorite YBBB Ambilobe breeders as an adult. He had an extra blue bar, and yellows were classic Ambilobe. Mavokely came to us from Bobby Ruddock and she brings some of my favorite YBBB Ambilobe genetics - Amarillo.&#xA;Hatch dates 7/26/22 - 8/20/2022 Hatch rate 8/18 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Furcifer pardalis Body Color Inheritance Theory</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/23/2022-07-23-body-color-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/23/2022-07-23-body-color-theory/</guid>
      <description>This article describes how Panther Chameleons inherit their color over multiple generations. There are many myths in the industry related to what you can get from various Panther Chameleon pairings, and these misconceptions result in pricing issues and scams.&#xA;TLDR; Most individuals have multiple body colors because the complete absence of a color is extremely rare. If a color is found in that locale, you usually can find at least some of it somewhere on every individual’s body from that locale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi (WC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/29/bibi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/29/bibi/</guid>
      <description>Imported by One World Exotica in June 2022.&#xA;Bibi is a very vibrant wild caught (WC) Ambilobe panther chameleon. Bibidia translates to wild in Malagasy, which is why we named our two WC Bibi and Dia. Bibi has a decent amount of red on his face and blue bars with a vibrant green/yellow body. The yellow covers both his body and bars, so his bars almost look green at times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miafina (WC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/29/miafina/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/29/miafina/</guid>
      <description>Imported by One World Exotica in June 2022.&#xA;Miafina is a wild caught (WC) Ambilobe Panther Chameleon. Miafina is derived from the Malagasy word for &amp;ldquo;mystery&amp;rdquo; because her phenotype is a complete mystery. We are very excited to prove her out with our WC Tratra who is an Ambilobe male without very much, if any, red highlighting. When we watch her sons develop, we&amp;rsquo;ll get an estimate for what she brings to the table besides fresh WC genetics!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tratra (WC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/29/tratra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/29/tratra/</guid>
      <description>Imported by One World Exotica&#xA;Tratra is a classic wild caught (WC) Ambilobe panther chameleon. Tratra translates to &amp;ldquo;caught&amp;rdquo; in Malagasy, which complements our other two WC Bibi and WC Dia because bibidia translates to &amp;ldquo;wild&amp;rdquo; in Malagasy. After we failed to fully acclimate Dia, we decided to try again with Tratra. He has beautiful baby blue bars like our first CB holdback, Jude, and a nice consistent green body color.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dia (WC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/28/dia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/28/dia/</guid>
      <description>Imported by One World Exotica in June 2022.&#xA;Dia was our favorite WC import, between him and Bibi. He had a clean yellow body and his bars showed more blue as he settled in; however, he did not fully acclimate and we only got a few clutches from him. We did find him some top notch females from our line, so hopefully those great traits get worked into the gene pool!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka x Lokana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/05/manjaka-lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/05/manjaka-lokana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our F1 sire from Colorado Chameleons, Manjaka, and our female from Chromatic Chameleons, Lokana. Lokana is a mix of Chromatic and Kammerflage Kreations yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe while Manjaka is a wonderful YBBB from a recent import, WC Arlo. The outcomes have been extremely consiste YBBB thus far which are not directly related to our main line of Ambilobe. They are a great option for people looking for high quality pairings with our multi-generational lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranoka</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/05/ranoka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/05/ranoka/</guid>
      <description>Ranoka is a really interesting mix of F1 Manjaka and Kromatisk, Lokana&amp;rsquo;s sire. He has the radiant yellow that Manjaka has, but he also has the red embers at the edge of the yellow like Kromatisk - this almost looks orange at times and gives it an almost 3D look against a blue background. Really unique animal!&#xA;Ranoka&#xA;Ranoka1&#xA;Ranoka2&#xA;Ranoka3&#xA;Ranoka4&#xA;Ranoka5&#xA;Ranoka6&#xA;Ranoka7&#xA;Ranoka8&#xA;Filial F2-CG14 Sire Manjaka Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tsara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/01/tsara/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/01/tsara/</guid>
      <description>Tsara Tarehy means attractive in Malagasy. We named the two sisters from Manjaka x Lokana Tsara and Tarehy :). Check out that clutch to see how consistent their YBBB phenotypes were. It is a very good proxy for what these two sisters bring to the table: great yellows and bars that shift from Landy to Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s blues. Very good complement to our existing lines!&#xA;Tsara&#xA;Tsara1&#xA;Tsara2&#xA;Filial F2-CG14 Sire Manjaka Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarehy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/31/tarehy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/31/tarehy/</guid>
      <description>Tsara Tarehy means attractive in Malagasy. We named the two sisters from Manjaka x Lokana Tsara and Tarehy :). Check out that clutch to see how consistent their YBBB phenotypes were. It is a very good proxy for what these two sisters bring to the table: great yellows and bars that shift from Landy to Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s blues. Very good complement to our existing lines!&#xA;Tarehy&#xA;Tarehy1&#xA;Tarehy2&#xA;Filial F2-CG14 Sire Manjaka Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mami</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/11/mami/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/11/mami/</guid>
      <description>Mami is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has more purples and pinks like her mother, Lokana, whereas her two sisters Vaosary and Bumble Bee remind me of their aunts, Papafee&amp;rsquo;s sisters. Her first pairing is with our new WC Ambilobe, so we expect her to produce some absolutely amazing F1 YBBB Ambilobe for us!&#xA;Mami&#xA;Mami1&#xA;Mami2&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robina</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/07/robina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/07/robina/</guid>
      <description>Robina is a female we acquired from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics Clapton x Layla pairing. Her sire, Clapton, and dam sire, DynamiteTNT, both have phenomenal blue bars which I believe will complement Ralph&amp;rsquo;s really well. With any luck, a few Ralph clones could pop out because Robina is an RBBB x RBBB female. She has some interesting turquoise and subtle differences from most of my other females. She is awesome!&#xA;Robina</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lizard Brain Radio: Episode 31</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/06/lizardbrain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/06/lizardbrain/</guid>
      <description>This podcast is a great introduction to our breeding program and philosophy.&#xA;How we got started individually raising panther chameleons Why we chose to focus on Yellow Body Blue Bar (YBBB) Ambilobe Challenges related to individually raising Selective breeding strategies How we track and document things with Gramps software Our strategy of transparency - we show hundreds of males from a given pairing and don&amp;rsquo;t cherry pick the best ones. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papamavo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/01/papamavo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/01/papamavo/</guid>
      <description>Papamavo is one of our 5th generation Ambilobe Panther Chameleon breeders from Papafee x Lokana. He has great vibrancy and a solid yellow body. His attitude is a bit more feisty than his father, but he&amp;rsquo;s calming down a bit now as he reaches adulthood. We are excited to see what he does for us!&#xA;Papamavo&#xA;Papamavo1&#xA;Papamavo2&#xA;Papamavo3&#xA;Papamavo4&#xA;Papamavo5&#xA;Papamavo6&#xA;Papamavo7&#xA;Papamavo8&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Academy: Hatchling Care Panel Q &amp; A</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/19/ca_hatchlings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/19/ca_hatchlings/</guid>
      <description>This is a great discussion with three men who have more experience than I do: Bill Strand, Sean McNeeley and Chris Young. These guys are some of the OGs of chameleon husbandry, and I really enjoyed listening as much as I enjoyed the opportunity to share my experience.&#xA;Sorry about the bad entry - I had not done many podcasts at this point lol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Academy: Should You Buy a Chameleon Egg? Part 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/17/chameleonacademyeggsalespart2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/17/chameleonacademyeggsalespart2/</guid>
      <description>Bill Strand was my original mentor in the hobby. He has more experience than anyone I know. He is accessible, fair and reliable. There is no other source of information on chameleon husbandry that I trust more.&#xA;In this episode, we get into a topic that is something I am very passionate about - egg sales. When I heard the framing of this question on Bill&amp;rsquo;s podcast, I sent him a long message and he was kind enough to give me a chance to speak my mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artilly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/03/artilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/03/artilly/</guid>
      <description>Artilly is a great YBBB from our Arti x Lilly pairing. Arti is one of our favorite ybbb breeders who we mixed in at the 3rd gen and Lilly is a female from our Jude x Kako group. We did not get too many examples from the small clutch that produced her, so it will be a lot of fun to prove her out!&#xA;Artilly&#xA;Artilly1&#xA;Artilly2&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Arti Dam Lilly 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squash</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/14/squash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/14/squash/</guid>
      <description>Squash is a great YBBB Ambilobe female from our good friend Brian Stewart. McNulty is a male from one of Brian&amp;rsquo;s old projects from the Stryfe line and he paired him up with a female from one of his recent pairings with Artemis from Colorado Chameleons. These should be a lot of fun to prove out because they have three ybbb sires in the closest lineage. Top notch stuff as always!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maize</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/13/maize/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/13/maize/</guid>
      <description>Maize is a great YBBB Ambilobe female from our good friend Brian Stewart. McNulty is a male from one of Brian&amp;rsquo;s old projects from the Stryfe line and he paired him up with a female from one of his recent pairings with Artemis from Colorado Chameleons. These should be a lot of fun to prove out because they have three ybbb sires in the closest lineage. Top notch stuff as always!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beans</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/12/beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/12/beans/</guid>
      <description>Beans is a great YBBB Ambilobe female from our good friend Brian Stewart. McNulty is a male from one of Brian&amp;rsquo;s old projects from the Stryfe line and he paired him up with a female from one of his recent pairings with Artemis from Colorado Chameleons. These should be a lot of fun to prove out because they have three ybbb sires in the closest lineage. Top notch stuff as always!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaosary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/12/vaosary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/12/vaosary/</guid>
      <description>Vaosary is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has a rusty coloration with even more orange than her sister Bumble Bee. Her first pairing is with our new WC Ambilobe, so we expect her to produce some absolutely amazing F1 YBBB Ambilobe for us!&#xA;Vaosary&#xA;Vaosary1&#xA;Vaosary2&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Vaosary (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bumble Bee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/11/bumblebee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/11/bumblebee/</guid>
      <description>Bumble Bee is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has a great personality and a rusty coloration with lots of orange and light purple dots. We expect her to produce some absolutely amazing Ambilobe for us!&#xA;Bumblebee&#xA;Bumblebee1&#xA;Bumblebee2&#xA;Bumblebee3&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Bumble Bee (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Bumble Bee (F4-CG14). Bumble Bee was born on 2022-01-11 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papafee x Lokana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/11/papafee-lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/11/papafee-lokana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Papafee, and our Ambilobe female from Chromatic Chameleons, Lokana. Lokana is from a great pairing between Kromatisk and Shirley. Kromatisk is one of my favorite Ambilobe breeders in the USA and Shirley is from one of my favorite ybbb combinations from Kammerflage Kreations. Papafee is the HB male from our Zanaka x Sunny clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the fourth generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Academy: Genetic Testing for Panther Chameleon Locale</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/07/ca_genetictest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/07/ca_genetictest/</guid>
      <description>This episode explains the origins of the genetic test for panther chameleon locale. It features Benson Morrill, PhD of Rare Genetics, Inc. and myself.&#xA;What we know about local forms Challenges that a genetic test would provide better information on Pricing and project stage Data underpinning the test Testing strategy </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Funded Genetic Test for Furcifer pardalis Haplogroup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/31/2021-12-31-locale-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/31/2021-12-31-locale-test/</guid>
      <description>Panther Chameleons (Furcifer pardalis) display an amazing variety of colors within distinct locales that are physically separated by mountains, oceans, rivers and mangrove forests. The Panther Chameleon hobby has never had a reliable way to test animals for locale origin, and we have had to rely on import labels, guessing locale based off of male phenotypes, or what the breeder one gen upstream said. However, females do not display their phenotype and have always been “proven out” by breeding with a male from an assumed locale and observing their offspring to determine if they look like we would expect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pepita</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/07/pepita/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/07/pepita/</guid>
      <description>Pepita is a great 5th gen YBBB from our Papafee x Coco pairing. She only had 3 brothers, and at least one looked a lot like the Landy side of Coco&amp;rsquo;s lineage. Therefore, my expectation is that Pepita will throw Papafee or Landy looks. It will be a lot of fun to see what she does for us. She definitely resembles Coco more than Papafee&amp;rsquo;s dam, Sunny.&#xA;Pepita&#xA;Pepita1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papafee x Coco</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/04/papafee-coco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/04/papafee-coco/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Papafee, and our little Ambilobe female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Coco. Coco is from a great pairing between Hendrix and Foxey. Hendrix brings a new WC Ambilobe line into the project and Foxey is from one of my favorite ybbb combinations from Kammerflage Kreations. Papafee is the HB male from our Zanaka x Sunny clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the fourth generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimanga</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/jimanga/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/jimanga/</guid>
      <description>Jimanga is one of our 5th gen Ambilobe breeders. He comes from our Manga x Imelda pairing, a great collab with Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics. I can trace his personality all the way back to Kako. They teach you that chameleons are a look-but-don&amp;rsquo;t-touch pet, the hard way haha&amp;hellip; but what comes with that is an absolutely amazing defense display. Definitely something I really enjoy about these guys!&#xA;Jimanga&#xA;Jimanga1&#xA;Jimanga2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimelda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/jimelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/jimelda/</guid>
      <description>Jimelda is Jimanga&amp;rsquo;s sister from our Manga x Imelda pairing. She has some wonderful purples and a fiesty attitude! Manga was one of our best ybbb of all time, so we are really hoping Jimelda carries some of those traits into an F1 gen with WC Bibi. Those could very well be some of the best in the country if they prove out.&#xA;Jimelda&#xA;Jimelda1&#xA;Jimelda2&#xA;Jimelda3&#xA;Jimelda4&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Manga Dam Imelda 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manga x Imelda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/manga-imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/manga-imelda/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our fourth generation hold back, Manga, and our female from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics, Imelda. Imelda is a great mix of WC Gambit lines and Kammerflage Kreations yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe while Manga is the male with the most striking yellows from our Bleu x Patch clutch. We kept Jimanga from this group and he has his father&amp;rsquo;s wonderful profile! Just a gorgeous group of Ambilobe.&#xA;Hatch dates 12/03/2021 - 2/19/2022 Hatch rate 15/19 M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Daisy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/17/arti-daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/17/arti-daisy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Daisy, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Daisy is a great female from our Jude x Kako clutch. Some of my favorite yellows came from this pairing and Daisy didn&amp;rsquo;t disappoint ;)&#xA;Arti x Daisy Hatch dates 10/17/2021 - 10/26/2021 Hatch rate 4/26 1st&#xA;Img 0370</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/17/ghost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/17/ghost/</guid>
      <description>Ghost is a 4th gen ybbb Ambilobe breeder here at iPardalis. He is from our Arti and Daisy pairing. His yellows are so light when he fires up that we decided to name him Ghost. They are just so clean and bright! There is also an H bar on his right side. We are very excited to have him carry the torch on this part of our tree.&#xA;Ghost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dehibe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/16/dehibe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/16/dehibe/</guid>
      <description>Dehibe is a great YBBB Ambilobe we produced with Arti and Alla. He brings some great blue bars and a yellow body, very similar to his sire. He and his sister, Artalla, were the only two babies to survive Alla&amp;rsquo;s last clutch, and they are very special to us. This is a great cb combination without any of our main line in it.&#xA;Dehibe&#xA;Dehibe1&#xA;Dehibe2&#xA;Dehibe3&#xA;Dehibe4&#xA;Dehibe5</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/15/artalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/15/artalla/</guid>
      <description>Artalla is a very special HB female from Arti, a great ybbb breeder for us produced by Brian Stewart, and Alla, one of our first females and most prolific breeder who gave us 17 clutches over her long life! Artalla has some big shoes to fill, and we are extremely excited to work with her :)&#xA;Artalla&#xA;Artalla1&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Arti Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Artalla (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Alla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/15/arti-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/15/arti-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our most prolific female from Panther Creek Chameleons, Alla, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Alla is a wonderful female from JJ who was produced by Kammerflage Kreations. We only had a single clutch from these two because it was towards the end of Alla&amp;rsquo;s breeding career.&#xA;Arti x Alla Hatch dates 10/15/2021 - 10/19/2021 Hatch rate 3/20 Dehibe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zozoro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/06/zozoro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/06/zozoro/</guid>
      <description>Zozoro is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage sire Gold Rush. His father is my favorite YBBB produced over the past few years and his mother is the combination of a vibrant YBBB named My Friend and a true F1 from two different WC that the Kammer&amp;rsquo;s acclimated recently. Very excited to work this guy into our 4th/5th generation of Ambilobe!&#xA;Zozoro&#xA;Zozoro1&#xA;Zozoro2&#xA;Zozoro3&#xA;Zozoro4&#xA;Zozoro5&#xA;Filial F3-CG13 Sire Au-Mirongatra (Gold Rush) Dam Ankoso-Bolamena (Goldie) 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x CH Bohana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/09/15/arti-bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/09/15/arti-bohana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our first captive hatched (CH) female, Bohana, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Bohana is a female Ambilobe hatched out by Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics from a wild caught imported female. Bohana&amp;rsquo;s wild genes didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to add much to our project when combined with Arti, so we did not keep any of these animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mainty</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/09/05/mainty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/09/05/mainty/</guid>
      <description>Mainty is one of the nicest RBBB females I could find for Ralph. Her sire, Bangheera, is a classic red body blue bar Ambilobe produced by Highlighter Chameleons and owned by Nature&amp;rsquo;s Van Gogh. After talking to Logan about Mainty&amp;rsquo;s brothers, it looks like many of them proved out to be similar to Grape Inferno or Bangheera, so although Moonclaw&amp;rsquo;s sire is Flamethrower, it seems she took after her dam sire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UVI Impact on Growth of Furcifer pardalis Neonates</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/08/04/2021-08-04-uvi-impact-on-growth-of-furcifer-pardalis-neonates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/08/04/2021-08-04-uvi-impact-on-growth-of-furcifer-pardalis-neonates/</guid>
      <description>We raised two clutches of Furcifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons) under controlled conditions to answer a simple question:&#xA;How do the growth rates of babies raised under UVI 3 and UVI 6 compare?&#xA;Background Michael Nash recently studied two groups of Furcifer lateralis neonates and found that UVI 7 and UVI 3 resulted in no noticeable difference in growth rates for that species. He descibes his research in this post. This was an inspiring example of research in the hobby, and I would love to see more people get involved!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parasites and Ethics: Origin Story</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/18/parasites_origin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/18/parasites_origin/</guid>
      <description>Rye, for good luck.&#xA;We received 5 females from reputable CB sources that had issues during/after quarantine since 2017. The first 2 were in 2017. They never had great appetites and seemed to have respiratory issues. We brought them to the vet and kept them isolated for 60 days; however, the vet did not see anything wrong with them, and after they seemed to be healthy enough, we tried to breed them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Academy: Chameleon Cage Type Decisions Part 1 - Hybrid</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/15/ca_hybrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/15/ca_hybrid/</guid>
      <description>Bill did a great two part series on different caging strategies. We jumped on for the first part because we use a lot of hybrid enclosures here in Maryland. It helps us keep their cage within a healthy humidity range and protects our walls from water damage.&#xA;Podcast Link: Ep 211: Chameleon Cage Type Decisions Part 1 - Hybrid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jiolahy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/14/jiolahy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/14/jiolahy/</guid>
      <description>Jiolahy is a big F1 female from Chameleons 101&amp;rsquo;s The Don (WC). She brings fresh ybbb genetics combined with a great CB ybbb line created by Modern Day Dragons. We are very lucky to have her in our breeding group.&#xA;Jiolahy&#xA;Filial F1-CG5 Sire The Don (WC) Dam Perregrin/Pyro&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Jiolahy (F1-CG5) Generation 1 1. Jiolahy (F1-CG5). Jiolahy was born on 2021-07-14 at Eric Thompson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/13/mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/13/mara/</guid>
      <description>Mara is the beautiful sister of Maro. They are a pair of Ambilobe breeders we acquired from Chi-Town Chameleons from their Sammy x Nova (F1) pairing. It is looking like Maro is taking after Sammy, so it will be interesting to prove out Mara and see who her sons resemble.&#xA;Mara&#xA;Mara1&#xA;Mara2&#xA;Mara3&#xA;Mara4&#xA;Mara5&#xA;Filial F3 Sire Sammy Dam Storm 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Mara (F3) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>maro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/13/maro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/13/maro/</guid>
      <description>Maro (F3) is a great edition to our YBBB project. We have been tracking the WC Legion line ever since we saw Jeremy Booker acquire him years ago. This great Chi-town Chameleons Sammy x Storm pairing finally carries those genetics with nice yellow bodies on both sides!&#xA;Maro&#xA;Maro1&#xA;Maro2&#xA;Maro3&#xA;mtDNA Haplogroup* 3 (Ambilobe East) Filial F3 Sire Sammy Dam Storm *preliminary results&#xA;5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Maro (F3) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parasites and Ethics: Intro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/12/parasites_and_ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/12/parasites_and_ethics/</guid>
      <description>tldr; Every animal you acquire, whether it be captive bred (CB) or wild caught (WC), should receive multiple fecal exams. A positive fecal should be managed in consultation with a qualified vet who has experience working with chameleons. Many different species of parasites do not shed at a constant rate, so a negative fecal is not a gaurantee that the animal is clean. We found Coccidia in 2 out of 25 exams that we performed in June-July 2021, and plan to run fecals on every animal in our possession and share the results/methods here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Tigravavy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/28/arti-tigravavy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/28/arti-tigravavy/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Tigravavy, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Tigravavy is a stunning female from our Jude x Alla clutch. We were very happy with these guys!&#xA;Arti x Tigravavy Hatch dates 6/28/2021 - 7/29/2021 Hatch rate 25/26 F1&#xA;F2&#xA;M1&#xA;M10&#xA;M2&#xA;M3&#xA;M4&#xA;M5&#xA;M6</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blossom x Mavokely</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/20/blossom-mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/20/blossom-mavokely/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Blossom, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Mavokely. Mavokely is from one of our favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe, Amarillo, and Blossom is the HB male from our Jude x Alla clutch. Great combination of colorful ybbb and clean yellows!&#xA;Blossom x Mavokely Hatch dates 6/20/2021 - 6/24/2021 Hatch rate 22/22 F1&#xA;F2&#xA;M2&#xA;M3&#xA;M4&#xA;Hatch dates 8/08/2021 - 8/22/2021 Hatch rate 23/26 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiborin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/20/kiborin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/20/kiborin/</guid>
      <description>Kiborin is our 4th gen HB from Blossom x Maitso. He is Blaitso&amp;rsquo;s brother. These two are just amazing animals and we are excited to see Kiborin&amp;rsquo;s clean yellow with blue. He has less red highlighting that his father and a really clean look!&#xA;Kiborin&#xA;Kiborin1&#xA;Kiborin2&#xA;Kiborin3&#xA;Kiborin4&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Blossom Dam Maitso 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Kiborin (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1. Kiborin (F4-CG13). Kiborin was born on 2021-06-19 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamony</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/20/mamony/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/20/mamony/</guid>
      <description>Mamony is a nice 4th gen female from our Blossom x Maitso. She resembles Blossom&amp;rsquo;s dam, Alla, more than she resembles her own dam, Maitso. I have a theory that those are hints about which side of the tree a female takes after, so check for Blossom-like offspring from Mamony!&#xA;Mamony&#xA;Mamony1&#xA;Mamony2&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Blossom Dam Maitso 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Mamony (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blaitso</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/19/blaitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/19/blaitso/</guid>
      <description>Blaitso is a drop dead gorgeous 4th gen female from our Blossom x Maitso. She has vibrant oranges, a great bar/body contrast and teal cheeks. Her lineage is also amazing so she will be fun to watch! We are lucky to have her in our breeding group.&#xA;Blaitso&#xA;Blaitso1&#xA;Blaitso2&#xA;Blaitso3&#xA;Blaitso4&#xA;Blaitso5&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Blossom Dam Maitso 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Blaitso (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ralph</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/05/ralph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/05/ralph/</guid>
      <description>Ralph is a great 4th generation continuation of the Alfred line with vibrant blues and reds! Alfred was an odd ball from our Jude x Alla pairing, so these red-heavy Ambilobe are not closely related to many of the other red Ambilobe out there. We plan to keep him paired to one or two females and only do a few clutches with this fun side project.&#xA;Ralph&#xA;Ralph1&#xA;Ralph2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zandrin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/04/zandrin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/04/zandrin/</guid>
      <description>Zandrin is our 4th gen HB from Nugget x Loko. He has amazing yellows with blue bars and some vibrant red highlights on his turrets and spine. He is a phenomenal Ambilobe Panther Chameleon.&#xA;Zandrin&#xA;Zandrin1&#xA;Zandrin2&#xA;Zandrin3&#xA;Zandrin4&#xA;Zandrin5&#xA;Zandrin6&#xA;Zandrin7&#xA;Zandrin8&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Nugget Dam Loko 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Zandrin (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Zandrin (F4-CG14). Zandrin was born on 2021-06-04 at iPardalis. He is the son of Nugget (F3-CG4) and Loko (F5-CG13).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/03/noko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/03/noko/</guid>
      <description>Noko is our HB female from Nugget and Loko. Her brother is Zandrin. She should throw some intense yellow and blue with some interesting red highlighting. Her personality is very calm and photogenic. It was incredibly easy to get some nice profile pictures of her!&#xA;Noko&#xA;Noko1&#xA;Noko2&#xA;Noko3&#xA;Noko4&#xA;Noko5&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Nugget Dam Loko 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Noko (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Noko (F4-CG14).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Loko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/03/nugget-loko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/03/nugget-loko/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our gorgeous Ambilobe female from Chromatic Chameleons, Loko. Loko is from a great pairing between Kromatisk and Wet Dream - a ybbb x ybbb Ambilobe combination. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination with our favorite third gen yellow male with an extremely high quality yellow female!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Amara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/nugget-amara/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/nugget-amara/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our female from Brian Stewart, Amara. Amara proved out to carry a lot of her sire&amp;rsquo;s, Artemis&amp;rsquo;, traits like his dark blue bars and red highlighting. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination of colorful ybbb with both blue bars and clean yellows!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tigerlilly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/tigerlilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/tigerlilly/</guid>
      <description>Tiger Lilly is one of the most stunning females I have seen in person. She has an amazing bar/body contrast, organge highlights in her face and turrets and an orang glow on her arms and tail. We are very lucky to get to work with her. Hopefully, those traits are a sign that she is as cool as her sire, Nugget.&#xA;Tigerlilly&#xA;Tigerlilly1&#xA;Tigerlilly2&#xA;Tigerlilly3&#xA;Tigerlilly4&#xA;Tigerlilly5&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Nugget Dam Amara 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tony</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/tony/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/01/tony/</guid>
      <description>Tony one of our 4th generation YBBB Ambilobe. He has some great traits from his dam, Amara, like his deep blue bars and red highlights, but he also has some vibrant yellows from his sire, Nugget. His profile is one of my favorites with striking turret and gular lines. We are very lucky to have him in our breeding group!&#xA;Tony&#xA;Tony1&#xA;Tony2&#xA;Tony3&#xA;Tony4&#xA;Tony5&#xA;Tony6&#xA;Tony7&#xA;Tony8</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kosma</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/05/02/kosma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/05/02/kosma/</guid>
      <description>Kosma is Kosmo&amp;rsquo;s sister. Kosmo is one of my favorite RBBB Ambilobe produced over the past few years. He was sold as an egg by Eric Thompson, purchased as a juvenile by LA Chams and then we acquired him and his sister, Kosma, so we could have a solid RBBB Ambilobe project with two unrelated lines. However, because of their many homes, their lineage information was not very well maintained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kosmo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/05/01/kosmo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/05/01/kosmo/</guid>
      <description>Kosmo is one of my favorite RBBB Ambilobe produced over the past few years. He was sold as an egg by Eric Thompson, purchased as a juvenile by LA Chams and then we acquired him so we could have a solid RBBB Ambilobe project with two unrelated lines. However, because of his many homes, his lineage information was not very well maintained. We know he was from Skyline and another Eric Thompson female, so I do not recommend pairing his offspring with anything from Chameleons101.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>paige</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/17/paige/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/17/paige/</guid>
      <description>Paige is a solid Modern Day Dragons x Tropical Chameleons YBBB female. She has great purples and pinks and a wonderful personality. We are very lucky to have her in our project and comes to us from Tiffany Mallay. Her first pairing will be with our 4th gen sire, Tony.&#xA;Paige&#xA;Paige1&#xA;Paige2&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire PJ Dam Sonny&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Paige (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alfred x Kanto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/13/alfred-kanto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/13/alfred-kanto/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Alfred, and our female from Frank Payne, Kanto, from Living Art by Frank Payne. Kanto comes from some great OBBB/RBBB lines from Canvas Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Alfred is the male with the most red from our Jude x Alla clutch. We kept Ralph from this group and he is a wonderful RBBB!&#xA;Alfred x Kanto Hatch dates 4/13/2021 - 5/04/2021 Hatch rate 22/24 No pictures available</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x CH Bohana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/11/nugget-bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/11/nugget-bohana/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our captive-hatched Ambilobe female from Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics, Bohana. Bohana was hatched from a wild caught female&amp;rsquo;s clutch of eggs and she seems to have a complex set of colors without a dominant phenotype. Nugget is the HB male from our Jude x Kako clutch. His yellows are my favorite from the third generation. This was a great combination of wild Ambilobe genetics and clean yellows!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lelafo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/02/lelafo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/04/02/lelafo/</guid>
      <description>Lelafo is a very different Ambilobe variety that we acquire specifically to keep the fun rolling with the Alfred line! Her Sire, Vulcan, was produced by Chameleons by Design with two very orange WC males and acquired by New England Chameleons who paired him with an amazing female from their orange boy, Odin. She has a ton of orange and red on both sides. Can&amp;rsquo;t wait to prove her out!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>zava</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/03/21/zava/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/03/21/zava/</guid>
      <description>Zava is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage Kreations Green Giant x Promise Keeper pairing, produced by Ed Kammer. He brings some great deep blue bars and a yellow body with a significant amount of red highlighting. We were really hoping he&amp;rsquo;d have less red and more yellow, so we only did a few clutches with him.&#xA;Zava&#xA;Zava1&#xA;Zava2&#xA;Zava3&#xA;Zava4&#xA;Zava5&#xA;Zava6&#xA;Filial F3-CG13 Sire Itso-triombe (Green Giant) Dam Jiona (June) 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Daisy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/03/08/zanaka-daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/03/08/zanaka-daisy/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project.&#xA;Zanaka x Daisy F3-CG5&#xA;Hatch dates 3/8/2021 - 3/20/2021 Hatch rate 21/26 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blossom x Maitso</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/27/blossom-maitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/27/blossom-maitso/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Blossom, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Maitso. Maitso is from one of our favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe, Amarillo, and Blossom is the HB male from our Jude x Alla clutch. Great combination of colorful ybbb and clean yellows! Kiborin is our keeper from this group.&#xA;Blossom x Maitso Hatch dates 1/27/2021 - 3/07/2021 Hatch rate 25/27 1st&#xA;10th</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>parasy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/21/parasy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/21/parasy/</guid>
      <description>Parasy is Jackson&amp;rsquo;s sister. She has great YBBB potential from our 4th generation of Ambilobe. We will have to prove her out to see which side of the tree she takes after, but her lineage is phenomenal on both sides. Her dam sire is one of our favorites from Bobby Rodduck, and Jack was one of the best YBBB from our Jude x Alla pairing.&#xA;Parasy&#xA;Parasy1&#xA;Parasy2&#xA;Parasy3</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack x Mavokely</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/20/jack-mavokely/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Jack, and our female from Bobby Ruddock, Mavokely. Jack had some of the nicest yellows from Jude x Alla and Bobby&amp;rsquo;s boy Amarillo is one of my favorite ybbb of all time. These guys should be very special.&#xA;Jack x Mavokely Hatch dates 1/20/2021 - 3/17/2021 Hatch rate 3/21 M1&#xA;Hb&#xA;Hb1&#xA;Jackson1&#xA;Jackson4</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>jackson</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/20/jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/20/jackson/</guid>
      <description>Jackson is a great YBBB from our 4th generation of Ambilobe. Son of Jack, he brings some great blue bars and a yellow body w/ a little less red/orange highlighting than his father. His dam sire is one of our favorites from Bobby Rodduck, so he&amp;rsquo;s a very valuable addition to our project!&#xA;Jackson&#xA;Jackson1&#xA;Jackson2&#xA;Jackson3&#xA;Jackson4&#xA;Jackson5&#xA;Jackson6&#xA;mtDNA Haplogroup* 3 (Ambilobe East) Filial F4-CG13 Sire Jack Dam Mavokely *preliminary results</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nuhana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/14/nuhana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/14/nuhana/</guid>
      <description>Nuhana is an F1 female we produced with our 3rd gen ybbb, Nugget and our captive-hatched (CH) female, Bohana. Her brothers have been pretty diverse in their color scheme. Fingers crossed she takes after her father!&#xA;Nuhana&#xA;Nuhana1&#xA;Nuhana2&#xA;Filial F1-CG5 Sire Nugget Dam Bohana 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Nuhana (F1-CG5) Generation 1 1. Nuhana (F1-CG5). Nuhana was born on 2021-01-14 at iPardalis. She is the daughter of Nugget (F3-CG4) and Bohana (CH).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>manjaya</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/06/manjaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/06/manjaya/</guid>
      <description>Manjaya s Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s sister and she brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with his daughters!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>manjalla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/05/manjalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/05/manjalla/</guid>
      <description>Manjalla is Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s sister and she brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with his daughter!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>coco</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/04/coco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/04/coco/</guid>
      <description>Coco brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She has phenomenal coloring for a female and has been able to lay and bounce back easily thus far. Very healthy girl!&#xA;Coco&#xA;Coco1&#xA;Coco2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>imelda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</guid>
      <description>Imelda brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She layed successfully, but we have been monitoring a minor gular edema on her. We adjusted her supplementation and feeding schedule. Hopefully, it clears up in no time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>lokana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</guid>
      <description>Lokana is the half-sister of Loko. They each have a 50% chance of bringing Kromatisk&amp;rsquo;s amazing ybbb into our project, but Lokana also has Landy x Hamy from her dam, Shirley&amp;rsquo;s side. Really can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with the two possibilities here. We are very excited to see how she proves out over the years :).&#xA;Lokana&#xA;mtDNA Haplogroup* 3 (Ambilobe East) Filial F9-CG13 Sire Kromatisk Dam Shirley *preliminary results</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaia/</guid>
      <description>Manjaia is Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s 3rd sister we own, and she also brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with his daughter!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</guid>
      <description>Manjaka brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with him!&#xA;Manjaka&#xA;Manjaka1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manga</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</guid>
      <description>Manga had some of the nicest yellows from all of Bleu and Patch&amp;rsquo;s sons. He has a striking facial pattern and is a classic Ambilobe panther chameleon. We&amp;rsquo;re very lucky to have him in our 4th generation breeding program.&#xA;Manga&#xA;Manga1&#xA;Manga2&#xA;Manga3&#xA;Manga4&#xA;Manga5&#xA;Manga6&#xA;Manga7&#xA;Manga8&#xA;Filial F4-CG4 Sire Bleu Dam Patch 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Manga Generation 1 1. Manga. Manga was born on 2020-10-28 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Bubbles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/10/15/zanaka-bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/10/15/zanaka-bubbles/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project.&#xA;1st Clutch F3-CG13&#xA;Hatch dates 10/15/2020 - 10/17/2020 Hatch rate 37/39 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bleu x Patch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/09/12/bleu-patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/09/12/bleu-patch/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Patch, and our male from Jeremy Booker, Bleu, from Brightside Chameleons. Bleu is the only male with Stryfe in him and we are excited to see what that brings to the project. Manga was our keeper from this group.&#xA;Bleu x Patch Hatch dates 9/12/2020 - 9/27/2020 Hatch rate 29/32 F1&#xA;F2&#xA;F3&#xA;F4&#xA;Img 3183&#xA;M1&#xA;M2&#xA;Manga7&#xA;Hatch dates 10/28/2020 - 11/17/2020 Hatch rate 33/41 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papafee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</guid>
      <description>Papafee is a monster yellow-bodied Ambilobe. He was our sole holdback from Zanaka and Sunny to carry on in our 4th generation of Ambilobe panther chameleons. His yellows are extremely vibrant and were evident at a young age (2 months). He almost has a neon quality to him and he is about 24&amp;quot; head to tail. A very impressive animal.&#xA;Papafee&#xA;Papafee1&#xA;Papafee2&#xA;Papafee3&#xA;Papafee4&#xA;Papafee5&#xA;Filial F3-CG12 Sire Zanaka Dam Sunny 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Sunny</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project. Papafee is our keeper from this group.&#xA;Zanaka x Sunny F3&#xA;Hatch dates 7/17/2020 - 7/28/2020 Hatch rate 28/29 F1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Alla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing is between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our most successful female, Alla, from RB Barto @Panther Creek Chameleons. Nugget is one of my favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe paired with an all-time great in JJ who comes from some of the most popular Ambilobe lines at Kammerflage Kreations.&#xA;Nugget x Alla F4&#xA;Hatch dates 7/10/2020 - 7/31/2020 Hatch rate 15/20 Aw&#xA;Hb&#xA;Hb1&#xA;Jh&#xA;M1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Husbandry: Furcifer pardalis (Panther Chameleon)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/05/panther-chameleon-husbandry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/05/panther-chameleon-husbandry/</guid>
      <description>Enclosure I tend to use indoor 24&amp;quot;x24&amp;quot;x48&amp;quot; screen enclosures for males, and 18&amp;quot;x18&amp;quot;x36&amp;quot; screen enclosures for females. I add horizontal and vertical boards to the frame which can support 3 levels of horizontal perching branches as well as hold up plants. In the base of the enclosure, I put 12&amp;quot; of bioactive space with drainage, soil barrier, abg mix, spag moss and leaf litter. For microfauna, I use springtails and isopods some red wrigglers and lesser mealworms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing: Furcifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/05/panther-chameleon-caging-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/07/05/panther-chameleon-caging-requirements/</guid>
      <description>We get a lot of questions about caring for a panther chameleon, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d provide an organized response. Here is our strategy for hatchling, baby, juvenile, adult male and adult female Furcifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons).&#xA;Term Age (months) Hatchling 0 - 1 Baby 1 - 4 Juvenile 4 - 8 Adult 8+ Hatchlings We find that it is advantageous to house hatchlings in bio-active tubs because their food items are so small - and would escape screen enclosures - and some hatchlings like to tuck under the leaves near the soil (ABG mix) while digesting their remaining yolk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/18/loko/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/18/loko/</guid>
      <description>Loko is a premium CB Ambilobe from some of the best lines in the USA. Her sire, Kromatisk from Chromatic Chameleons, is one of my favorite active breeders of the locale. My hope is that we can get some little guys that glow yellow from her and Nugget!&#xA;Loko&#xA;Loko1&#xA;Loko2&#xA;Filial Group F5-CG13 Sire Kromatisk Dam Jackie 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Loko Generation 1 1. Loko. Loko was born on 2020-04-18 at Chromatic Chameleons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bing (冰)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/14/bing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/14/bing/</guid>
      <description>Great little girl we got from Frank Payne. I am a huge fan of her shoulder patches and her night sky pattern on the dark body sections. Her older sister, Violet, was our first female; however, we have not gotten any clutches from her yet. Bing is a sweetheart, and we hope to hatch our first clutches from her in 2021!&#xA;Bing&#xA;Bing1&#xA;Bing10&#xA;Bing11&#xA;Bing12&#xA;Bing13&#xA;Bing14&#xA;Bing2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feng (风)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/07/feng/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/07/feng/</guid>
      <description> Another little girl we got from Frank Payne. She&amp;rsquo;s very healthy and vibrant with an nice dark background on her body.&#xA;Feng&#xA;Feng1&#xA;Feng10&#xA;Feng11&#xA;Feng12&#xA;Feng13&#xA;Feng14&#xA;Feng2&#xA;Feng3&#xA;Feng4&#xA;Feng5&#xA;Feng6&#xA;Feng7&#xA;Feng8&#xA;Feng9&#xA;Sire M1 Dam F3 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arti</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</guid>
      <description>Arti is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. He brings some great deep blue bars and a yellow body. We are very excited to see what he produces in concert with our existing lines!&#xA;Arti&#xA;Arti1&#xA;Arti2&#xA;Arti3&#xA;Arti4&#xA;Arti5&#xA;Arti6&#xA;Arti7&#xA;Arti8&#xA;Filial F3-CG12 Sire Artemis Dam Felipe Sanchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Arti Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New iPardalis Genes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/05/newline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/05/newline/</guid>
      <description>Zanaka (F2) Zanaka is F2 because his mother&amp;rsquo;s father was a wild-caught Ambilobe named Herb (Fanitso), owned by Kammerflage Kreations.&#xA;Bohana (CH) Bohana was hatched by Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics from eggs laid by an Ambilobe female imported in 2019.&#xA;Bohana&amp;rsquo;s brothers proved out and are some very nice yellow body blue bar Ambilobe, like this guy owned by Daniel Gordinho named Goldust:&#xA;I was thinking of pairing these two together, but Nugget has really impressed us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/04/amara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/04/04/amara/</guid>
      <description>Amara is Arti&amp;rsquo;s sister from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. It will be interesting to compare her offspring with Arti&amp;rsquo;s to figure out which traits she is carrying from their shared lineage. I have always been curious about the females role in breeding and I think it is the key to producing some extraordinary animals.&#xA;Amara&#xA;Amara1&#xA;Amara2&#xA;Filial F3-CG12 Sire Artemis Dam Felipe Sanchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bohana (CH)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/03/29/bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/03/29/bohana/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful captive hatched (CH) female we picked up from Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics. Her brothers have ranged from true solid red body blue bar (RBBB) to yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe, so it will be extremely interesting to see where she lands. Fingers crossed she is carrying the YBBB genes we specialize in! If not, we will pair her to Alfred next to create some fresh combinations of vibrant, multi-colored Ambilobe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/02/15/kanto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/02/15/kanto/</guid>
      <description>Kanto is a beautiful female we picked up from Living Art by Frank Payne this year because her sire, Brightflame, is a great match for Alfred. All we know is that Brightflame came from a Canvas pairing and that some of the last pairings done were Bolt x Marley and Marley x Outline.&#xA;Kanto&#xA;Kanto1&#xA;Filial Group Unknown Sire Brightflame Dam Triple&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 3 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Kanto Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huo (火)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/01/01/huo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2020/01/01/huo/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful female that we picked up from Kevin Stanford. She has a really nice pitch-black body with a fire tip on the top of her yellow streaks. Stunning specimen of this species! We were able to get a few healthy clutches from her and hope to produce our first clutch from them. She has been very fun to work with thus far.&#xA;Huo&#xA;Huo1&#xA;Huo2&#xA;Huo3&#xA;Huo4&#xA;Huo5&#xA;Huo6</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tigravavy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/12/12/tigravavy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/12/12/tigravavy/</guid>
      <description>Tigravavy is a one of our favorite females from the Jude x Alla clutch. Her brothers have been everything from clean ybbb like Mondrian, Clyde, and Toby to more rainbow Ambilobe like Alfred, Blossom and Jack. Predominantly ybbb but a few beautiful odd balls mixed in. Tigravavy has deep browns and a golden body, great contrast. If her sons have even a fraction of her good looks, they will be wild!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maitso</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/11/13/maitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/11/13/maitso/</guid>
      <description>Maitso&amp;rsquo;s sire, Amarillo, is the top yellow boby blue bar Ambilobe in the USA. He is a vibrant yellow from snout to vent without any red to mess with what he has going on. The only way I could concieve of a way to improve upon him is to get some thicker blue bars on him and get rid of the red on his turrets. We&amp;rsquo;ll see what we can do!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mavokely</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/11/12/mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/11/12/mavokely/</guid>
      <description>Mavokely&amp;rsquo;s sire, Amarillo, is the top yellow boby blue bar Ambilobe in the USA. He is a vibrant yellow from snout to vent without any red to mess with what he has going on. The only way I could concieve of a way to improve upon him is to get some thicker blue bars on him and get rid of the red on his turrets. We&amp;rsquo;ll see what we can do!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alfred</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</guid>
      <description>Alfred is an extreme outlier from the Jude x Alla pairing. We were lucky to keep him because he carries some vibrant, almost dark neon colors. His resting colors are some of the nicest I have ever seen in person and I am very excited to work with him moving forward!&#xA;Alfred&#xA;Alfred1&#xA;Alfred2&#xA;Alfred3&#xA;Alfred4&#xA;Alfred5&#xA;Alfred6&#xA;Alfred7&#xA;Alfred8&#xA;Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</guid>
      <description>Jack is a beautiful Ambilobe from our Jude x Alla pairing. When he was young, his yellows were dominant and covered his entire body. However, as he aged, oranges started to creep into his body from his gular and his tail turned a vibrant red. He is a beautiful animal, but that is not the look we are breeding for long-term, aside from his clean blue bars and yellow body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/08/21/zanaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/08/21/zanaka/</guid>
      <description>Zanaka is a giant F2 Ambilobe from Kammerflage Kreations. His personality was gentle to the extreme and he was hard to get fired up. It was almost as if other males didn&amp;rsquo;t exist, but when he saw a female, he would light up and start bobbing like a mad man. He was a phenomenal animal to work with, but he had a lot more red in his bars than what our long-term project goals are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bubbles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</guid>
      <description>Bubbles is a massive female. At the one year mark, she already weighs 90 grams when receptive. She came from our Jude x Alla pairing and is one of the few females we decided to keep. She&amp;rsquo;s like a giant version of Alla. Healthy, hungry and bold. Very happy we decided to hold on to this girl!&#xA;Bubbles&#xA;Bubbles1&#xA;Bubbles3&#xA;Filial F3-CG12 Sire Jude Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bleu</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/15/bleu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/15/bleu/</guid>
      <description>Bleu is a male we picked up from the Stryfe line. He was raised by Jeremy Booker at Brightside Chameleons, and he was a bit of a challenge to work with. We released him in early 2020 and only produced a few clutches with him. We hope to select some nice males from his offspring to bring that line into our project.&#xA;Bleu&#xA;Bleu1&#xA;Bleu2&#xA;Filial F3-CG11 Sire Stryfe Dam Emma Frost 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Button</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/14/button/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/14/button/</guid>
      <description>Button was a female with nice high contrast barring from Jude x Alla. We bred her a few times before letting her go to make space for fresh genetics, but she was a phenomenal breeder for us! It will be interesting to see how much the high contrast carries into her offspring.&#xA;Button&#xA;Button1&#xA;Filial F3-CG12 Sire Jude Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Button (F3) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blossom</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</guid>
      <description>We got lucky holding back Blossom from Jude x Alla. He looks like a mini-JJ, Alla&amp;rsquo;s sire, and is a key member of our 3rd generation breeding group. His personality is very similar to Alla&amp;rsquo;s in that he is very bold and rarely defensive. His yellows are bright and his colors are very vibrant. I could not be happier with how he has turned out!&#xA;Blossom&#xA;Blossom1&#xA;Blossom2&#xA;Blossom3</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Alla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</guid>
      <description>This has been our most successful pairing to-date. Alla is an amazing female Ambilobe that we purchased from RB Barto in 2017. She has been producing clutches between 25-34 eggs every 60 to 90 days ever since!&#xA;We decided to keep Blossom, Jack, and Afred from this pairing as well as numerous females.&#xA;Jude x Alla Filial F3 Hatch dates 7/9/2019 - 7/20/2019 Hatch rate 30/31 Dsc02741&#xA;Img 2442</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunny</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/10/sunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/10/sunny/</guid>
      <description>Sunny was my second favorite female from the Jude x Kako clutch, hatched 6/5/19. She reminds me a lot of her mother, Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. With any luck we will be able to grap a killer yellow body blue bar male from her and Zanaka.&#xA;Sunny&#xA;Sunny1&#xA;Sunny2&#xA;Filial F3-CG4 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nugget</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</guid>
      <description>Nugget was an alpha male from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. He has many of the traits I love about Jude/Flash. He is a bold YBBB with great lineage. His yellows are more vibrant and his blue bars do not have any red pock marks like Jude. He is an amazingly clean yellow body blue bar Ambilobe.&#xA;Nugget&#xA;Nugget1&#xA;Nugget2&#xA;Nugget3&#xA;Nugget4&#xA;Nugget5&#xA;Filial F3-CG4 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/08/patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/08/patch/</guid>
      <description>Patch was my favorite female from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her line is an extremely strong yellow body blue bar Ambilobe group, so I have high hopes!&#xA;Patch&#xA;Patch1&#xA;Patch2&#xA;Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Patch (F3) Generation 1 1. Patch (F3).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daisy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/07/daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/07/daisy/</guid>
      <description>Daisy also has some really nice purples, hatched 6/5/19 from Jude x Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her 19 male siblings were bright yellow bodied blue bar Ambilobe, with the exception of one male who fired red bar. I hope she can function like a female version of her brother, Nugget, in our pairings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lilly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/06/lilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/06/lilly/</guid>
      <description>Lilly has some really nice purples, hatched 6/5/19 from Jude x Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her daughters will hopefully be equally beautiful, but we have a theory that her coloration indicates her sons will be killer yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe!&#xA;Lilly&#xA;Lilly1&#xA;Lilly2&#xA;Lilly3&#xA;Lilly4&#xA;Filial F3-CG4 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Kako</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/05/jude-kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2019/06/05/jude-kako/</guid>
      <description>This pairing gave us Nugget, Patch, Sunny, Lilly, and Daisy.&#xA;Jude x Kako F2&#xA;Hatch dates 6/5/2019 - 6/19/2019 Hatch rate 34/34 Daisy&#xA;Img 1&#xA;Img 11&#xA;Img 2&#xA;Img 2535&#xA;Img 2584&#xA;Img 2587&#xA;Img 2612&#xA;Img 2619&#xA;Img 2631&#xA;Img 2678&#xA;Img 2718&#xA;Img 2780&#xA;Img 2813&#xA;Img 2828&#xA;Img 2857&#xA;Img 2917&#xA;Img 2919&#xA;Img 2954&#xA;Img 2977&#xA;Img 3224&#xA;Img 3632&#xA;Img 3642&#xA;Img 3873</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Di (地)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2018/11/04/di/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2018/11/04/di/</guid>
      <description> Our first adult male from Frank Payne&#xA;Di&#xA;Sire M3 Dam F5 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alla</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</guid>
      <description>Alla is our most successful female breeder to date. She has a gregarious personality and brings some of the nicest YBBB Kammerflage Kreations lineage into our project via her sire, JJ. We were very lucky to pick her up from Panther Creek Chameleons back in 2017 before JJ was sold to Chromatic Chameleons.&#xA;Alla&#xA;Alla1&#xA;Alla2&#xA;Filial F8-CG11 Sire JJ Dam Blue Bird&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Alla Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kako</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/11/21/kako/</guid>
      <description>Kako was one of the two females we paired with our second generation breeder - Jude. We purchased her from RB Barto, but she was produced by Bobby Ruddock. Her line is one of our favorite yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe lines in the USA. Vibrant yellows and clean blue bars.&#xA;Kako&#xA;Kako1&#xA;Filial Group F2 Sire Sparkles Dam Leo&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 4 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Kako (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash x Judy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/10/17/flash-judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/10/17/flash-judy/</guid>
      <description>This was our first clutch. Both parents, Flash and Judy, were sourced from Bruce Galbraith at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. Our hatch rate was ~50% and 4 of the babies did not make it to the 3 month mark. That was the baseline that we have tried to improve upon. For this clutch, we had used a standard calcium w/ multivitamin twice a month for most of Judy&amp;rsquo;s life, and we raised the babies in what I would call &amp;ldquo;standard&amp;rdquo; baby bins (not fully-planted, bioactive bins like we use today).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.&#xA;Body shot&#xA;Dsc00380&#xA;Dsc00383&#xA;Jude&#xA;Jude2&#xA;Filial Group F2 Sire Flash Dam Judy 4 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Jude (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judy&#39;s First Clutch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/03/21/first-clutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2017/03/21/first-clutch/</guid>
      <description>Female Fucifer pardalis (Panther Chameleons) will rock back and forth with their mouth agape in a defensive posture when they are not ready to mate.&#xA;It is always good to introduce the female into the male&amp;rsquo;s enclosure to avoid injury to either animal because their body language is not for show. Males are often too persistent for their own good. In the beginning of March, Judy climbed willingly into Flash&amp;rsquo;s cage, but we had to try multiple times before she was confortable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Chi-Town Chameleons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/chitown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/chitown/</guid>
      <description> Chi-Town Chameleons Sammy Sammy&#xA;Sammy1&#xA;Sammy2&#xA;Sire Tony Stark Dam Unknown Tony Stark Tony&#xA;Tony1&#xA;Sire Rick Dam Unknown Nova F1&#xA;Nova&#xA;Nova1&#xA;Nova3&#xA;Sire Legion (WC) Dam Magik Storm F2&#xA;Storm&#xA;Sire Nova Dam Natasha Natasha Natasha&#xA;Sire Steve Dam Unknown Steve Steve&#xA;Sire Unknown Dam Unknown </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Colorado Chameleon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/coloradochams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/coloradochams/</guid>
      <description> Colorado Chameleon Arlo (WC) Arlo&#xA;Arlo1&#xA;Arlo2&#xA;Artemis Artemis&#xA;Artemis1&#xA;Artemis2&#xA;Artemis3&#xA;Artemis4&#xA;Artemis5&#xA;Sire Fantara Dam Felipe Sannchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter Perregrin/Pryo&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Sire Perregrin/Pyro Dam Miss Piggy </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kevin Stanford Reptiles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/kevinstanford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/kevinstanford/</guid>
      <description>Kevin Stanford Reptiles Kevin has some really interesting oranges on a lot of his female Furcifer minor. The lineage on&#xA;Huo&amp;rsquo;s Sire Img 5681&#xA;Img 5683&#xA;Huo&amp;rsquo;s Dam Img 5679&#xA;Img 5680&#xA;Huo&amp;rsquo;s Grand Dam Img 5677&#xA;Img 5678</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Living Art by Frank Payne</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/livingart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/livingart/</guid>
      <description> Living Art by Frank Payne Brightflame Unknown&#xA;Brightflame&#xA;Brightflame1&#xA;Sire Canvas Sire (possibly Bolt/Marley) Dam Canvas Dam (possibly Marley or Outline&amp;rsquo;s daughter) Minors Sires M1, M3, M6, M20 Dams F3, F5, F8, F20 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Modern Day Dragons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/moderndaydragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/moderndaydragons/</guid>
      <description> Modern Day Dragons Miss Piggy Sire Higgins Dam Sire Candy Cane PJ Pj&#xA;Pj1&#xA;Pj2&#xA;Sire Perregrin/Pyro Dam Miss Piggy </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Strohl&#39;s Herptiles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/strohlsherptiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/22/strohlsherptiles/</guid>
      <description> Strohl&amp;rsquo;s Herptiles Rick Rick&#xA;Sire Unknown Dam Unknown </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Bobby Ruddock</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/bobbyruddock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/bobbyruddock/</guid>
      <description> Sparkles F1&#xA;Sparkles1&#xA;Sparkles2&#xA;Sire Son of Loza and Flamming River&amp;rsquo;s daughter Dam Unknown WC Amarillo F2&#xA;Amarillo&#xA;Amarillo1&#xA;Sire Sparkles Dam Leo Sasha Sire Sinister </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Brightside Chameleons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/brightside/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/brightside/</guid>
      <description> Brightside Chameleons Stryfe Stryfe&#xA;Stryfe1&#xA;Stryfe2&#xA;Sire Dio Dam Stryfe&amp;rsquo;s Dam Emma Frost Sire Felipe Sanchez Dam Sire Macho Perregrin/Pyro Pyro&#xA;Pyro1&#xA;Pyro2&#xA;Pyro3&#xA;Sire Sparkles Dam Sasha Polaris Sire Cyclops Dam Pheonix Cyclops Cyclops&#xA;Cyclops1&#xA;Cyclops2&#xA;Pheonix Sire Zephyros Dam Unknown Gambit WC&#xA;Gambit&#xA;Gambit1&#xA;Legion WC&#xA;Legion&#xA;Legion1&#xA;Legion2&#xA;Legion3&#xA;Legion4&#xA;Legion5&#xA;Magik Sire Marley Dam Unknown </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Canvas Chameleons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/canvas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/canvas/</guid>
      <description>Canvas Chameleons Marley Marley&#xA;Marley1&#xA;Marley2&#xA;Bolt WC&#xA;Bolt&#xA;Outline Outline&#xA;Outline1&#xA;Sinister Sinister</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Chameleon&#39;s Paradise</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/chameleonparadise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/chameleonparadise/</guid>
      <description>Chameleon Paradise Cowboy WC&#xA;Cowboy&#xA;Cowboy2&#xA;Cowboy3&#xA;Candy Cane F1&#xA;Candy cane&#xA;Candy cane1&#xA;Candy cane2&#xA;Candy cane3&#xA;Jake F1 Jake&#xA;Jake1&#xA;Jake2&#xA;King King&#xA;King1&#xA;24k 24k&#xA;24k1&#xA;24k3&#xA;600 24k1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Chameleons by Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/chamsbydesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/chamsbydesign/</guid>
      <description> Chameleons by Design Rick James (WC) Rickjames&#xA;Rickjames1&#xA;Rickjames2&#xA;Firestarter (WC) Firestarter&#xA;Firestarter1&#xA;Firestarter&amp;rsquo;s daughter Sire Firestarter Dam Dio&amp;rsquo;s daughter </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Charles Yamaguchi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/yamaguchi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/yamaguchi/</guid>
      <description>Charles Yamaguchi Charles Yamaguchi isn&amp;rsquo;t a real person. Elizabeth Lawrence scammed people under this persona selling a bunch of Ambilobe x Nosy Be crosses to people. Her other aliases include: Cami Garden Hat, April Wilcox, Trevor Neufeld, and April Michelle. I would never add a female from this lineage, but I found a great looking male that&amp;rsquo;s a few gens removed from her scam. So the male has proven out, but I will definitely want to run a locale genetic test to confirm the locale of these.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Chromatic Chameleons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/chromatic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/chromatic/</guid>
      <description>Chromatic Chameleons Felipe Sanchez Sire WC Bolt Dam Cowboy&amp;rsquo;s daughter Felipe&#xA;Felipe1&#xA;Felipe2&#xA;Felipe3&#xA;Capella Sire Felipe Sanchez Dam JJ&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Capella&#xA;Capella1&#xA;Capella2&#xA;Capella3&#xA;Kromatisk Sire JJ Dam Daisy Kromatisk&#xA;Kromatisk1&#xA;Kromatisk2&#xA;Kromatisk3&#xA;Jackie Sire Wet Dream Dam Marley&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Shirley Sire Landy (Silk) Dam Hamy (Sweetness) Daisy Sire Seventeen Dam Dio&amp;rsquo;s daughter JJ&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Sire JJ Dam Daisy Kromatisk&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Sire Kromatisk Dam Xanthos&amp;rsquo; daughter Xanthos&amp;rsquo; Daughter Sire Xanthos Dam Sienna Xanthos Sire Unknown Dam Unknown Xanthos</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Highlighter Chameleons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/highlighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/highlighter/</guid>
      <description> Highlighter Chameleons Mango Saphire Mangosaphire&#xA;Sire Karamba-ady (Cage Combat) Dam Telo heny&amp;rsquo;s daughter Flamethrower Flamethrower&#xA;Flamethrower1&#xA;Flamethrower2&#xA;Sire Tropicali Dam Sire [Arira/Thunder&amp;rsquo;s daughter] Copperhead&amp;rsquo;s daughter Sire Copperhead Dam Unknown Grape Inferno Grapeinferno&#xA;Grapeinferno1&#xA;Sire Manga-hay (Blue Heat) Dam Bolitika-zandry (Little Sister) Tropicali Tropicali&#xA;Tropicali1&#xA;Tropicali2&#xA;Sire Unknown Dam Unknown </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Joshua Illencik</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/joshuaillencik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/joshuaillencik/</guid>
      <description>Joshua Illencik Dio Sire Little Foot Dio&#xA;Dio1&#xA;Dio2&#xA;Stryfe&amp;rsquo;s Dam Sire Zeratul Zeratul&#xA;Zeratul1&#xA;Zeratul2&#xA;Dam Sire Noki Noki&#xA;(s)AINT (s) aint&#xA;Sire Nergal Dam Sire Dio Nergal Nergal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kammerflage Kreations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</guid>
      <description>Kammerflage Kreations Manome-toky (Promise Keeper) Sire Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) Dam Vony-reny Promise keeper&#xA;Promise keeper1&#xA;Promise keeper2&#xA;Promise keeper3&#xA;Promise keeper4&#xA;Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) 67102557 214752709408715 5451583889820614656 n&#xA;67119195 2313830222028769 4345136138969677824 n&#xA;Ankoso-bolamena (Goldie) Sire Ihany-drako (My Friend) Dam Hay-vao (Novel) Ihany-drako (My Friend) Sire Ampiosonga-fantatra (Also Known As) Dam Unknown My friend&#xA;Myfriend&#xA;Myfriend1&#xA;Hay-vao (Novel) Sire WC Bakaina (Divergent) Dam Goavy (Guava) Ampiosonga-fantatra (Also Known As) Sire Unknown Dam Unknown Alsoknownas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kaz Chameleons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/kazkameleons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/kazkameleons/</guid>
      <description> Kaz Kameleons Rambo Rambo&#xA;Sire Miroborobo (Blaze) Dam Haran-dranomasina (Coral) Candy Cane&amp;rsquo;s daughter Sire Candy Cane Dam Cowboy&amp;rsquo;s daughter Rambo&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Sire Rambo </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Nature&#39;s Van Gogh</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/naturesvangogh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/naturesvangogh/</guid>
      <description> Nature&amp;rsquo;s Van Gogh Bangheera Bangheera&#xA;Bangheera1&#xA;Bangheera2&#xA;Bangheera3&#xA;Bangheera4&#xA;Sire Mango Saphire Dam Copperhead&amp;rsquo;s daughter Moonclaw Sire Flamethrower Dam Grape Inferno&amp;rsquo;s daughter </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: New England Chameleons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/newenglandchameleons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/newenglandchameleons/</guid>
      <description> New England Chameleons Vulcan Vulcan&#xA;Sire Rick James Dam Firestarter&amp;rsquo;s daughter Odin Odin&#xA;Sire Rambo Dam Candy Cane&amp;rsquo;s daughter Odin&amp;rsquo;s daughter Sire Odin Dam Agent Orange&amp;rsquo;s daughter Agent Orange&amp;rsquo;s daughter Sire Polisy-menapina (Agent Orange) Dam Fantara&amp;rsquo;s daughter </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Company</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/pantherco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/pantherco/</guid>
      <description>Panther Company Leo Leo&#xA;Leo1&#xA;Leo1&#xA;Leo2&#xA;Leo3&#xA;Leo4&#xA;Leo5&#xA;Leo6&#xA;Leo7</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Creek Chameleons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</guid>
      <description>Panther Creek JJ Jj&#xA;Jj1&#xA;Jj2&#xA;Jj3&#xA;Jj4&#xA;Jj5&#xA;Jj6&#xA;Sire Mavo-ra (Yellow Blood) Dam Sire Kely-tongotra (Little Foot) Wet Dream Wetdream&#xA;Wetdream1&#xA;Wetdream2&#xA;Sire Macho Dam Sire 24k&amp;rsquo;s daughter Test Sire Marley Dam Sire Unknown </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Shane Conlin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/shaneconlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/21/shaneconlin/</guid>
      <description> Shane Conlin Macho Macho&#xA;Macho1&#xA;Macho2&#xA;Sire Candy Cane Dam Sire Cowboy </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Chameleons 101</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/20/chams101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/20/chams101/</guid>
      <description> Chameleons101 The Don (WC) 1st&#xA;2nd&#xA;3rd&#xA;4th&#xA;Skyline Skyline&#xA;Sire Unknown Dam Unknown Perregrin/Pryo&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Sire Perregrin/Pyro Dam Miss Piggy Eric Thompson Female Sire Unknown Dam Unknown </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Eye Candy Chameleons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/20/eyecandy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/20/eyecandy/</guid>
      <description> Eye Candy Chameleons DynamiteTNT Dynamite tnt&#xA;Dynamite tnt1&#xA;Dynamite tnt2&#xA;Sire (s)AINT Dam Rambo&amp;rsquo;s Daughter </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Ramblin&#39; Exotics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/20/ramblin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/20/ramblin/</guid>
      <description> Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics Hendrix Hendrix&#xA;Hendrix1&#xA;Hendrix2&#xA;Sire Dante Dam Sunkist Foxey Foxey&#xA;Foxey1&#xA;Foxey2&#xA;Sire Landy (Silk) Dam Hamy (Sweetness) Clapton Clapton&#xA;Clapton1&#xA;Clapton2&#xA;Sire Varatra (Thunderbolt) Dam So-Soa (So Beautiful) Layla Sire DynamiteTNT Dam Sire Mr America Jr. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Rose Exotic Reptiles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/20/roseexoticreptiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/20/roseexoticreptiles/</guid>
      <description> Rose Exotic Reptiles Mr America Jr Mrarmericajr&#xA;Mrarmericajr1&#xA;Sire Mr America Dam Unknown </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Tropical Chameleons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/20/tropical/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/20/tropical/</guid>
      <description> Tropical Chameleons Dante Dante&#xA;Sire Gambit Dam Polaris Sunkist Sire Bolt Dam Test Sonny Sonny&#xA;Sonny1&#xA;Sire Giga-vony (Old Yeller) Dam Fanala-Andriana (Frost Queen) Sonny&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Sire Sonny Dam Unknown </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Brian Collins</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/19/briancollins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/19/briancollins/</guid>
      <description> Higgins Higgins&#xA;Higgins1&#xA;Higgins2&#xA;Sire Pelellu Dam Sire Anguar </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Brian Stewart</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/19/brianstewart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/19/brianstewart/</guid>
      <description> Phone (414-243-9995) McNulty Mcnulty&#xA;Mcnulty1&#xA;Mcnulty2&#xA;Sire Stryfe Dam Sire Unknown Kammers Sire Artemis&amp;rsquo;s Daughter Sire Artemis Dam Felipe Sanchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Mythical Exotics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/19/mythicalexotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2016/03/19/mythicalexotics/</guid>
      <description>Mythical Exotics Zephyros Zephyros</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/02/11/judy/</guid>
      <description>Judy was our first generation breeder from Candy Cane (F1) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. She laid one good clutch for us but died during laying complications after 2 more infertile clutches.&#xA;Judy (1)&#xA;Judy (2)&#xA;Judy (3)&#xA;Judy (4)&#xA;Judy (6)&#xA;Judy 1 year&#xA;Filial Group F2 Sire Candy Cane Dam Jake&amp;rsquo;s daughter 3 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Judy (F2) Generation 1 1. Judy (F2). Judy was born on 2015-02-11 at Chameleon&#39;s Paradise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2015/01/10/flash/</guid>
      <description>Flash was our first generation breeder from Cowboy (CH) at Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Paradise. He had a very gentle personality and only gave us one healthy clutch with Judy, from which we kept Jude. We were still learning when we got Flash and he passed after consuming a large number of wild bugs when pesticides had been applied to the lawn behind ours. The vet said that he had kidney failure like he&amp;rsquo;d been poisoned, but we have been continuing to improve our husbandry year-after-year in his honor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pituophis deppei jani</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/1/01/01/pdjani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/1/01/01/pdjani/</guid>
      <description>We have a small breeding group of &amp;lsquo;18 and &amp;lsquo;19 Pituophis deppei jani (Northern Mexican Pine Snakes). They are a beautiful big-bodied Pituophis species that start out &amp;ldquo;ugly,&amp;rdquo; brown and tan. They are highly variable, and as they age, their colors become more distinct. Many animals develop an orange head and tail. Their back saddle markings wash out in the middle and are crisp near the extremities. They can grow to be up to 9&amp;rsquo; long and are thicker than most colubrids.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
