<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>iPardalis Interviews on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/podcasts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in iPardalis Interviews on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/podcasts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reptile Show Reporter: Jon Hill from iPardalis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/09/23/rsr_jonhill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/09/23/rsr_jonhill/</guid>
      <description>A great discussion with Sean McNeeley where we cover:&#xA;my history in the hobby individually raising Panther Chameleons the impact of husbandry on polygenic traits show strategies to grow the industry and improve outcomes for customers </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Chronicles: Ethics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/23/cc_egg_sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/06/23/cc_egg_sales/</guid>
      <description>Great discussion with Amanda &amp;amp; Lee Ready of Ready&amp;rsquo;s Rainforest, The Reptile Gumbo Podcast, and Dr. Rob Coke DVM about egg sales and other random ideas that popped into our heads.&#xA;We planned on discussing&#xA;Ethics The impact of egg sales on the community Why we chose not to sell eggs This was a great show with 2 chameleon breeders and a top reptile veterinarian.&#xA;Podcast link: Chameleon Chronicles: Ethics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Academy: Chameleon Breeder Husbandry vs Keeper Husbandry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/05/05/ca_keepervsbreeder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/05/05/ca_keepervsbreeder/</guid>
      <description>This is a discussion about whether breeders should get a pass for poor husbandry. We know that the practical constraints of breeding animals for a profit yields a compromising attitude towards husbandry. I believe it should be uncompromising, and I am happy to hold myself to the same standards as my customers. Bill is a leader in this movement and I hope we can encourage more breeders to commit to higher standards of care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mighty Morphing Reptiles: The Ethics of Selling Chameleon Eggs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/04/09/mm_shortcuttotrama/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/04/09/mm_shortcuttotrama/</guid>
      <description>Ryan and Mitch are two breeders who I have a long history with. We met on social media when I got started in the hobby in 2015-2016. We have had late-night discussions on all sorts of drama, challenges, and much needed breeder therapy sessions. Mitch was a major sponsor of the panther chameleon local form genetic test. He creates some crazy cool cross-locale and pure locale panther chameleons, and Ryan started a podcast recently but I knew him from his Cap Est project - which is to-date the best I have seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animals at Home: Selling Chameleon Eggs &amp; Other Unethical Breeding Practices</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/02/12/animalsathome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/02/12/animalsathome/</guid>
      <description>This is a great discussion about our project from an ethical perspective. Dillon over at Animals at Home has created some of the best content on ethical keeping. We were honored to speak with him after he fired an ethical shot across the bow of herpetoculture.&#xA;Care of the animal comes first - business comes second Over production and a breeder&amp;rsquo;s responsibility to market their work Egg sales Group raising vs individual-raising Breeding vs flipping Genetics - polygenic traits and selective breeding Wild caught and importation Parasites and captive health management strategies </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Academy: The Chameleon Hour, Oct 7, 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/10/07/chamhour20221007/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/10/07/chamhour20221007/</guid>
      <description>This episode kicks off with a discussion about chameleon safe plants, Michael Nash on diapause, and finishes up with a discussion between Bill and I about creating a safe environment for chameleon hatchlings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lizard Brain Radio: Episode 31</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/06/lizardbrain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/06/lizardbrain/</guid>
      <description>This podcast is a great introduction to our breeding program and philosophy.&#xA;How we got started individually raising panther chameleons Why we chose to focus on Yellow Body Blue Bar (YBBB) Ambilobe Challenges related to individually raising Selective breeding strategies How we track and document things with Gramps software Our strategy of transparency - we show hundreds of males from a given pairing and don&amp;rsquo;t cherry pick the best ones. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Academy: Hatchling Care Panel Q &amp; A</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/19/ca_hatchlings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/19/ca_hatchlings/</guid>
      <description>This is a great discussion with three men who have more experience than I do: Bill Strand, Sean McNeeley and Chris Young. These guys are some of the OGs of chameleon husbandry, and I really enjoyed listening as much as I enjoyed the opportunity to share my experience.&#xA;Sorry about the bad entry - I had not done many podcasts at this point lol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Academy: Should You Buy a Chameleon Egg? Part 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/17/chameleonacademyeggsalespart2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/17/chameleonacademyeggsalespart2/</guid>
      <description>Bill Strand was my original mentor in the hobby. He has more experience than anyone I know. He is accessible, fair and reliable. There is no other source of information on chameleon husbandry that I trust more.&#xA;In this episode, we get into a topic that is something I am very passionate about - egg sales. When I heard the framing of this question on Bill&amp;rsquo;s podcast, I sent him a long message and he was kind enough to give me a chance to speak my mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Academy: Genetic Testing for Panther Chameleon Locale</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/07/ca_genetictest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/07/ca_genetictest/</guid>
      <description>This episode explains the origins of the genetic test for panther chameleon locale. It features Benson Morrill, PhD of Rare Genetics, Inc. and myself.&#xA;What we know about local forms Challenges that a genetic test would provide better information on Pricing and project stage Data underpinning the test Testing strategy </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon Academy: Chameleon Cage Type Decisions Part 1 - Hybrid</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/15/ca_hybrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/07/15/ca_hybrid/</guid>
      <description>Bill did a great two part series on different caging strategies. We jumped on for the first part because we use a lot of hybrid enclosures here in Maryland. It helps us keep their cage within a healthy humidity range and protects our walls from water damage.&#xA;Podcast Link: Ep 211: Chameleon Cage Type Decisions Part 1 - Hybrid</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
