<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ambilobe-sires on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>https://ipardalis.com/categories/ambilobe-sires/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ambilobe-sires on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ipardalis.com/categories/ambilobe-sires/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</guid>
      <description>Manjaka brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manga</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/10/28/manga/</guid>
      <description>Manga had some of the nicest yellows from all of Bleu and Patch&amp;rsquo;s sons. He has a striking facial pattern and is a classic Ambilobe panther chameleon. We&amp;rsquo;re very lucky to have him in our 4th generation breeding program.
  Manga
      Manga1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papafee</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</guid>
      <description>Papafee is a monster yellow-bodied Ambilobe. He was our sole holdback from Zanaka and Sunny to carry on in our 4th generation of Ambilobe panther chameleons. His yellows are extremely vibrant and were evident at a young age (2 months). He almost has a neon quality to him and he is about 24&amp;quot; head to tail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arti</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/06/arti/</guid>
      <description>Arti is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. He brings some great deep blue bars and a yellow body. We are very excited to see what he produces in concert with our existing lines!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfred</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</guid>
      <description>Alfred is an extreme outlier from the Jude x Alla pairing. We were lucky to keep him because he carries some vibrant, almost dark neon colors. His resting colors are some of the nicest I have ever seen in person and I am very excited to work with him moving forward!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blossom</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</guid>
      <description>We got lucky holding back Blossom from Jude x Alla. He looks like a mini-JJ, Alla&amp;rsquo;s sire, and is a key member of our 3rd generation breeding group. His personality is very similar to Alla&amp;rsquo;s in that he is very bold and rarely defensive. His yellows are bright and his colors are very vibrant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</guid>
      <description>Nugget was an alpha male from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. He has many of the traits I love about Jude/Flash. He is a bold YBBB with great lineage. His yellows are more vibrant and his blue bars do not have any red pock marks like Jude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
