<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ambilobe Sires - Active on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/ambilobe-sires/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ambilobe Sires - Active on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/ambilobe-sires/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Taiyang (WC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/10/03/taiyang/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/10/03/taiyang/</guid>
      <description>Imported by One World Exotica in October 2023.&#xA;WC Taiyang and WC Haiyang are two of my favorite wild caught imports; Taiyang means sun in Chinese because he has a ton of yellow w/ a little mix of orange like the sun, and Haiyang means sea/ocean in Chinese. Haiyang&amp;rsquo;s blue bars are really something for a WC, so we have the sun (Taiyang) and the sea (Haiyang). They both came in great condition, and I hope to be working with them for years to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiyang (WC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/10/02/haiyang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/10/02/haiyang/</guid>
      <description>Imported by One World Exotica in October 2023.&#xA;WC Haiyang came in with some face injuries which make him less likely to get the glam shots on social media; however, we are incredibly happy with him from a genetics and breeding standpoint. His blue bars are the best of all of our WC imports from One World Exotica and his body is very nice as well - green/yellow and only some very sparce red/orange markings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi (WC)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/29/bibi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/29/bibi/</guid>
      <description>Imported by One World Exotica in June 2022.&#xA;Bibi is a very vibrant wild caught (WC) Ambilobe panther chameleon. Bibidia translates to wild in Malagasy, which is why we named our two WC Bibi and Dia. Bibi has a decent amount of red on his face and blue bars with a vibrant green/yellow body. The yellow covers both his body and bars, so his bars almost look green at times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papamavo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/01/papamavo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/03/01/papamavo/</guid>
      <description>Papamavo is one of our 5th generation Ambilobe Panther Chameleon breeders from Papafee x Lokana. He has great vibrancy and a solid yellow body. His attitude is a bit more feisty than his father, but he&amp;rsquo;s calming down a bit now as he reaches adulthood. We are excited to see what he does for us!&#xA;Papamavo&#xA;Papamavo1&#xA;Papamavo2&#xA;Papamavo3&#xA;Papamavo4&#xA;Papamavo5&#xA;Papamavo6&#xA;Papamavo7&#xA;Papamavo8&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimanga</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/jimanga/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/jimanga/</guid>
      <description>Jimanga is one of our 5th gen Ambilobe breeders. He comes from our Manga x Imelda pairing, a great collab with Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics. I can trace his personality all the way back to Kako. They teach you that chameleons are a look-but-don&amp;rsquo;t-touch pet, the hard way haha&amp;hellip; but what comes with that is an absolutely amazing defense display. Definitely something I really enjoy about these guys!&#xA;Jimanga&#xA;Jimanga1&#xA;Jimanga2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/17/ghost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/17/ghost/</guid>
      <description>Ghost is a 4th gen ybbb Ambilobe breeder here at iPardalis. He is from our Arti and Daisy pairing. His yellows are so light when he fires up that we decided to name him Ghost. They are just so clean and bright! There is also an H bar on his right side. We are very excited to have him carry the torch on this part of our tree.&#xA;Ghost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dehibe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/16/dehibe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/10/16/dehibe/</guid>
      <description>Dehibe is a great YBBB Ambilobe we produced with Arti and Alla. He brings some great blue bars and a yellow body, very similar to his sire. He and his sister, Artalla, were the only two babies to survive Alla&amp;rsquo;s last clutch, and they are very special to us. This is a great cb combination without any of our main line in it.&#xA;Dehibe&#xA;Dehibe1&#xA;Dehibe2&#xA;Dehibe3&#xA;Dehibe4&#xA;Dehibe5</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ralph</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/05/ralph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/05/ralph/</guid>
      <description>Ralph is a great 4th generation continuation of the Alfred line with vibrant blues and reds! Alfred was an odd ball from our Jude x Alla pairing, so these red-heavy Ambilobe are not closely related to many of the other red Ambilobe out there. We plan to keep him paired to one or two females and only do a few clutches with this fun side project.&#xA;Ralph&#xA;Ralph1&#xA;Ralph2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zandrin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/04/zandrin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/04/zandrin/</guid>
      <description>Zandrin is our 4th gen HB from Nugget x Loko. He has amazing yellows with blue bars and some vibrant red highlights on his turrets and spine. He is a phenomenal Ambilobe Panther Chameleon.&#xA;Zandrin&#xA;Zandrin1&#xA;Zandrin2&#xA;Zandrin3&#xA;Zandrin4&#xA;Zandrin5&#xA;Zandrin6&#xA;Zandrin7&#xA;Zandrin8&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Nugget Dam Loko 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Zandrin (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Zandrin (F4-CG14). Zandrin was born on 2021-06-04 at iPardalis. He is the son of Nugget (F3-CG4) and Loko (F5-CG13).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kosmo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/05/01/kosmo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/05/01/kosmo/</guid>
      <description>Kosmo is one of my favorite RBBB Ambilobe produced over the past few years. He was sold as an egg by Eric Thompson, purchased as a juvenile by LA Chams and then we acquired him so we could have a solid RBBB Ambilobe project with two unrelated lines. However, because of his many homes, his lineage information was not very well maintained. We know he was from Skyline and another Eric Thompson female, so I do not recommend pairing his offspring with anything from Chameleons101.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>jackson</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/20/jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/01/20/jackson/</guid>
      <description>Jackson is a great YBBB from our 4th generation of Ambilobe. Son of Jack, he brings some great blue bars and a yellow body w/ a little less red/orange highlighting than his father. His dam sire is one of our favorites from Bobby Rodduck, so he&amp;rsquo;s a very valuable addition to our project!&#xA;Jackson&#xA;Jackson1&#xA;Jackson2&#xA;Jackson3&#xA;Jackson4&#xA;Jackson5&#xA;Jackson6&#xA;mtDNA Haplogroup* 3 (Ambilobe East) Filial F4-CG13 Sire Jack Dam Mavokely *preliminary results</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
