<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ambilobe-sires on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/categories/ambilobe-sires/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ambilobe-sires on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/ambilobe-sires/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jimanga</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/12/03/jimanga/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/12/03/jimanga/</guid>
      <description>Jimanga is one of our 5th gen Ambilobe breeders. He comes from our Manga x Imelda pairing, a great collab with Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics. I can trace his personality all the way back to Kako. They teach you that chameleons are a look-but-don&amp;rsquo;t-touch pet, the hard way haha&amp;hellip; but what comes with that is an absolutely amazing defense display. Definitely something I really enjoy about these guys!
Jimanga
Jimanga1
Jimanga2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/17/ghost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/17/ghost/</guid>
      <description>Ghost is a 4th gen ybbb Ambilobe breeder here at iPardalis. He is from our Arti and Daisy pairing. His yellows are so light when he fires up that we decided to name him Ghost. They are just so clean and bright! There is also an H bar on his right side. We are very excited to have him carry the torch on this part of our tree.
Ghost</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dehibe</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/16/dehibe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/16/dehibe/</guid>
      <description>Dehibe is a great YBBB Ambilobe we produced with Arti and Alla. He brings some great blue bars and a yellow body, very similar to his sire. He and his sister, Artalla, were the only two babies to survive Alla&amp;rsquo;s last clutch, and they are very special to us. This is a great cb combination without any of our main line in it.
Dehibe
Dehibe1
Dehibe2
Dehibe3
Dehibe4
Filial F4-CG13 Sire Arti Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zozoro</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/06/zozoro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/06/zozoro/</guid>
      <description>Zozoro is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage sire Gold Rush. His father is my favorite YBBB produced over the past few years and his mother is the combination of a vibrant YBBB named My Friend and a true F1 from two different WC that the Kammer&amp;rsquo;s acclimated recently. Very excited to work this guy into our 4th/5th generation of Ambilobe!
Zozoro
Zozoro1
Zozoro2
Filial F3-CG13 Sire Au-Mirongatra (Gold Rush) Dam Ankoso-Bolamena (Goldie) 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>maro</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/07/13/maro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/07/13/maro/</guid>
      <description>Maro (F3) is a great edition to our YBBB project. We have been tracking the WC Legion line ever since we saw Jeremy Booker acquire him years ago. This great Chi-town Chameleons Sammy x Storm pairing finally carries those genetics with nice yellow bodies on both sides!
Maro
Maro1
Maro2
Maro3
mtDNA Haplogroup* 3 (Ambilobe East) Filial F3 Sire Sammy Dam Storm *preliminary results
5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Maro (F3) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ralph</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/05/ralph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/05/ralph/</guid>
      <description>Ralph is a great 4th generation continuation of the Alfred line with vibrant blues and reds! Alfred was an odd ball from our Jude x Alla pairing, so these red-heavy Ambilobe are not closely related to many of the other red Ambilobe out there. We plan to keep him paired to one or two females and only do a few clutches with this fun side project.
Ralph
Ralph1
Ralph2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zandrin</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/04/zandrin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/04/zandrin/</guid>
      <description>Zandrin is our 4th gen HB from Nugget x Loko. He has amazing yellows with blue bars and some vibrant red highlights on his turrets and spine. He is a phenomenal Ambilobe Panther Chameleon.
Zandrin
Zandrin1
Zandrin2
Zandrin3
Zandrin4
Zandrin5
Zandrin6
Zandrin7
Zandrin8
Filial F4-CG14 Sire Nugget Dam Loko 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Zandrin (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Zandrin (F4-CG14). Zandrin was born on 2021-06-04 at iPardalis. He is the son of Nugget (F3-CG4) and Loko (F5-CG13).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tony</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/01/tony/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/01/tony/</guid>
      <description>Tony one of our 4th generation YBBB Ambilobe. He has some great traits from his dam, Amara, like his deep blue bars and red highlights, but he also has some vibrant yellows from his sire, Nugget. His profile is one of my favorites with striking turret and gular lines. We are very lucky to have him in our breeding group!
Tony
Tony1
Tony2
Tony3
Tony4
Tony5
Tony6
Tony7
Tony8</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kosmo</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/05/01/kosmo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/05/01/kosmo/</guid>
      <description>Kosmo is one of my favorite RBBB Ambilobe produced over the past few years. He was sold as an egg by Eric Thompson, purchased as a juvenile by LA Chams and then we acquired him so we could have a solid RBBB Ambilobe project with two unrelated lines. However, because of his many homes, his lineage information was not very well maintained. We know he was from Skyline and another Eric Thompson female, so I do not recommend pairing his offspring with anything from Chameleons101.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jackson</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/01/20/jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/01/20/jackson/</guid>
      <description>Jackson is a great YBBB from our 4th generation of Ambilobe. Son of Jack, he brings some great blue bars and a yellow body w/ a little less red/orange highlighting than his father. His dam sire is one of our favorites from Bobby Rodduck, so he&amp;rsquo;s a very valuable addition to our project!
Jackson
Jackson1
Jackson2
Jackson3
Jackson4
Jackson5
mtDNA Haplogroup* 3 (Ambilobe East) Filial F4-CG13 Sire Jack Dam Mavokely *preliminary results</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manjaka</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/12/01/manjaka/</guid>
      <description>Manjaka brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with him!
Manjaka
Manjaka1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papafee</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</guid>
      <description>Papafee is a monster yellow-bodied Ambilobe. He was our sole holdback from Zanaka and Sunny to carry on in our 4th generation of Ambilobe panther chameleons. His yellows are extremely vibrant and were evident at a young age (2 months). He almost has a neon quality to him and he is about 24&amp;quot; head to tail. A very impressive animal.
Papafee
Papafee1
Papafee2
Papafee3
Papafee4
Papafee5
Filial F3 Sire Zanaka Dam Sunny 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/06/09/nugget/</guid>
      <description>Nugget was an alpha male from Jude and Kako&amp;rsquo;s first clutch, hatched 6/5/19. He has many of the traits I love about Jude/Flash. He is a bold YBBB with great lineage. His yellows are more vibrant and his blue bars do not have any red pock marks like Jude. He is an amazingly clean yellow body blue bar Ambilobe.
Nugget
Nugget1
Nugget2
Nugget3
Nugget4
Nugget5
Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Kako 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/10/17/jude/</guid>
      <description>Jude was the alpha male from Flash and Judy&amp;rsquo;s clutch, hatched 10/17/17. He has strong yellows and a fierce attitude! We were lucky to select a male that looks a lot like his grandfather, Cowboy. He has now sired the majority of our babies and we will breed him sparingly moving forward.
Body shot
Dsc00380
Dsc00383
Jude
Jude2
Filial Group F2 Sire Flash Dam Judy 4 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Jude (F2) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
