<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ambilobe-dams on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>https://ipardalis.com/categories/ambilobe-dams/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ambilobe-dams on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ipardalis.com/categories/ambilobe-dams/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lelafo</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/04/02/lelafo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/04/02/lelafo/</guid>
      <description>Lelafo is a very different Ambilobe variety that we acquire specifically to keep the fun rolling with the Alfred line! Her Sire, Vulcan, was produced by Chameleons by Design with two very orange WC males and acquired by New England Chameleons who paired him with an amazing female from their orange boy, Odin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>parasy</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/01/21/parasy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2021/01/21/parasy/</guid>
      <description>Parasy is Jackson&amp;rsquo;s sister. She has great YBBB potential from our 4th generation of Ambilobe. We will have to prove her out to see which side of the tree she takes after, but her lineage is phenomenal on both sides. Her dam sire is one of our favorites from Bobby Rodduck, and Jack was one of the best YBBB from our Jude x Alla pairing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>manjalla</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/05/manjalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/05/manjalla/</guid>
      <description>Manjalla is Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s sister and she brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coco</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/04/coco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/04/coco/</guid>
      <description>Coco brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&#39; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She has phenomenal coloring for a female and has been able to lay and bounce back easily thus far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>imelda</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</guid>
      <description>Imelda brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&#39; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She layed successfully, but we have been monitoring a minor gular edema on her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lokana</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</guid>
      <description>Lokana is the half-sister of Loko. They each have a 50% chance of bringing Kromatisk&amp;rsquo;s amazing ybbb into our project, but Lokana also has Landy x Hamy from her dam, Shirley&amp;rsquo;s side. Really can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with the two possibilities here. We are very excited to see how she proves out over the years :).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loko</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/18/loko/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/18/loko/</guid>
      <description>Loko is a premium CB Ambilobe from some of the best lines in the USA. Her sire, Kromatisk from Chromatic Chameleons, is one of my favorite active breeders of the locale. My hope is that we can get some little guys that glow yellow from her and Nugget!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amara</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/04/amara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/04/04/amara/</guid>
      <description>Amara is Arti&amp;rsquo;s sister from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. It will be interesting to compare her offspring with Arti&amp;rsquo;s to figure out which traits she is carrying from their shared lineage. I have always been curious about the females role in breeding and I think it is the key to producing some extraordinary animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bohana (CH)</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/03/29/bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/03/29/bohana/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful captive hatched (CH) female we picked up from Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics. Her brothers have ranged from true solid red body blue bar (RBBB) to yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe, so it will be extremely interesting to see where she lands. Fingers crossed she is carrying the YBBB genes we specialize in! If not, we will pair her to Alfred next to create some fresh combinations of vibrant, multi-colored Ambilobe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maitso</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/11/13/maitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/11/13/maitso/</guid>
      <description>Maitso&amp;rsquo;s sire, Amarillo, is the top yellow boby blue bar Ambilobe in the USA. He is a vibrant yellow from snout to vent without any red to mess with what he has going on. The only way I could concieve of a way to improve upon him is to get some thicker blue bars on him and get rid of the red on his turrets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mavokely</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/11/12/mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/11/12/mavokely/</guid>
      <description>Mavokely&amp;rsquo;s sire, Amarillo, is the top yellow boby blue bar Ambilobe in the USA. He is a vibrant yellow from snout to vent without any red to mess with what he has going on. The only way I could concieve of a way to improve upon him is to get some thicker blue bars on him and get rid of the red on his turrets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daisy</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/07/daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/07/daisy/</guid>
      <description>Daisy also has some really nice purples, hatched 6/5/19 from Jude x Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her 19 male siblings were bright yellow bodied blue bar Ambilobe, with the exception of one male who fired red bar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lilly</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/06/lilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/06/06/lilly/</guid>
      <description>Lilly has some really nice purples, hatched 6/5/19 from Jude x Kako. It will be a lot of fun to watch her eggs hatch to see which traits she is carrying. Her daughters will hopefully be equally beautiful, but we have a theory that her coloration indicates her sons will be killer yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alla</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</guid>
      <description>Alla is our most successful female breeder to date. She has a gregarious personality and brings some of the nicest YBBB Kammerflage Kreations lineage into our project via her sire, JJ. We were very lucky to pick her up from Panther Creek Chameleons back in 2017 before JJ was sold to Chromatic Chameleons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
