<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ambilobe-dams on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/categories/ambilobe-dams/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ambilobe-dams on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/ambilobe-dams/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vaosary</title>
      <link>/blog/2022/01/12/vaosary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022/01/12/vaosary/</guid>
      <description>Vaosary is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has a rusty coloration with even more orange than her sister Bumble Bee. Her first pairing is with our new WC Ambilobe, so we expect her to produce some absolutely amazing F1 YBBB Ambilobe for us!
Vaosary
Vaosary1
Vaosary2
Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Vaosary (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bumble Bee</title>
      <link>/blog/2022/01/11/bumble-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022/01/11/bumble-bee/</guid>
      <description>Bumble Bee is one of our 5th generation HB females from Papafee x Lokana. She has a great personality and a rusty coloration with lots of orange and light purple dots. We expect her to produce some absolutely amazing Ambilobe for us!
Bumblebee
Bumblebee1
Bumblebee2
Bumblebee3
Filial F4-CG14 Sire Papafee Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Bumble Bee (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Bumble Bee (F4-CG14). Bumble Bee was born on 2022-01-11 at iPardalis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artalla</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/15/artalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/15/artalla/</guid>
      <description>Artalla is a very special HB female from Arti, a great ybbb breeder for us produced by Brian Stewart, and Alla, one of our first females and most prolific breeder who gave us 17 clutches over her long life! Artalla has some big shoes to fill, and we are extremely excited to work with her :)
Artalla
Artalla1
Filial F4-CG13 Sire Arti Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Artalla (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainty</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/09/05/mainty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/09/05/mainty/</guid>
      <description>Mainty is one of the nicest RBBB females I could find for Ralph. Her sire, Bangheera, is a classic red body blue bar Ambilobe produced by Highlighter Chameleons and owned by Nature&amp;rsquo;s Van Gogh. After talking to Logan about Mainty&amp;rsquo;s brothers, it looks like many of them proved out to be similar to Grape Inferno or Bangheera, so although Moonclaw&amp;rsquo;s sire is Flamethrower, it seems she took after her dam sire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jiolahy</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/07/14/jiolahy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/07/14/jiolahy/</guid>
      <description>Jiolahy is a big F1 female from Chameleons 101&amp;rsquo;s The Don (WC). She brings fresh ybbb genetics combined with a great CB ybbb line created by Modern Day Dragons. We are very lucky to have her in our breeding group.
Jiolahy
Filial F1-CG5 Sire The Don (WC) Dam Perregrin/Pyro&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Jiolahy (F1-CG5) Generation 1 1. Jiolahy (F1-CG5). Jiolahy was born on 2021-07-14 at Eric Thompson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mara</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/07/13/mara/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/07/13/mara/</guid>
      <description>Mara is the beautiful sister of Maro. They are a pair of Ambilobe breeders we acquired from Chi-Town Chameleons from their Sammy x Nova (F1) pairing. It is looking like Maro is taking after Sammy, so it will be interesting to prove out Mara and see who her sons resemble.
Mara
Mara1
Mara2
Mara3
Mara4
Mara5
Filial F3 Sire Sammy Dam Storm 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Mara (F3) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blaitso</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/19/blaitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/19/blaitso/</guid>
      <description>Blaitso is a drop dead gorgeous 4th gen female from our Blossom x Maitso. She has vibrant oranges, a great bar/body contrast and teal cheeks. Her lineage is also amazing so she will be fun to watch! We are lucky to have her in our breeding group.
Blaitso
Blaitso1
Blaitso2
Blaitso3
Blaitso4
Blaitso5
Filial F4-CG13 Sire Blossom Dam Maitso 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Blaitso (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noko</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/03/noko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/03/noko/</guid>
      <description>Noko is our HB female from Nugget and Loko. Her brother is Zandrin. She should throw some intense yellow and blue with some interesting red highlighting. Her personality is very calm and photogenic. It was incredibly easy to get some nice profile pictures of her!
Noko
Noko1
Noko2
Noko3
Noko4
Noko5
Filial F4-CG14 Sire Nugget Dam Loko 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Noko (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Noko (F4-CG14).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tigerlilly</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/01/tigerlilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/01/tigerlilly/</guid>
      <description>Tiger Lilly is one of the most stunning females I have seen in person. She has an amazing bar/body contrast, organge highlights in her face and turrets and an orang glow on her arms and tail. We are very lucky to get to work with her. Hopefully, those traits are a sign that she is as cool as her sire, Nugget.
Tigerlilly
Tigerlilly1
Tigerlilly2
Tigerlilly3
Tigerlilly4
Tigerlilly5
Filial F4-CG13 Sire Nugget Dam Amara 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>paige</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/04/17/paige/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/04/17/paige/</guid>
      <description>Paige is a solid Modern Day Dragons x Tropical Chameleons YBBB female. She has great purples and pinks and a wonderful personality. We are very lucky to have her in our project and comes to us from Tiffany Mallay. Her first pairing will be with our 4th gen sire, Tony.
Paige
Paige1
Paige2
Filial F4-CG13 Sire PJ Dam Sonny&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Paige (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lelafo</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/04/02/lelafo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/04/02/lelafo/</guid>
      <description>Lelafo is a very different Ambilobe variety that we acquire specifically to keep the fun rolling with the Alfred line! Her Sire, Vulcan, was produced by Chameleons by Design with two very orange WC males and acquired by New England Chameleons who paired him with an amazing female from their orange boy, Odin. She has a ton of orange and red on both sides. Can&amp;rsquo;t wait to prove her out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>parasy</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/01/21/parasy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/01/21/parasy/</guid>
      <description>Parasy is Jackson&amp;rsquo;s sister. She has great YBBB potential from our 4th generation of Ambilobe. We will have to prove her out to see which side of the tree she takes after, but her lineage is phenomenal on both sides. Her dam sire is one of our favorites from Bobby Rodduck, and Jack was one of the best YBBB from our Jude x Alla pairing.
Parasy
Parasy1
Parasy2
Parasy3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nuhana</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/01/14/nuhana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/01/14/nuhana/</guid>
      <description>Nuhana is an F1 female we produced with our 3rd gen ybbb, Nugget and our captive-hatched (CH) female, Bohana. Her brothers have been pretty diverse in their color scheme. Fingers crossed she takes after her father!
Nuhana
Nuhana1
Nuhana2
Filial F1-CG5 Sire Nugget Dam Bohana 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Nuhana (F1-CG5) Generation 1 1. Nuhana (F1-CG5). Nuhana was born on 2021-01-14 at iPardalis. She is the daughter of Nugget (F3-CG4) and Bohana (CH).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>manjaya</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/12/06/manjaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/12/06/manjaya/</guid>
      <description>Manjaya s Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s sister and she brings fresh genetics from a new WC sire, Arlo, who was acclimated by Chris Neeley at Colorado Chameleon. Arlo has a distinct look with red sprinkled on blue bars and a nice yellow body. Very cool Ambilobe import and one of the nicer ybbb with red highlights to come in the past few years. We are very lucky to have the opportunity to work with his daughters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coco</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/12/04/coco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/12/04/coco/</guid>
      <description>Coco brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She has phenomenal coloring for a female and has been able to lay and bounce back easily thus far. Very healthy girl!
Coco
Coco1
Coco2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>imelda</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</guid>
      <description>Imelda brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&amp;rsquo; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She layed successfully, but we have been monitoring a minor gular edema on her. We adjusted her supplementation and feeding schedule. Hopefully, it clears up in no time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lokana</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</guid>
      <description>Lokana is the half-sister of Loko. They each have a 50% chance of bringing Kromatisk&amp;rsquo;s amazing ybbb into our project, but Lokana also has Landy x Hamy from her dam, Shirley&amp;rsquo;s side. Really can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with the two possibilities here. We are very excited to see how she proves out over the years :).
Lokana
mtDNA Haplogroup* 3 (Ambilobe East) Filial F9-CG12 Sire Kromatisk Dam Shirley *preliminary results</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loko</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/04/18/loko/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/04/18/loko/</guid>
      <description>Loko is a premium CB Ambilobe from some of the best lines in the USA. Her sire, Kromatisk from Chromatic Chameleons, is one of my favorite active breeders of the locale. My hope is that we can get some little guys that glow yellow from her and Nugget!
Loko
Loko1
Loko2
Filial Group F5 Sire Kromatisk Dam Jackie 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Loko Generation 1 1. Loko. Loko was born on 2020-04-18 at Chromatic Chameleons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amara</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/04/04/amara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/04/04/amara/</guid>
      <description>Amara is Arti&amp;rsquo;s sister from the Kammerflage Fantara line produced by Brian Stewart in partnership with Colorado Chameleons. It will be interesting to compare her offspring with Arti&amp;rsquo;s to figure out which traits she is carrying from their shared lineage. I have always been curious about the females role in breeding and I think it is the key to producing some extraordinary animals.
Amara
Amara1
Amara2
Filial F3 Sire Artemis Dam Felipe Sanchez&amp;rsquo;s daughter 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bohana (CH)</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/03/29/bohana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/03/29/bohana/</guid>
      <description>Beautiful captive hatched (CH) female we picked up from Busy B&amp;rsquo;s Exotics. Her brothers have ranged from true solid red body blue bar (RBBB) to yellow body blue bar (YBBB) Ambilobe, so it will be extremely interesting to see where she lands. Fingers crossed she is carrying the YBBB genes we specialize in! If not, we will pair her to Alfred next to create some fresh combinations of vibrant, multi-colored Ambilobe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maitso</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/11/13/maitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/11/13/maitso/</guid>
      <description>Maitso&amp;rsquo;s sire, Amarillo, is the top yellow boby blue bar Ambilobe in the USA. He is a vibrant yellow from snout to vent without any red to mess with what he has going on. The only way I could concieve of a way to improve upon him is to get some thicker blue bars on him and get rid of the red on his turrets. We&amp;rsquo;ll see what we can do!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mavokely</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/11/12/mavokely/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/11/12/mavokely/</guid>
      <description>Mavokely&amp;rsquo;s sire, Amarillo, is the top yellow boby blue bar Ambilobe in the USA. He is a vibrant yellow from snout to vent without any red to mess with what he has going on. The only way I could concieve of a way to improve upon him is to get some thicker blue bars on him and get rid of the red on his turrets. We&amp;rsquo;ll see what we can do!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
