<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ambilobe Dams - Active on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/ambilobe-dams/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ambilobe Dams - Active on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/ambilobe-dams/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Avana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/23/avana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023/01/23/avana/</guid>
      <description>Avana has some great Kammerflage Kreations lineage from her sire, Zozoro, and her dam, Artalla. All of her brothers had yellow bodies and a few had deep blue bars. It will be a lot of fun to prove her out with Zandrin - hoping for those blue bars!&#xA;Avana&#xA;Avana1&#xA;Avana2&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Zozoro Dam Artalla 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Avana (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Avana (F4-CG14).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teny</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/10/teny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/09/10/teny/</guid>
      <description>Teny is a beautiful female Ambilobe panther chameleon who we produced with Tony and Paige. Her sire had nice deep blue bars like his dam sire, Artemis with a clean yellow body like Nugget. Her dam brings a great Tropical Chameleons x Modern Day Dragons YBBB lineage from Tiffany Mallay.&#xA;Teny&#xA;Teny1&#xA;Teny2&#xA;Filial F5-CG14 Sire Tony Dam Paige 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Teny (F5-CG14) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kintana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/31/kintana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/31/kintana/</guid>
      <description>Kintana is a line-bred YBBB from Chromatic Chameleons from Capella and Kromatisk. Capella is one of our favorite sires they have produced over the past few years, and Kromatisk is easily one of our favorites over the past decade. We have a decent amount of Felipe Sanchez and JJ/Kromatisk in our existing lines, so we will do our best to avoid those as long as we can. Otherwise, she should bring some more solid genetics from one of the best Ambilobe projects in the USA over at Chromatic Chameleons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mena</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/27/mena/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/07/27/mena/</guid>
      <description>Mena is our HB from Zava and F1 Manjaya. Zava had a significant amount of red and a few of Mena&amp;rsquo;s brothers got it, too. Manjaya seems to have taken after her WC sire, Arlo. A few of Mena&amp;rsquo;s brothers looked like mini Arlo&amp;rsquo;s. So less of the Perregrin/Pyro side of the lineage, more of the WC Arlo combined with Zava is what she brings to the table.&#xA;Mena</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tsara</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/01/tsara/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/06/01/tsara/</guid>
      <description>Tsara Tarehy means attractive in Malagasy. We named the two sisters from Manjaka x Lokana Tsara and Tarehy :). Check out that clutch to see how consistent their YBBB phenotypes were. It is a very good proxy for what these two sisters bring to the table: great yellows and bars that shift from Landy to Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s blues. Very good complement to our existing lines!&#xA;Tsara&#xA;Tsara1&#xA;Tsara2&#xA;Filial F2-CG14 Sire Manjaka Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarehy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/31/tarehy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/05/31/tarehy/</guid>
      <description>Tsara Tarehy means attractive in Malagasy. We named the two sisters from Manjaka x Lokana Tsara and Tarehy :). Check out that clutch to see how consistent their YBBB phenotypes were. It is a very good proxy for what these two sisters bring to the table: great yellows and bars that shift from Landy to Manjaka&amp;rsquo;s blues. Very good complement to our existing lines!&#xA;Tarehy&#xA;Tarehy1&#xA;Tarehy2&#xA;Filial F2-CG14 Sire Manjaka Dam Lokana 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artilly</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/03/artilly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/02/03/artilly/</guid>
      <description>Artilly is a great YBBB from our Arti x Lilly pairing. Arti is one of our favorite ybbb breeders who we mixed in at the 3rd gen and Lilly is a female from our Jude x Kako group. We did not get too many examples from the small clutch that produced her, so it will be a lot of fun to prove her out!&#xA;Artilly&#xA;Artilly1&#xA;Artilly2&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Arti Dam Lilly 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squash</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/14/squash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022/01/14/squash/</guid>
      <description>Squash is a great YBBB Ambilobe female from our good friend Brian Stewart. McNulty is a male from one of Brian&amp;rsquo;s old projects from the Stryfe line and he paired him up with a female from one of his recent pairings with Artemis from Colorado Chameleons. These should be a lot of fun to prove out because they have three ybbb sires in the closest lineage. Top notch stuff as always!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pepita</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/07/pepita/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/07/pepita/</guid>
      <description>Pepita is a great 5th gen YBBB from our Papafee x Coco pairing. She only had 3 brothers, and at least one looked a lot like the Landy side of Coco&amp;rsquo;s lineage. Therefore, my expectation is that Pepita will throw Papafee or Landy looks. It will be a lot of fun to see what she does for us. She definitely resembles Coco more than Papafee&amp;rsquo;s dam, Sunny.&#xA;Pepita&#xA;Pepita1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimelda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/jimelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/12/03/jimelda/</guid>
      <description>Jimelda is Jimanga&amp;rsquo;s sister from our Manga x Imelda pairing. She has some wonderful purples and a fiesty attitude! Manga was one of our best ybbb of all time, so we are really hoping Jimelda carries some of those traits into an F1 gen with WC Bibi. Those could very well be some of the best in the country if they prove out.&#xA;Jimelda&#xA;Jimelda1&#xA;Jimelda2&#xA;Jimelda3&#xA;Jimelda4&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Manga Dam Imelda 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blaitso</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/19/blaitso/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/19/blaitso/</guid>
      <description>Blaitso is a drop dead gorgeous 4th gen female from our Blossom x Maitso. She has vibrant oranges, a great bar/body contrast and teal cheeks. Her lineage is also amazing so she will be fun to watch! We are lucky to have her in our breeding group.&#xA;Blaitso&#xA;Blaitso1&#xA;Blaitso2&#xA;Blaitso3&#xA;Blaitso4&#xA;Blaitso5&#xA;Filial F4-CG13 Sire Blossom Dam Maitso 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Blaitso (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/03/noko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2021/06/03/noko/</guid>
      <description>Noko is our HB female from Nugget and Loko. Her brother is Zandrin. She should throw some intense yellow and blue with some interesting red highlighting. Her personality is very calm and photogenic. It was incredibly easy to get some nice profile pictures of her!&#xA;Noko&#xA;Noko1&#xA;Noko2&#xA;Noko3&#xA;Noko4&#xA;Noko5&#xA;Filial F4-CG14 Sire Nugget Dam Loko 5 Generation Tree&#xA;Ancestral Report for Noko (F4-CG14) Generation 1 1. Noko (F4-CG14).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
