<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>alla on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>https://ipardalis.com/tags/alla/</link>
    <description>Recent content in alla on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ipardalis.com/tags/alla/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Alla</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing is between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our most successful female, Alla, from RB Barto @Panther Creek Chameleons. Nugget is one of my favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe paired with an all-time great in JJ who comes from some of the most popular Ambilobe lines at Kammerflage Kreations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfred</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</guid>
      <description>Alfred is an extreme outlier from the Jude x Alla pairing. We were lucky to keep him because he carries some vibrant, almost dark neon colors. His resting colors are some of the nicest I have ever seen in person and I am very excited to work with him moving forward!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</guid>
      <description>Jack is a beautiful Ambilobe from our Jude x Alla pairing. When he was young, his yellows were dominant and covered his entire body. However, as he aged, oranges started to creep into his body from his gular and his tail turned a vibrant red. He is a beautiful animal, but that is not the look we are breeding for long-term, aside from his clean blue bars and yellow body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubbles</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</guid>
      <description>Bubbles is a massive female. At the one year mark, she already weighs 90 grams when receptive. She came from our Jude x Alla pairing and is one of the few females we decided to keep. She&amp;rsquo;s like a giant version of Alla. Healthy, hungry and bold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Button</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/14/button/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/14/button/</guid>
      <description>Button was a female with nice high contrast barring from Jude x Alla. We bred her a few times before letting her go to make space for fresh genetics, but she was a phenomenal breeder for us! It will be interesting to see how much the high contrast carries into her offspring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blossom</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</guid>
      <description>We got lucky holding back Blossom from Jude x Alla. He looks like a mini-JJ, Alla&amp;rsquo;s sire, and is a key member of our 3rd generation breeding group. His personality is very similar to Alla&amp;rsquo;s in that he is very bold and rarely defensive. His yellows are bright and his colors are very vibrant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Alla</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</guid>
      <description>This has been our most successful pairing to-date. Alla is an amazing female Ambilobe that we purchased from RB Barto in 2017. She has been producing clutches between 25-34 eggs every 60 to 90 days ever since!
We decided to keep Blossom, Jack, and Afred from this pairing as well as numerous females.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alla</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</guid>
      <description>Alla is our most successful female breeder to date. She has a gregarious personality and brings some of the nicest YBBB Kammerflage Kreations lineage into our project via her sire, JJ. We were very lucky to pick her up from Panther Creek Chameleons back in 2017 before JJ was sold to Chromatic Chameleons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kammerflage Kreations</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</guid>
      <description>Kammerflage Kreations  Manome-toky (Promise Keeper)  Sire Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) Dam Vony-reny    Promise keeper
      Promise keeper1
      Promise keeper2
      Promise keeper3
      Promise keeper4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Creek Chameleons</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</guid>
      <description>Panther Creek  JJ   Jj
      Jj1
      Jj2
      Jj3
      Jj4
      Jj5
      Jj6
      Sire Mavo-ra (Yellow Blood) Dam Sire Kely-tongotra (Little Foot)   Wet Dream   Wetdream</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
