<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>alla on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/alla/</link>
    <description>Recent content in alla on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/alla/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dehibe</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/16/dehibe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/16/dehibe/</guid>
      <description>Dehibe is a great YBBB Ambilobe we produced with Arti and Alla. He brings some great blue bars and a yellow body, very similar to his sire. He and his sister, Artalla, were the only two babies to survive Alla&amp;rsquo;s last clutch, and they are very special to us. This is a great cb combination without any of our main line in it.
Dehibe
Dehibe1
Dehibe2
Dehibe3
Dehibe4
Filial F4-CG13 Sire Arti Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artalla</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/15/artalla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/15/artalla/</guid>
      <description>Artalla is a very special HB female from Arti, a great ybbb breeder for us produced by Brian Stewart, and Alla, one of our first females and most prolific breeder who gave us 17 clutches over her long life! Artalla has some big shoes to fill, and we are extremely excited to work with her :)
Artalla
Artalla1
Filial F4-CG13 Sire Arti Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Artalla (F4-CG13) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arti x Alla</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/10/15/arti-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/10/15/arti-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our most prolific female from Panther Creek Chameleons, Alla, and our male from Brian Stewart, Arti. Arti comes from some great Ambilobe lines from Colorado Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Alla is a wonderful female from JJ who was produced by Kammerflage Kreations. We only had a single clutch from these two because it was towards the end of Alla&amp;rsquo;s breeding career.
Arti x Alla Hatch dates 10/15/2021 - 10/19/2021 Hatch rate 3/20 Dehibe</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nugget x Alla</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/07/10/nugget-alla/</guid>
      <description>This pairing is between our third generation hold back, Nugget, and our most successful female, Alla, from RB Barto @Panther Creek Chameleons. Nugget is one of my favorite yellow-bodied blue bar Ambilobe paired with an all-time great in JJ who comes from some of the most popular Ambilobe lines at Kammerflage Kreations.
Nugget x Alla F4
Hatch dates 7/10/2020 - 7/31/2020 Hatch rate 15/20 Aw
Hb
Hb1
Jh
M1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tigravavy</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/12/12/tigravavy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/12/12/tigravavy/</guid>
      <description>Tigravavy is a one of our favorite females from the Jude x Alla clutch. Her brothers have been everything from clean ybbb like Mondrian, Clyde, and Toby to more rainbow Ambilobe like Alfred, Blossom and Jack. Predominantly ybbb but a few beautiful odd balls mixed in. Tigravavy has deep browns and a golden body, great contrast. If her sons have even a fraction of her good looks, they will be wild!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfred</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/10/21/alfred/</guid>
      <description>Alfred is an extreme outlier from the Jude x Alla pairing. We were lucky to keep him because he carries some vibrant, almost dark neon colors. His resting colors are some of the nicest I have ever seen in person and I am very excited to work with him moving forward!
Alfred
Alfred1
Alfred2
Alfred3
Alfred4
Alfred5
Alfred6
Alfred7
Alfred8
Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/10/20/jack/</guid>
      <description>Jack is a beautiful Ambilobe from our Jude x Alla pairing. When he was young, his yellows were dominant and covered his entire body. However, as he aged, oranges started to creep into his body from his gular and his tail turned a vibrant red. He is a beautiful animal, but that is not the look we are breeding for long-term, aside from his clean blue bars and yellow body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bubbles</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/08/16/bubbles/</guid>
      <description>Bubbles is a massive female. At the one year mark, she already weighs 90 grams when receptive. She came from our Jude x Alla pairing and is one of the few females we decided to keep. She&amp;rsquo;s like a giant version of Alla. Healthy, hungry and bold. Very happy we decided to hold on to this girl!
Bubbles
Bubbles1
Bubbles3
Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Button</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/07/14/button/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/07/14/button/</guid>
      <description>Button was a female with nice high contrast barring from Jude x Alla. We bred her a few times before letting her go to make space for fresh genetics, but she was a phenomenal breeder for us! It will be interesting to see how much the high contrast carries into her offspring.
Button
Button1
Filial F3 Sire Jude Dam Alla 5 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Button (F3) Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blossom</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/07/09/blossom/</guid>
      <description>We got lucky holding back Blossom from Jude x Alla. He looks like a mini-JJ, Alla&amp;rsquo;s sire, and is a key member of our 3rd generation breeding group. His personality is very similar to Alla&amp;rsquo;s in that he is very bold and rarely defensive. His yellows are bright and his colors are very vibrant. I could not be happier with how he has turned out!
Blossom
Blossom1
Blossom2
Blossom3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jude x Alla</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/07/09/jude-alla/</guid>
      <description>This has been our most successful pairing to-date. Alla is an amazing female Ambilobe that we purchased from RB Barto in 2017. She has been producing clutches between 25-34 eggs every 60 to 90 days ever since!
We decided to keep Blossom, Jack, and Afred from this pairing as well as numerous females.
Jude x Alla Filial F3 Hatch dates 7/9/2019 - 7/20/2019 Hatch rate 30/31 Dsc02741
Img 2442</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alla</title>
      <link>/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018/01/30/alla/</guid>
      <description>Alla is our most successful female breeder to date. She has a gregarious personality and brings some of the nicest YBBB Kammerflage Kreations lineage into our project via her sire, JJ. We were very lucky to pick her up from Panther Creek Chameleons back in 2017 before JJ was sold to Chromatic Chameleons.
Alla
Alla1
Alla2
Filial Unknown Sire JJ Dam Blue Bird&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 3 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Alla Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kammerflage Kreations</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</guid>
      <description>Kammerflage Kreations Manome-toky (Promise Keeper) Sire Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) Dam Vony-reny Promise keeper
Promise keeper1
Promise keeper2
Promise keeper3
Promise keeper4
Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) 67102557 214752709408715 5451583889820614656 n
67119195 2313830222028769 4345136138969677824 n
Ankoso-bolamena (Goldie) Sire Ihany-drako (My Friend) Dam Hay-vao (Novel) Ihany-drako (My Friend) Sire Ampiosonga-fantatra (Also Known As) Dam Unknown My friend
Myfriend
Myfriend1
Hay-vao (Novel) Sire WC Bakaina (Divergent) Dam Goavy (Guava) Ampiosonga-fantatra (Also Known As) Sire Unknown Dam Unknown Alsoknownas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Panther Creek Chameleons</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/panthercreek/</guid>
      <description>Panther Creek JJ Jj
Jj1
Jj2
Jj3
Jj4
Jj5
Jj6
Sire Mavo-ra (Yellow Blood) Dam Sire Kely-tongotra (Little Foot) Wet Dream Wetdream
Wetdream1
Wetdream2
Sire Macho Dam Sire 24k&amp;rsquo;s daughter Test Sire Bolt Dam Sire Marley </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
