<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kanto on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/kanto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kanto on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/kanto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ralph</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/06/05/ralph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/06/05/ralph/</guid>
      <description>Ralph is a great 4th generation continuation of the Alfred line with vibrant blues and reds! Alfred was an odd ball from our Jude x Alla pairing, so these red-heavy Ambilobe are not closely related to many of the other red Ambilobe out there. We plan to keep him paired to one or two females and only do a few clutches with this fun side project.
Ralph
Ralph1
Ralph2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfred x Kanto</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/04/13/alfred-kanto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/04/13/alfred-kanto/</guid>
      <description>This pairing was between our third generation hold back, Alfred, and our female from Frank Payne, Kanto, from Living Art by Frank Payne. Kanto comes from some great OBBB/RBBB lines from Canvas Chameleons and Kammerflage Kreations, and Alfred is the male with the most red from our Jude x Alla clutch. We kept Ralph from this group and he is a wonderful RBBB!
Alfred x Kanto Hatch dates 4/13/2021 - 5/04/2021 Hatch rate 22/24 No pictures available</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanto</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/02/15/kanto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/02/15/kanto/</guid>
      <description>Kanto is a beautiful female we picked up from Living Art by Frank Payne this year because her sire, Brightflame, is a great match for Alfred. All we know is that Brightflame came from a Canvas pairing and that some of the last pairings done were Bolt x Marley and Marley x Outline.
Kanto
Kanto1
Filial Group Unknown Sire Brightflame Dam Triple&amp;rsquo;s Daughter 3 Generation Tree
Ancestral Report for Kanto Generation 1 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Living Art by Frank Payne</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/22/livingart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/22/livingart/</guid>
      <description> Living Art by Frank Payne Brightflame Unknown
Brightflame
Brightflame1
Sire Canvas Sire (possibly Bolt/Marley) Dam Canvas Dam (possibly Marley or Outline&amp;rsquo;s daughter) Minors Sires M1, M3, M6, M20 Dams F3, F5, F8, F20 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Canvas Chameleons</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/canvas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/canvas/</guid>
      <description>Canvas Chameleons Marley Marley
Marley1
Marley2
Bolt WC
Bolt
Outline Outline
Outline1
Sinister Sinister</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
