<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Promise Keeper on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>/tags/promise-keeper/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Promise Keeper on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/promise-keeper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>zava</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/03/21/zava/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/03/21/zava/</guid>
      <description>Zava is a great YBBB from the Kammerflage Kreations Green Giant x Promise Keeper pairing, produced by Ed Kammer. He brings some great deep blue bars and a yellow body with a significant amount of red highlighting. We were really hoping he&amp;rsquo;d have less red and more yellow, so we only did a few clutches with him.
Zava
Zava1
Zava2
Zava3
Zava4
Zava5
Zava6
Filial F3-CG13 Sire Itso-triombe (Green Giant) Dam Jiona (June) 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Daisy</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/03/08/zanaka-daisy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/03/08/zanaka-daisy/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project.
Zanaka x Daisy F3-CG5
Hatch dates 3/8/2021 - 3/20/2021 Hatch rate 21/26 F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Bubbles</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/10/15/zanaka-bubbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/10/15/zanaka-bubbles/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project.
Zanaka x Bubbles F3-CG13
Hatch dates 10/15/2020 - 10/17/2020 Hatch rate 37/39 F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papafee</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</guid>
      <description>Papafee is a monster yellow-bodied Ambilobe. He was our sole holdback from Zanaka and Sunny to carry on in our 4th generation of Ambilobe panther chameleons. His yellows are extremely vibrant and were evident at a young age (2 months). He almost has a neon quality to him and he is about 24&amp;quot; head to tail. A very impressive animal.
Papafee
Papafee1
Papafee2
Papafee3
Papafee4
Papafee5
Filial F3 Sire Zanaka Dam Sunny 5 Generation Tree</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Sunny</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project. Papafee is our keeper from this group.
Zanaka x Sunny F3
Hatch dates 7/17/2020 - 7/28/2020 Hatch rate 28/29 F1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/08/21/zanaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/08/21/zanaka/</guid>
      <description>Zanaka is a giant F2 Ambilobe from Kammerflage Kreations. His personality was gentle to the extreme and he was hard to get fired up. It was almost as if other males didn&amp;rsquo;t exist, but when he saw a female, he would light up and start bobbing like a mad man. He was a phenomenal animal to work with, but he had a lot more red in his bars than what our long-term project goals are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kammerflage Kreations</title>
      <link>/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</guid>
      <description>Kammerflage Kreations Manome-toky (Promise Keeper) Sire Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) Dam Vony-reny Promise keeper
Promise keeper1
Promise keeper2
Promise keeper3
Promise keeper4
Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) 67102557 214752709408715 5451583889820614656 n
67119195 2313830222028769 4345136138969677824 n
Ankoso-bolamena (Goldie) Sire Ihany-drako (My Friend) Dam Hay-vao (Novel) Ihany-drako (My Friend) Sire Ampiosonga-fantatra (Also Known As) Dam Unknown My friend
Myfriend
Myfriend1
Hay-vao (Novel) Sire WC Bakaina (Divergent) Dam Goavy (Guava) Ampiosonga-fantatra (Also Known As) Sire Unknown Dam Unknown Alsoknownas</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
