<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Promise Keeper on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>https://ipardalis.com/tags/promise-keeper/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Promise Keeper on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ipardalis.com/tags/promise-keeper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Papafee</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/17/papafee/</guid>
      <description>Papafee is a monster yellow-bodied Ambilobe. He was our sole holdback from Zanaka and Sunny to carry on in our 4th generation of Ambilobe panther chameleons. His yellows are extremely vibrant and were evident at a young age (2 months). He almost has a neon quality to him and he is about 24&amp;quot; head to tail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka x Sunny</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/07/17/zanaka-sunny/</guid>
      <description>We added Zanaka (F2) to our project because he is the product of one of Kammerflage Kreations&amp;rsquo;s top yellow-bodied Ambilobe, Promise Keeper, and a classic WC Ambilobe, Fanitso. We paired him with both of our main 3rd gen lines from Jude with the goal of producing something a bit different and adding new blood to the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zanaka</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/08/21/zanaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2019/08/21/zanaka/</guid>
      <description>Zanaka is a giant F2 Ambilobe from Kammerflage Kreations. His personality was gentle to the extreme and he was hard to get fired up. It was almost as if other males didn&amp;rsquo;t exist, but when he saw a female, he would light up and start bobbing like a mad man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lineage: Kammerflage Kreations</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2016/03/21/kammerflage/</guid>
      <description>Kammerflage Kreations  Manome-toky (Promise Keeper)  Sire Bararata-fatio (Bamboo Falcon) Dam Vony-reny    Promise keeper
      Promise keeper1
      Promise keeper2
      Promise keeper3
      Promise keeper4</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
