<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>landy on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</title>
    <link>https://ipardalis.com/tags/landy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in landy on iPardalis - Ambilobe Panther Chameleons for sale. Panther chameleons for sale near me.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ipardalis.com/tags/landy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>coco</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/04/coco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/04/coco/</guid>
      <description>Coco brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&#39; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She has phenomenal coloring for a female and has been able to lay and bounce back easily thus far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>imelda</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/03/imelda/</guid>
      <description>Imelda brings a new WC line from Brightside Chameleon&amp;rsquo;s Gambit into our project via Hendrix/Dante from Ramblin&#39; Exotics! Hendrix is a great mix of two recent WC sires, Gambit and Bolt, and we are very excited to add his daughter to our breeding group. She layed successfully, but we have been monitoring a minor gular edema on her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lokana</title>
      <link>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ipardalis.com/blog/2020/12/02/lokana/</guid>
      <description>Lokana is the half-sister of Loko. They each have a 50% chance of bringing Kromatisk&amp;rsquo;s amazing ybbb into our project, but Lokana also has Landy x Hamy from her dam, Shirley&amp;rsquo;s side. Really can&amp;rsquo;t go wrong with the two possibilities here. We are very excited to see how she proves out over the years :).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
